<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-10-25 03:43:57"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 09:55:00" d="2020-11-01 11:00:00"><n u="George Clarke's Amazing Spaces">George Clarke's Amazing Spaces VI (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>George meets a teacher building a classroom in a salvaged jet and a Devon couple turning a cricket scorebox into a garden hang-out. Plus:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 11:00:00" d="2020-11-01 12:00:00"><n u="George Clarke's Amazing Spaces">George Clarke's Amazing Spaces VI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Lincolnshire, a couple are adding a dance floor to a rare campervan, while a small Stirlingshire business converts a Sea King helicopter into luxury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 12:00:00" d="2020-11-01 13:00:00"><n u="George Clarke's Amazing Spaces">George Clarke's Amazing Spaces VI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>George meets a Dorset couple building a room with views over Chesil Beach. There's also a canine campervan, and a remote lodge made almost entirely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 13:00:00" d="2020-11-01 13:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Devon. The first host, glamorous 51-year-old community nurse Tina, plans a menu that incorporates all of her favourite dishes, including a seaside-inspired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 13:35:00" d="2020-11-01 14:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Devon. Rob serves an Italian menu and gets his guests to draw each other in a no-holds-barred sketching session. What could possibly go wrong? (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 14:05:00" d="2020-11-01 14:40:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Devon. Pilot Rhys hopes to take the competition to new heights. But he's mistaken for a stripper, and Holly gets the hump when she's thrown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 14:40:00" d="2020-11-01 15:10:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Devon. HR manager Holly plans a menu inspired by her restaurant favourites. But her loo rules shock her guests - as does the revealing portrait</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 15:10:00" d="2020-11-01 15:40:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Devon. Detective Steve is counting on a menu of bold flavours to win him the grand, on an evening full of fun, friction, feuding and experimental food. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 15:40:00" d="2020-11-01 16:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Health-conscious Andy Peters and his friend Jeronime host at Rooms 36 in the Lake District. But Andy's healthy breakfast and expensive furniture don't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 16:10:00" d="2020-11-01 16:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Trish and her son Connor host at the Red Lion Coaching Inn, near Gainsborough. Julie and James aren't impressed by the dated bathrooms, and the mattresses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 16:40:00" d="2020-11-01 17:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The third visit is to Schiehallion Hotel in Aberfeldy, run by Julie Dunbar and James Graham. But luxury-lovers Andy and Jeronime are once again left wanting more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 17:15:00" d="2020-11-01 17:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Stephen and Jan host the last visit of the week at Townhead Hotel in Lockerbie. The guests are impressed by the high level of finish, but Andy and Jeronime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 17:50:00" d="2020-11-01 18:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;Bers meet for the last time. There's tension in the air as the payments are revealed and the winner is announced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 18:20:00" d="2020-11-01 18:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Swansea area. DJ Kevin hosts a Spanish-themed night of laughter, singing and flirting, inspired by his favourite holiday destination: Benidorm. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 18:50:00" d="2020-11-01 19:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Swansea area. Café bar owner Tino serves up an African banquet inspired by her homeland, and teaches her guests to twerk. But former bodybuilder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 19:25:00" d="2020-11-01 19:55:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Swansea area. Natalie has made some daft comments on the first two nights, and now her guests have low expectations. But will her George Michael-themed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 19:55:00" d="2020-11-01 20:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Swansea area. Sales manager Rob serves up a simple but tasty Thai menu. But his main is very similar to his starter, and his dessert takes 'simple'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 20:25:00" d="2020-11-01 21:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Swansea area. The final host, GP Janine, hopes to serve an ace tennis-themed evening. The guests turn up dressed for Centre Court, with Rob in a miniskirt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 21:00:00" d="2020-11-01 22:00:00"><n>Autumn at Jimmy's Farm</n><e>F</e>    <k>The wildlife park welcomes an anteater, Nero the stud ram is introduced to his ewes, and there's joy and tragedy in the paddocks as Jimmy gets to grips</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 22:00:00" d="2020-11-01 23:00:00"><n>Emergency Rescue: Air, Land &amp; Sea</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Emergency Rescue: Air,. 
. and &amp; Sea: Brand new series: Inverness Search and Rescue scramble when a vessel's hit by a freak wave at sea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 23:00:00" d="2020-11-02 00:05:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The series that looks at modern Britain through the eyes of our ambulance staff. This episode follows paramedics as they help people who are having</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 00:05:00" d="2020-11-02 01:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Independent 80-year-old Frances has fallen into her empty swimming pool. Jerry, who's 20, is starting to question partying until 5am on a weeknight after ending up in A&amp;E</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 01:05:00" d="2020-11-02 02:05:00"><n u="Ramsay's Hotel Hell">Ramsay's Hotel Hell III (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Gordon checks into the Vienna Inn, an Austrian-themed hotel and restaurant in Southbridge, Massachusetts, where business isn't what it used to be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 02:05:00" d="2020-11-02 03:05:00"><n>Emergency Rescue: Air, Land &amp; Sea</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series: Inverness Search and Rescue scramble when a vessel is hit by a freak wave in the North Sea. And a nine-year-old with appendicitis needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 03:05:00" d="2020-11-02 04:10:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick VI (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
A Saint Bernard suffering with hip dysplasia and a collie that's been hit by a car are brought into the clinic for treatment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 04:10:00" d="2020-11-02 09:55:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>85% Rock-a-Hula Ted: A feminist protest singer arrives on the island just as Ted is about to judge the Lovely Girls competition</k>  </p>
</a>
