<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-10-30 03:40:59"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 09:55:00" d="2020-11-06 10:15:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and furniture maker Anselm Fraser help Jannine and Shaun Cartwright build treasure chests for their young boys' toys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 10:15:00" d="2020-11-06 11:05:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Laura Hamilton house-hunts near Limoges in France with Gary and Maggie from Norfolk. They want a place to retire to that's big enough for all the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 11:05:00" d="2020-11-06 12:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole finds a treat for restorer Guy, and Simon O'Brien creates stunning table lamps from old theatre lights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 12:05:00" d="2020-11-06 13:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Max McMurdo travel the length of Britain looking for items to fix up and flog. In Wales, picks include an oil dispenser, a chaise longue and a catamaran</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 13:05:00" d="2020-11-06 14:10:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Dick joins the search for a stash of wine said to have been hidden during World War II in Jonathan and Michael's caves. Fiona starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 14:10:00" d="2020-11-06 15:15:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Alan and Lucy are building an upside-down house in Fife with stunning views of the Forth Bridge. Alan knows what he wants, so what does he make of Charlie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 15:15:00" d="2020-11-06 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The first visit is to Alston House in Cumbria, where Michael and Carole Allchorne are brimming with confidence. But things get hairy for one guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 15:50:00" d="2020-11-06 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to Scotia House in Harrogate, where host Marie suspects some of her guests are seeking revenge. Can she impress with deluxe teddy bears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 16:20:00" d="2020-11-06 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Yvonne hosts at The Canberra Guest House in Blackpool, where relationships are strained and cracks start to show. And one of the guests ruffles more than just feathers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 16:50:00" d="2020-11-06 17:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The last visit is to The Crown &amp; Kitchen in East Linton, Scotland, where tensions are close to breaking point. Yvonne and Gail leave no mattress unturned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 17:20:00" d="2020-11-06 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition and tensions run high with allegations of tit-for-tat scoring and a barrage of criticism. The payments are revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 17:55:00" d="2020-11-06 18:55:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo IV (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Critically endangered rhino Zuri gives birth to baby Ike. Otter Annie has three new pups. Camel Shan-shan is unwell. And sun bears Toni and Millie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 18:55:00" d="2020-11-06 19:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jonathan and Michael's latest idea - to keep goats - doesn't go down well with their investors. Philip and Angelina contend with broken toilets at their anniversary party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 19:55:00" d="2020-11-06 20:55:00"><n u="Grand Designs Australia">Grand Designs Australia VIII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>70% Eddie and Dot dream of a home with a magnificent 360-degree view in Strathbogie Ranges. Can they work around huge granite boulders to achieve their dream?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 20:55:00" d="2020-11-06 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>David and Greta are replacing their house, which they designed and constructed themselves, with a German-built, precision-engineered Huf</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 22:00:00" d="2020-11-06 23:05:00"><n>The Same Sky</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>75% New: The Same Sky
Brand new series: A compelling German drama from Walter Presents set in Berlin in 1974. Lauren is torn between her feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 23:05:00" d="2020-11-07 00:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Phil, who's 60, is rushed to A&amp;E in a critical condition after falling just two feet off a ladder at work. Violet, who's 93, has fallen and seriously fractured her leg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-07 00:05:00" d="2020-11-07 01:10:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Corey, who's 27, is rushed to St George's after having a cardiac arrest during a game of ice hockey. His wife of seven days, Alice, was watching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-07 01:10:00" d="2020-11-07 02:05:00"><n u="Ramsay's Hotel Hell">Ramsay's Hotel Hell III (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Gordon continues his battle to help turn around Town's Inn in Harpers Ferry, West Virginia. Can he win over the stubborn owner and give the hotel a chance of success?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-07 02:05:00" d="2020-11-07 03:10:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Phil, who's 60, is rushed to A&amp;E in a critical condition after falling just two feet off a ladder at work. Violet, who's 93, has fallen and seriously fractured her leg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-07 03:10:00" d="2020-11-07 04:15:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick VI (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
An excitable cocker spaniel needs bionic paws. A puppy with a fractured knee must sit still if he's going to get better. And a cat dragging</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-07 04:15:00" d="2020-11-07 07:15:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped XI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>76% How much prawn is in a prawn cracker? What's in low-salt food instead of salt? Plus: the new high-tech method of keeping fresh herbs alive for longer</k>  </p>
</a>
