<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-10-26 03:43:08"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 09:55:00" d="2020-11-02 10:15:00"><n>Food Unwrapped</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jelly beans don't contain gelatine, so what is the jelly in a jelly bean? Kate Quilton visits the world's largest jelly bean producer to find out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 10:15:00" d="2020-11-02 11:05:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Jo and Darrell from London are looking for a bolthole on Menorca to enjoy with their children. Can Danni Menzies find the perfect property in the south</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 11:05:00" d="2020-11-02 12:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien turn unwanted items into cash for their owners. In Kent, the boys are in stitches over some serious sewing machines</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 12:05:00" d="2020-11-02 13:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole monkeys around with a monkey bike, while Simon O'Brien uses all his skills to restore an old racing bike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 13:05:00" d="2020-11-02 14:10:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau VI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>As autumn arrives at the chateau, Dick and Angel start a new project, turning a 35-foot eight-tonne riverboat into luxury guest accommodation, with bespoke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 14:10:00" d="2020-11-02 15:15:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream V (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Lincolnshire, Juana and Trevor plan to knock down some decrepit barns and create their dream home. But is Trevor putting his health at risk by being so hands-on?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 15:15:00" d="2020-11-02 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The first visit is to The Bell House Hotel in Wiltshire, where owners Chris and Jacqui aim to bring London chic to the shires. But their absence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 15:50:00" d="2020-11-02 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to The Partridge in Oxfordshire, where Matthew Cockman and Paula Szkwarkowska share a passion for organic food. But the self-service</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 16:20:00" d="2020-11-02 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The third visit is to Strawberry Gardens B&amp;B in Heysham, where David and Susan Speak aim to make their guests feel at home with northern hospitality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 16:50:00" d="2020-11-02 17:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The last visit is to The Bateman's Mill near Chesterfield, where Jade Hendon and Diana Yates aim to be the best, but David and Susan are quick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 17:20:00" d="2020-11-02 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>It's payment day, and fur flies as Jade tackles Matthew over feedback for The Bateman's Mill. The group thrash out their differences before the winner is revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 17:55:00" d="2020-11-02 18:55:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo IV (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Male onager Holmes chases every female in sight - including the camel next door - when he's released into the female paddock in mating season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 18:55:00" d="2020-11-02 19:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Dick Strawbridge and his wife Angel help Brits who run chateau businesses in France. The couple give Johnny a crash course in the dos and don'ts of chateau shopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 19:55:00" d="2020-11-02 20:55:00"><n u="Grand Designs Australia">Grand Designs Australia VII</n><e>RF</e>    <k>A discarded 100-year-old Queenslander home is split into pieces and moved 140km on separate trucks to be reconstructed on a plot in the Gold Coast hinterland. Ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 20:55:00" d="2020-11-02 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Commercial architect Martin Pease embarks on designing and building a home for his family. But the giant 'sugar cube' is a high-concept design that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 22:00:00" d="2020-11-02 23:00:00"><n>Inside the Spitfire Factory</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Inside the Spitfire Factory
Brand new series: After two years of hard work, the Spitfire is nearly complete and the team prepare for the maiden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-02 23:00:00" d="2020-11-03 00:05:00"><n>Secrets of the Superfactories</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Secrets of the Superfactories
Brand new series: This episode reveals the inner workings of UPS's delivery service, Brompton's folding bikes, Rold's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 00:05:00" d="2020-11-03 01:10:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Reggie, who's seven, has broken his arm while doing a cartwheel to celebrate England beating Wales at Euro 2016. John, who's 84, has crashed his car into a road sign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 01:10:00" d="2020-11-03 02:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown IX (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Jon Richardson and Alex Brooker take on Johnny Vegas and Sara Pascoe. Tom Allen is in Dictionary Corner. Plus Claudia Winkleman and Rob Beckett</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 02:15:00" d="2020-11-03 03:20:00"><n>Inside the Spitfire Factory</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series: After two years of hard work, the Spitfire is nearly complete and the team prepare for the maiden flight, but will she fly? Peter gets ready for his next project. (Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 03:20:00" d="2020-11-03 04:25:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick VI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
A chinchilla requires surgery for a broken leg. But his tiny airways and bones make it a difficult procedure. And Professor Noel fights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 04:25:00" d="2020-11-03 07:25:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped X (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>76% What are those worms doing in bottles of tequila? How do you stop carp tasting of mud? And what's the difference between tangerines, mandarins, satsumas and clementines?</k>  </p>
</a>
