<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2020-10-24 04:33:14"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 09:55:00" d="2020-10-31 10:30:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped X (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>76% Kate visits Rome to find out the difference between gelato and ice cream. Are dark rum and white rum made with different ingredients? Why do mints make your mouth cold?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 10:30:00" d="2020-10-31 11:25:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>TF</e>    <k>George from Bedfordshire has visited Mallorca's Port de Pollensa over 30 times and now wants to buy a second home there. Can his best friend Diane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 11:25:00" d="2020-10-31 12:25:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Gary and Janet have sold up in the UK and are ready to take early retirement in the traditional Spanish city of Orihuela. Can Laura Hamilton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 12:25:00" d="2020-10-31 13:30:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Keen astronomer Colin and Elspeth from Edinburgh are hunting for a holiday home on Menorca. Will the stars align as Danni Menzies shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 13:30:00" d="2020-10-31 14:35:00"><n u="Location, Location, Location">Location, Location, Location XXVIII (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Phil Spencer catches up with two sets of family planners - civil partners Ally and Jo in south London, and Steve and Jo in Cardiff. Did the two couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 14:35:00" d="2020-10-31 15:40:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kevin McCloud meets Anjana and David Devoy who, having outgrown their tiny Victorian house in Clapham, plan to build a modern, minimalist home in their back garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 15:40:00" d="2020-10-31 16:10:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Surrey. The first host, 38-year-old chauffeur James, treats his guests to a taste of the tropics with his Caribbean-inspired menu. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 16:10:00" d="2020-10-31 16:45:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Surrey. Nail technician Myle serves traditional Vietnamese food, but the pressure mounts when her mum shows up in the kitchen. And Caroline and Ben unearth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 16:45:00" d="2020-10-31 17:15:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Surrey. The third host, 35-year-old hairdresser Ben, throws a Mexican fiesta, complete with mariachis and pinatas. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 17:15:00" d="2020-10-31 17:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Surrey. Music teacher Caroline hosts a bright and beautiful night full of charisma, charm, singing, dancing and nursery rhymes. (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 17:50:00" d="2020-10-31 18:20:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Surrey. Uber-competitive businessman John is banking on his home-cooked menu to bag him the prize, but will his lengthy anecdotes let him down? (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 18:20:00" d="2020-10-31 18:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>So and Kevin host the first visit at The Admiral Hotel in central London. But the sky-high prices leave their guests gobsmacked, and a discussion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 18:55:00" d="2020-10-31 19:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Ursula and Daria welcome their rivals to The Redstone in Blackpool. But the mood turns sour during an afternoon of cake-decorating, and one of the guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 19:25:00" d="2020-10-31 19:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Chris and his friend Christel host at Ann's Farmhouse in Thornton in West Yorkshire. But their guests find the decor dated, and bubbling tensions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 19:55:00" d="2020-10-31 20:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kris and Vikki host the final visit at The R Inn in Desborough in Northamptonshire, where relationships within the group break down and one guest refuses to stay the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 20:25:00" d="2020-10-31 21:00:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition. After airing their grievances, from marks on a toilet seat to one guest refusing to stay the night, the payments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 21:00:00" d="2020-10-31 22:00:00"><n>Emergency Rescue: Air, Land &amp; Sea</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series: Humberside Search and Rescue help a woman who's fallen while out walking her dog, and in Newquay, teams search for an aircraft reported</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 22:00:00" d="2020-10-31 23:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mel, who's 71, is rushed to St George's after being accidentally knocked down and run over by her husband John. Maddi, who's four, has fallen and injured</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 23:00:00" d="2020-11-01 00:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mark, who's 52, fights for his life after being thrown from his motorbike in a crash. Kayley, who's 25, has fallen from her horse and doctors worry she's dislocated her hip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 00:05:00" d="2020-11-01 00:40:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>85% The Plague: Father Dougal is excited about his pet rabbit, Sampras, while Bishop Brennan is due to arrive to investigate a case of suspected</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 00:40:00" d="2020-11-01 01:15:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>85% Rock-a-Hula Ted: A feminist protest singer arrives on the island just as Ted is about to judge the Lovely Girls competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 01:15:00" d="2020-11-01 02:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown IX</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts. Sean Lock and Bob Mortimer take on Jon Richardson and Holly Walsh. Isy Suttie joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner. Claudia Winkleman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 02:15:00" d="2020-11-01 03:20:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mel, who's 71, is rushed to St George's after being accidentally knocked down and run over by her husband John. Maddi, who's four, has fallen and injured</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 03:20:00" d="2020-11-01 04:25:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Supervet
A young family rush to the clinic with their chihuahua, who has a crushed pelvis after being hit by a car. And much-loved spaniel Banjo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-01 04:25:00" d="2020-11-01 09:55:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>85% The Plague: Father Dougal is excited about his pet rabbit, Sampras, while Bishop Brennan is due to arrive to investigate a case of suspected</k>  </p>
</a>
