<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-10-28 03:47:58"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 09:55:00" d="2020-11-04 10:15:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and cider maker Andy Thompstone show us how to make a winter version of one of our favourite drinks. Plus: a limoncello recipe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 10:15:00" d="2020-11-04 11:05:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Julie and Jerry have been married for 33 years and, with Jerry about to retire, the time is right to buy a holiday home in Brittany in France. Can Jasmine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 11:05:00" d="2020-11-04 12:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien turn unwanted possessions into cash. Simon takes Henry to a stately home in Somerset, where he thinks he's unearthed a bona fide Tudor relic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 12:05:00" d="2020-11-04 13:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien look for items to fix up and flog. In this episode, items include a pair of battlefield telephones and some Gothic church windows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 13:05:00" d="2020-11-04 14:10:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jonathan and Michael try to convince an American couple to book their wedding with them. Phil and Angelina clear their garden. Johnny and Ashley search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 14:10:00" d="2020-11-04 15:15:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VI (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Charlie Luxton heads to Hertfordshire to help Roz and Mick Abrahams downsize and build a new compact, contemporary home on a plot at the bottom of their garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 15:15:00" d="2020-11-04 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition kicks off at the Park Hotel in Gloucestershire, where Lauren Abraham and Callum Hogg make their bid for the prize, but some robust feedback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 15:50:00" d="2020-11-04 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Sisters Sue and Wendy offer a home from home at Sue's B&amp;B in Trowbridge. But the communal breakfast brings some awkward moments, and Sue is under pressure in the kitchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 16:20:00" d="2020-11-04 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The third visit is to The Talbot in Dorset, where Erika Watt and Ellie Gill's rooms don't live up to first impressions. And some of the feedback sends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 16:50:00" d="2020-11-04 17:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Hotel manager Cameron Thomas likes to keep things strictly professional at The Old Rectory in south Wales. And guests Lauren and Callum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 17:20:00" d="2020-11-04 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day and the B&amp;Bers meet for the last time to settle some scores. Tensions are in the air and issues are debated before the winner is revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 17:55:00" d="2020-11-04 18:55:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo IV (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Three-legged chameleon Tripod goes speed-dating. And sloth Tina has been giving her partner Rico a hard time, but the keepers have a plan to bring them closer together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 18:55:00" d="2020-11-04 19:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Dick helps Philip and Angelina build a bridge, Jonathan and Michael test their chateau's services, and Johnny and Ashley continue the search for their dream chateau</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 19:55:00" d="2020-11-04 20:55:00"><n u="Grand Designs Australia">Grand Designs Australia VII</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Retired chef Phillip links together a quirky cluster of disconnected, historic structures in Stanley, Tasmania, into a contemporary, cohesive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 20:55:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Pru and Richard Irvine plan to build a bespoke family home in the Midlothian countryside. But their plot of land is an old industrial site with lime kilns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 23:00:00"><n>The Kennedys: Tragedy &amp; Triumph</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: The Kennedys: Tragedy &amp;. 
. riumph: Brand new series - Family Secrets: The President and his brother Bobby must work together to avoid nuclear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 23:00:00" d="2020-11-05 00:20:00"><n>Catching a Killer</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catching a Killer: A Bullet. 
. hrough the Window: A 19-year-old is shot through a window in a quiet street. This programme follows the police</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 00:20:00" d="2020-11-05 01:30:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Nicky's been hit by a car. Doctors rush her for a CT scan. Her husband Richard tries to reassure everyone as her daughter Annie tries to come to terms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 01:30:00" d="2020-11-05 02:30:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown IX (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Sean Lock and Katherine Ryan take on Jon Richardson and David Mitchell. Nick Helm is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent. Plus Rachel Riley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 02:30:00" d="2020-11-05 03:35:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick VI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
Tina and her sons bring in their springer spaniel puppy, whose badly deformed hind leg requires complicated surgery. A cocker spaniel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 03:35:00" d="2020-11-05 06:35:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Nicky's been hit by a car. Doctors rush her for a CT scan. Her husband Richard tries to reassure everyone as her daughter Annie tries to come to terms</k>  </p>
</a>
