<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-10-29 03:49:26"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 09:55:00" d="2020-11-05 10:15:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Will Kirstie Allsopp's caramelised onion sausage impress the judges at the Nidderdale Show?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 10:15:00" d="2020-11-05 11:05:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n>    <k>Martine, who's originally from France, and her son Remi are searching for a holiday home on the Charente coast on the island of Oléron. Can Ben Hillman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 11:05:00" d="2020-11-05 12:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>In Wales, Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien restore a dentist's table and a barber's chair, and make a coffee table out of parquet flooring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 12:05:00" d="2020-11-05 13:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In the Cotswolds, Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien compete to see who can create the most profit on two old lamps, and take a spin in a Devonshire fire engine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 13:05:00" d="2020-11-05 14:10:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Dick helps Philip and Angelina build a bridge, Jonathan and Michael test their chateau's services, and Johnny and Ashley continue the search for their dream chateau</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 14:10:00" d="2020-11-05 15:15:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Charlie Luxton's in West Sussex, where Cathryn and Adam Raybould plan to build their dream period-style home on Cathryn's family farm. But the project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 15:15:00" d="2020-11-05 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Fay and Ray host at the Shiralee B&amp;B in Salisbury, with its striking Tunisian-inspired design. But their cluttered decor and CCTV provoke comment from their guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 15:50:00" d="2020-11-05 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to The Bluebell Woods in Northampton, where David and Donna try to bring a touch of class to their woodland B&amp;B. But the feedback has the hosts fuming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 16:20:00" d="2020-11-05 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The third visit is to The Lion Hotel in Pontypool, where manager Marc Harris and chef Wayne Williams aim to deliver a high-end service. But over dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 16:50:00" d="2020-11-05 17:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The last visit is to The New Inn in Talgarth, where ex-naval officer Damon Lewis is the captain of his ship. Fay and Ray have high expectations, but Damon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 17:20:00" d="2020-11-05 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's payment day and the B&amp;Bers meet for the last time. Tensions come to a head, as the group air their grievances and find out how much they've been paid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 17:55:00" d="2020-11-05 18:55:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Golden poison frog Pablo has lost interest in his partner Maria, so bad boy El Loco is brought in to shake things up. Baby porcupine Marion faces the meerkat mob. Plus: chimps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 18:55:00" d="2020-11-05 19:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Dick joins the search for a stash of wine said to have been hidden during World War II in Jonathan and Michael's caves. Fiona starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 19:55:00" d="2020-11-05 20:55:00"><n u="Grand Designs Australia">Grand Designs Australia VII (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>70% IT engineer Damien Lederer from Canberra uses green building materials and commercial elements to create a zero-carbon family home with sophisticated high-tech features</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 20:55:00" d="2020-11-05 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tiffany and Jonny are building a striking modernist home in Bath: a German prefabricated kit house with great green credentials that should</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 22:00:00" d="2020-11-05 23:00:00"><n>Billion Pound Cruise</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Billion Pound Cruise
Brand new series: The Symphony of the Seas cruise ship is out at sea, but how do the 6680 guests occupy themselves aboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-05 23:00:00" d="2020-11-06 00:05:00"><n>Britain's Most Expensive Home</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Britain's Most Expensive Home:. 
. uilding for a Billionaire: Documentary following billionaire John Caudwell as his ?65 million property refurbishment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 00:05:00" d="2020-11-06 01:10:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>George, who's 70, has impaled his eye on a piece of driftwood. Debby, who's 59, has cut her hand on her lawnmower. And eight-year-old Phoebe has scissors stuck in her thigh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 01:10:00" d="2020-11-06 02:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown X (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Sean Lock and Henning Wehn go up against Jon Richardson and Victoria Coren Mitchell. Tom Allen joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 02:15:00" d="2020-11-06 03:15:00"><n>Billion Pound Cruise</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series: The Symphony of the Seas cruise ship is out at sea, but how do the 6680 guests occupy themselves aboard this billion-pound vessel that's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 03:15:00" d="2020-11-06 04:20:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick VI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
A Staffordshire bull terrier, who senses owner Karen's nocturnal epileptic seizures, needs treatment for its painful legs. And an Irish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-06 04:20:00" d="2020-11-06 07:20:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped XI (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>76% Bergamot gives Jimmy's Earl Grey tea flavour, but what exactly is it? How does instant tea do against tea bags? Plus: Kate visits a jelly bean factory</k>  </p>
</a>
