<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-10-27 04:06:00"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 09:55:00" d="2020-11-03 10:15:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp wants to surprise some guests with two delicious mains: roast beef with mulled wine gravy and a vegetarian option of masala cauliflower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 10:15:00" d="2020-11-03 11:05:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Sisters Kay and Faye enjoyed many happy childhood holidays in Cannes and now want to buy a holiday home to make new memories, on a budget of ?400,000</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 11:05:00" d="2020-11-03 12:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Simon O'Brien leads Henry Cole to a barn that features an amazing collection of replica Rolls-Royce cars, while Henry tries his hand at driving a tractor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 12:05:00" d="2020-11-03 13:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In York, Henry Cole struggles to squeeze into some motorcycle leathers, and Simon O'Brien gets into deep water when he tries to restore an aluminium boat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 13:05:00" d="2020-11-03 14:10:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Dick Strawbridge and his wife Angel help Brits who run chateau businesses in France. The couple give Johnny a crash course in the dos and don'ts of chateau shopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 14:10:00" d="2020-11-03 15:15:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VI (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Charlie Luxton meets Sam and Eryka, who plan to build a contemporary warehouse-style home in an industrial unit in south east London. But getting planning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 15:15:00" d="2020-11-03 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition kicks off at Keats Cottage in Shanklin on the Isle of Wight, where David and Ewa Woodward play host to some critical guests who don't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 15:50:00" d="2020-11-03 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Donna Taylor takes a no-frills approach to hosting at Jasmine House in Lutterworth in Leicestershire. But guests Martin and Sara discover that the added</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 16:20:00" d="2020-11-03 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Martin Hulme and Sara Williams host at the luxury Halliwell House in Cheshire, where rooms have a hefty price tag of nearly ?500 a night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 16:50:00" d="2020-11-03 17:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The final visit is to Soar Chapel Guest House in Wales, the family home of mum-and-daughter duo Lesley and Chloe Priestly. A beatboxing competition brings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 17:20:00" d="2020-11-03 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;Bers meet for the last time to find out how much they've been paid and to settle some scores, before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 17:55:00" d="2020-11-03 18:55:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo IV (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Chester's male lemurs' peaceful life is changed by a female arrival. Can Permata, a young Javan green magpie, impress female Metina and help boost their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 18:55:00" d="2020-11-03 19:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jonathan and Michael try to convince an American couple to book their wedding with them. Phil and Angelina clear their garden. Johnny and Ashley search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 19:55:00" d="2020-11-03 20:55:00"><n u="Grand Designs Australia">Grand Designs Australia VII</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike plans to build a spotted gum-clad home on French Island, Victoria, featuring exposed timber trusses and dry stacked stone walls, transporting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 20:55:00" d="2020-11-03 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Inspired by their love of Gothic architecture and horror movies, Jo and Shaun Bennett decide to build an Addams Family-style house, but their pricey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 22:00:00" d="2020-11-03 23:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XXII</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Kin, who has motor neurone disease, is rushed to St George's with severe sepsis. Steve has severed three fingers with an electric saw. And teenager Jordan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-03 23:00:00" d="2020-11-04 00:05:00"><n u="Shut Ins: Britain's Fattest People">Shut Ins: Britain's Fattest People II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Shut-Ins: Britain's Fattest People
Series that follows people who are affected by obesity. Emily, a 24-year-old single mum, has struggled with her weight all her life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 00:05:00" d="2020-11-04 01:05:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown IX (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Sean Lock and Kevin Bridges take on Jon Richardson and Rebecca Front. Joe Lycett is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 01:05:00" d="2020-11-04 02:05:00"><n u="Ramsay's Hotel Hell">Ramsay's Hotel Hell III (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Gordon's at Harpers Ferry in West Virginia, for the first half of a two-part visit to the Town's Inn, a historic hotel that's so full of clutter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 02:05:00" d="2020-11-04 03:10:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XXII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kin, who has motor neurone disease, is rushed to St George's with severe sepsis. Steve has severed three fingers with an electric saw. And teenager Jordan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 03:10:00" d="2020-11-04 04:15:00"><n>China: Treasures of the Jade...</n><e>RF</e>    <k>. mpire: Secret History reveals the Han dynasty's extraordinary treasures as archaeologists use cutting-edge technology to discover for the first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-11-04 04:15:00" d="2020-11-04 07:15:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped XI (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>76% Jimmy, Kate and Matt uncover more food secrets. Could squid and chips replace fish and chips as our national dish? Where do multivitamins come from? Why is clotted cream yellow?</k>  </p>
</a>
