<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-10-23 04:35:36"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 09:55:00" d="2020-10-30 10:15:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp is in sweet tooth heaven as she learns how to make candy in Manhattan and, back in the UK, creates perfect passion fruit marshmallows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 10:15:00" d="2020-10-30 11:05:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Karen and Julian, who run a B&amp;B in Cornwall, have never been to the Greek island of Naxos, but have decided it's the perfect place to buy a holiday home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 11:05:00" d="2020-10-30 12:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien visit the Cotswolds and Somerset, where their finds include a set of milk churns and an old munitions shell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 12:05:00" d="2020-10-30 13:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien turn unwanted items into cash for their owners. In Yorkshire, they scour Wensleydale for profitable finds and celebrate Henry's birthday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 13:05:00" d="2020-10-30 14:10:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau VI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the beginning of autumn, and Dick and Angel convert the old tack room into a grand entrance, with Angel knocking down walls and Dick laying a new floor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 14:10:00" d="2020-10-30 15:15:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream V (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In south Wales, Jodie and Rhodri Howells must decide whether to renovate the 1950s bungalow on their countryside plot or knock it down. Charlie Luxton's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 15:15:00" d="2020-10-30 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition starts at The Oak Tree Cottage in Burley, where Jacqui Castle hopes her homely approach will win the day. But her communal breakfast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 15:50:00" d="2020-10-30 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to The Rising Sun Inn in Bath, where owners Lorraine Hawkins and Norman Butcher impose a dress code for dinner. Some of the guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 16:20:00" d="2020-10-30 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The third visit is to The Busfeild Arms in East Morton, where hosts Martin and Catherine Crosswaite pride themselves on Yorkshire hospitality, but Martin's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 16:50:00" d="2020-10-30 17:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The final visit is to Epstein House in Liverpool, where there's a competitive Beatles-themed game of charades and some shocking revelations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 17:20:00" d="2020-10-30 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the last day and Patrick has some questions for Jacqui and Jane, while Martin and Catherine have some explaining to do, before the payments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 17:55:00" d="2020-10-30 18:55:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo IV (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Andean bear cub Madidi goes on an adventure into a neighbouring paddock. Young elephant Nandita is desperate to befriend babies Aayu and Indali</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 18:55:00" d="2020-10-30 19:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau VI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>As autumn arrives at the chateau, Dick and Angel start a new project, turning a 35-foot eight-tonne riverboat into luxury guest accommodation, with bespoke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 19:55:00" d="2020-10-30 20:55:00"><n u="Grand Designs Australia">Grand Designs Australia VII</n><e>RF</e>    <k>City couple Ronnen and Trace move to a 20-acre plot near Daylesford in Victoria, creating a rural oasis in a 100m-long, steel-framed shed that blends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 20:55:00" d="2020-10-30 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kevin McCloud meets a couple building an ultra-modern, low-maintenance home in the back garden of their elegant Regency house in Cheltenham, despite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 22:00:00" d="2020-10-30 23:05:00"><n>The Same Sky</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>75% New: The Same Sky
Brand new series: Compelling German drama from Walter Presents set in Berlin in 1974. Lars proves to be a natural as Lauren becomes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-30 23:05:00" d="2020-10-31 00:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XI (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tulsi, 12, is airlifted to St George's after falling from a cliff near Hastings. Bus driver Adam, 39, faces lengthy emergency surgery after his motorbike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 00:05:00" d="2020-10-31 01:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Cyclist Athar, who's 22, has collided with a car. Doctors assess whether he has sustained a serious head injury and life-changing damage to his neck, spine or internal organs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 01:05:00" d="2020-10-31 02:05:00"><n u="Ramsay's Hotel Hell">Ramsay's Hotel Hell III (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Angler's Lodge in Idaho, a stunning venue whose owners have been struck by family tragedy. Can he rescue the broken family's business?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 02:05:00" d="2020-10-31 03:10:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XI (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tulsi, 12, is airlifted to St George's after falling from a cliff near Hastings. Bus driver Adam, 39, faces lengthy emergency surgery after his motorbike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 03:10:00" d="2020-10-31 04:15:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick VI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>86% The Supervet
Professor Noel Fitzpatrick helps Hetty the Labrador, a guide and seizure dog who's become lame. There's also a Rhodesian ridgeback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-10-31 04:15:00" d="2020-10-31 07:15:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped X (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>76% Kate visits Rome to find out the difference between gelato and ice cream. Are dark rum and white rum made with different ingredients? Why do mints make your mouth cold?</k>  </p>
</a>
