<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-10-25 03:42:52"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-01 12:00:00" d="2020-11-01 14:00:00"><n>Rise of the Guardians</n><e>R</e>    <k>Animated adventure with Alec Baldwin and Hugh Jackman. When evil spirit Pitch taints the dreams of Earth's children, the Guardians, including Santa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-01 14:00:00" d="2020-11-01 15:35:00"><n>FernGully: The Last Rainforest</n><e>R</e>    <k>Family animation. An adventurous fairy and a miniaturised man try to save the rainforest where she lives from a deforestation project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-01 15:35:00" d="2020-11-01 17:35:00"><n>A Dog's Purpose</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lasse Hallström's comedy drama about the adventures of a dog who gets reincarnated as different breeds and has many different owners over the decades</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-01 17:35:00" d="2020-11-01 19:45:00"><n>Congo</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action-adventure with Laura Linney. An expedition deep into central Africa encounters dangers that include a troop of intelligent killer apes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-01 19:45:00" d="2020-11-01 22:00:00"><n u="Pitch Perfect">Pitch Perfect 2</n><e>R</e>    <k>Cheeky comedy sequel starring Anna Kendrick, Rebel Wilson and Hailee Steinfeld. Can the Barden Bellas redeem themselves after a very embarrassing incident?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-01 22:00:00" d="2020-11-01 23:45:00"><n>A Quiet Place</n><e>R</e>    <k>John Krasinski and Emily Blunt star in the tense horror about a family trying to survive in a world overrun by aliens who can't see but</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-01 23:45:00" d="2020-11-02 02:10:00"><n>Blue Velvet</n><e>R</e>    <k>David Lynch's adult thriller starring Kyle MacLachlan. The discovery of a severed ear leads a man into an underworld of sex and violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-02 02:10:00" d="2020-11-02 09:00:00"><n>The Love Witch</n><e>R</e>    <k>Stylised thriller with Samantha Robinson. In 1960s California, a woman uses occult potions and spells in her troubled quest for love. Nudity/sex/violence/gory images</k>  </p>
</a>
