<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-10-26 03:41:49"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-02 09:00:00" d="2020-11-02 12:00:00"><n>BSL Zone: Zoom Double Destination</n><e>R</e>    <k>Written and directed by Rinkoo Barpaga, this personal documentary examines whether racism exists in the deaf community, told from Rinkoo's perspective</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-02 12:00:00" d="2020-11-02 13:45:00"><n>Hondo</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western starring John Wayne and Geraldine Page. A US cavalryman takes a rancher who's been abandoned by her husband under his wing, protecting her from an Apache chief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-02 13:45:00" d="2020-11-02 15:30:00"><n>Man in the Saddle</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western. Randolph Scott stars as a rancher who's the target of unwelcome harassment by his richer and more powerful neighbour. With Alexander Knox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-02 15:30:00" d="2020-11-02 17:55:00"><n>The Man Who Knew Too Much</n><e>R</e>    <k>Hitchcock thriller starring James Stewart and Doris Day as a couple whose son is kidnapped in order to stop the father from revealing some incendiary information</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-02 17:55:00" d="2020-11-02 20:05:00"><n>Track of the Cat</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western with Robert Mitchum. In 1880s northern California, an isolated, dysfunctional family's lives change forever when a mountain lion starts prowling around their ranch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-02 20:05:00" d="2020-11-02 22:00:00"><n>Daddy's Home</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy starring Mark Wahlberg, Will Ferrell and Linda Cardellini. A man is living happily with his wife and stepchildren, until the kids' biological</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-02 22:00:00" d="2020-11-03 00:05:00"><n>Jack Ryan: Shadow Recruit</n><e>R</e>    <k>Thriller starring Chris Pine, Keira Knightley, Kevin Costner and Kenneth Branagh. A CIA agent is sent on a dangerous mission to Moscow to investigate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-03 00:05:00" d="2020-11-03 02:40:00"><n>Pain &amp; Gain</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action-comedy with Mark Wahlberg, Dwayne Johnson and Anthony Mackie. Three bodybuilders become killers. Brutal violence/very strong language and sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-03 02:40:00" d="2020-11-03 05:40:00"><n>Brother</n><e>R</e>    <k>Takeshi 'Beat' Kitano directs and stars as a Japanese gangster exiled to Los Angeles, where he builds a drugs empire that attracts Mafia interest</k>  </p>
</a>
