<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-10-27 04:02:44"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-03 12:00:00" d="2020-11-03 13:55:00"><n>Winchester '73</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western. James Stewart stars as sharpshooter Lin McAdam, who wins a Winchester rifle. But a murderous rival steals his prize, so McAdam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-03 13:55:00" d="2020-11-03 15:45:00"><n>The Sound of Fury</n><e>R</e>    <k>Film noir starring Frank Lovejoy and Lloyd Bridges. When two down-and-outs murderously bungle a kidnap plot and end up in prison, a newspaper dangerously</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-03 15:45:00" d="2020-11-03 17:30:00"><n>The Last Blitzkrieg</n><e>R</e>    <k>Van Johnson, Kerwin Mathews and Dick York star in Arthur Dreifuss's World War II drama about a group of Nazis who disguise themselves as GIs to infiltrate the Allied ranks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-03 17:30:00" d="2020-11-03 20:05:00"><n>The Odessa File</n><e>R</e>    <k>Post-war thriller starring Jon Voight and Maximillian Schell. A journalist uncovers a dark conspiracy while searching for a former SS Captain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-03 20:05:00" d="2020-11-03 22:00:00"><n>Crocodile Dundee</n><e>R</e>    <k>Oscar-nominated comedy. Paul Hogan plays Crocodile Dundee, the fearless Australian outback hero who takes on the wilds of New York with his US journalist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-03 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 00:50:00"><n>X-Men: Apocalypse</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action fantasy sequel. Can Charles Xavier and his young mutants prevent god-like Apocalypse and his allies from destroying the world? With James McAvoy and Oscar Isaac. Violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-04 00:50:00" d="2020-11-04 02:55:00"><n>Brotherhood</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama with Noel Clarke. Ten years after the events of Adulthood, Sam is married and trying to build an honest life. But his past haunts him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-04 02:55:00" d="2020-11-04 05:55:00"><n>Ouija</n><e>R</e>    <k>Violent supernatural horror. Olivia Cooke, Ana Coto and Daren Kagasoff star as friends who unwisely attempt to contact the spirit of a friend who killed herself</k>  </p>
</a>
