<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-10-28 03:45:56"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-04 12:00:00" d="2020-11-04 14:05:00"><n>The Fighting Kentuckian</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western with John Wayne and Oliver Hardy. In Alabama in 1818, two ex-Kentucky militiamen side with exiled French settlers against a land-grabber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-04 14:05:00" d="2020-11-04 16:10:00"><n>Anastasia</n><e>R</e>    <k>Historical drama. The Oscar-winning Ingrid Bergman stars as an amnesiac refugee who Yul Brynner tries to pass off as the daughter of the murdered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-04 16:10:00" d="2020-11-04 17:45:00"><n>Decision at Sundown</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western starring Randolph Scott and John Carroll. A man seeking revenge on the person who took his wife, who later killed herself, tracks his quarry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-04 17:45:00" d="2020-11-04 19:50:00"><n>Funeral in Berlin</n><e>R</e>    <k>Cold War thriller starring Michael Caine as the British spy Harry Palmer, who is sent to help a Communist defector cross over from East Berlin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-04 19:50:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00"><n>The Huntsman: Winter's War</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dark fairy-tale action-adventure starring Chris Hemsworth, Jessica Chastain, Charlize Theron and Emily Blunt. A story of evil queens and ill-fated lovers. Violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 23:45:00"><n>The Take</n><e>R</e>    <k>Violent thriller with Idris Elba, Richard Madden and Charlotte Le Bon. A pickpocket, an anti-fascist and a CIA agent uncover a conspiracy in Paris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-04 23:45:00" d="2020-11-05 02:00:00"><n>World War Z</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action horror starring Brad Pitt. A retired UN investigator joins an armed research group travelling the globe in search of a cure for a virulent zombie plague. Gory violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-05 02:00:00" d="2020-11-05 05:00:00"><n u="Child">Child 44</n><e>R</e>    <k>Thriller with Tom Hardy and Noomi Rapace. In 1950s Russia, a demoted security services agent realises that a serial killer is targeting young boys</k>  </p>
</a>
