<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-10-29 03:47:23"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-05 12:00:00" d="2020-11-05 13:45:00"><n>Rawhide</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western thriller starring Tyrone Power and Susan Hayward. Ruthless outlaws target a remote overland mail staging post as the perfect place to ambush a shipment of gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-05 13:45:00" d="2020-11-05 15:50:00"><n>Millions Like Us</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama about the fortunes of a British family who are split up during the Second World War. Starring Eric Portman, Patricia Roc and Gordon Jackson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-05 15:50:00" d="2020-11-05 17:40:00"><n>The Savage</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western with Charlton Heston. A White boy is raised by the Sioux after his family is massacred by Crow warriors. But his loyalties are torn between Sioux</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-05 17:40:00" d="2020-11-05 19:50:00"><n>Alvarez Kelly</n><e>R</e>    <k>Civil war era western. William Holden is Alvarez Kelly, the man who stole a herd of cattle and panicked an army. Richard Widmark is the colonel trying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-05 19:50:00" d="2020-11-05 22:00:00"><n>Congo</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action-adventure with Laura Linney. An expedition deep into central Africa encounters dangers that include a troop of intelligent killer apes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-05 22:00:00" d="2020-11-05 23:50:00"><n u="Commando">Commando (1985)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Commando
(1985) Violent thriller starring Arnold Schwarzenegger. To free his kidnapped daughter, a US ex-commando must agree to assassinate a South</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-05 23:50:00" d="2020-11-06 02:30:00"><n>Bone Tomahawk</n><e>R</e>    <k>Wild West horror starring Kurt Russell, Lili Simmons, Patrick Wilson, Richard Jenkins and Matthew Fox. A posse tries to rescue townsfolk abducted by cannibals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-06 02:30:00" d="2020-11-06 05:30:00"><n>The Quiet Ones</n><e>R</e>    <k>Supernatural horror with Jared Harris, Sam Claflin and Olivia Cooke. A university professor and his team perform disturbing experiments on a seemingly possessed woman. Violence</k>  </p>
</a>
