<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-10-24 04:33:14"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-10-31 12:00:00" d="2020-10-31 13:50:00"><n>Carry On Cabby</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy starring Hattie Jacques and Sid James. A piqued wife sets up a female-staffed taxi firm to rival her husband's after he forgets their wedding anniversary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-10-31 13:50:00" d="2020-10-31 15:40:00"><n>Paddington</n><e>R</e>    <k>Part-animated family fun. Hugh Bonneville, Sally Hawkins and Nicole Kidman star in this adaptation of Michael Bond's tales of the adventures of a small</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-10-31 15:40:00" d="2020-10-31 17:35:00"><n>How to Train Your Dragon</n><e>R</e>    <k>Oscar-nominated animation. The young Viking Hiccup and his friend Astrid inhabit a village that lives in fear of fire-breathing dragons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-10-31 17:35:00" d="2020-10-31 19:45:00"><n>Romancing the Stone</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy action adventure starring Michael Douglas and Kathleen Turner. An adventurer helps a bestselling author to search for her sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-10-31 19:45:00" d="2020-10-31 22:00:00"><n u="Super">Super 8</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sci-fi thriller with Joel Courtney, Elle Fanning and Riley Griffiths. Children witness a train crash that heralds strange events and a dangerous presence in their town. Violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-10-31 22:00:00" d="2020-10-31 23:45:00"><n>Breaking In</n>    <k>Violent action thriller. After her father is murdered, a woman takes her kids to his home - a fortress packed to the gills with state-of-the-art security</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-10-31 23:45:00" d="2020-11-01 01:30:00"><n>Halloween</n>    <k>Jamie Lee Curtis stars in John Carpenter's seminal horror in which a masked maniac starts slaughtering babysitting teenagers in smalltown America. Gory violence/nudity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-01 01:30:00" d="2020-11-01 03:20:00"><n>They Live</n><e>R</e>    <k>A guy, Nada, finds a pair of shades that reveal the truth of things, like extra-terrestrials with skull heads on Earth, in John Carpenter's sci-fi horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-01 03:20:00" d="2020-11-01 12:00:00"><n>Pi</n><e>R</e>    <k>Disturbing thriller. A mathematical genius (Sean Gullette) believes he can unlock the key to both the stock market and the universe. But the idea attracts</k>  </p>
</a>
