<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-10-30 03:39:06"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-06 12:00:00" d="2020-11-06 14:10:00"><n>Track of the Cat</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western with Robert Mitchum. In 1880s northern California, an isolated, dysfunctional family's lives change forever when a mountain lion starts prowling around their ranch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-06 14:10:00" d="2020-11-06 16:10:00"><n>Flying Tigers</n><e>R</e>    <k>World War II drama starring John Wayne - in his first ever war film - as one of the US pilots who helped to defend China from invading Japanese troops</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-06 16:10:00" d="2020-11-06 17:45:00"><n>Three Faces West</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western starring Charles Coburn, Sigrid Gurie and John Wayne. An Austrian doctor and his daughter flee the Nazis to America, before a natural disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-06 17:45:00" d="2020-11-06 19:45:00"><n>Sink the Bismarck!</n><e>R</e>    <k>Second World War drama. Kenneth More stars as the British captain charged with finding and destroying the Bismarck, Germany's largest battleship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-06 19:45:00" d="2020-11-06 22:00:00"><n u="Pitch Perfect">Pitch Perfect 2</n><e>R</e>    <k>Cheeky comedy sequel starring Anna Kendrick, Rebel Wilson and Hailee Steinfeld. Can the Barden Bellas redeem themselves after a very embarrassing incident?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-06 22:00:00" d="2020-11-07 00:10:00"><n>Red Heat</n>    <k>Action comedy. Arnold Schwarzenegger stars as an iron-jawed, iron-willed cop from behind the Iron Curtain, partnered with an American who he considers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-07 00:10:00" d="2020-11-07 01:55:00"><n>Attack the Block</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sci-fi horror-comedy with Jodie Whittaker and John Boyega. Aliens unwisely pick a tough London housing estate as the 'beachhead' for their invasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-11-07 01:55:00" d="2020-11-07 04:55:00"><n>Pain &amp; Gain</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action-comedy with Mark Wahlberg, Dwayne Johnson and Anthony Mackie. Three bodybuilders become killers. Brutal violence/very strong language and sexual</k>  </p>
</a>
