<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-10-24 04:33:14"><p id_tv="1042" o="2020-10-31 05:15:00" d="2020-10-31 06:30:00" c="1"><n>Batman: Year One</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% After years away Bruce Wayne returns to Gotham and becomes the masked vigilante known as the Batman. Animated adventure with the voices of Ben McKenzie and Bryan Cranston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-10-31 06:30:00" d="2020-10-31 07:00:00"><n>Sky Cinema Preview</n>    <k>Check out all the great movies coming soon to Sky Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-10-31 07:00:00" d="2020-10-31 09:15:00" c="1"><n>Captain Marvel</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Oscar winner Brie Larson is Captain Marvel, one of the great heroes of the universe, caught up in an intergalactic struggle between alien worlds. With Samuel L Jackson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-10-31 09:15:00" d="2020-10-31 11:25:00" c="1"><n u="Lethal Weapon">Lethal Weapon III</n><t>F</t>    <k>Tough cops Riggs and Murtaugh (Mel Gibson and Danny Glover) return for another all-action adventure in which they must confront a former cop turned crime lord</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-10-31 11:25:00" d="2020-10-31 13:20:00" c="1"><n>Big Trouble In Little China</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Kurt Russell is the trucker hauled into a battle between good and evil in a world beneath Chinatown. Kung fu adventure from John Carpenter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-10-31 13:20:00" d="2020-10-31 15:40:00" c="1"><n>Jack Reacher</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Tom Cruise plays an elusive and brutal investigator who uses strong-arm tactics to catch a killer. Action with Rosamund Pike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-10-31 15:40:00" d="2020-10-31 17:45:00" c="1"><n>Gemini Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Will Smith stars as an aging assassin who becomes targeted by a mysterious enemy that seems able to anticipate his every move. Ang Lee directs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-10-31 17:45:00" d="2020-10-31 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Glass</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% David Dunn hunts a dangerous superhuman with 24 personalities in the final instalment of the Unbreakable trilogy. With Samuel L Jackson, Bruce Willis and James McAvoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-10-31 20:00:00" d="2020-10-31 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Men In Black: International</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% The Men in Black are back to take down a new global threat - a mole within their own organisation. Starring Chris Hemsworth and Tessa Thompson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-10-31 22:00:00" d="2020-11-01 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Jack Reacher</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Tom Cruise plays an elusive and brutal investigator who uses strong-arm tactics to catch a killer. Action with Rosamund Pike</k>  </p>
</a>
