<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-10-23 04:46:52"><p id_tv="1044" o="2020-10-30 05:30:00" d="2020-10-30 07:15:00" c="1"><n>Point Last Seen</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% As tracker Linda Hamilton searches the desert for a missing girl, she's haunted by the disappearance of her own children, snatched by their violent dad. Drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-10-30 07:15:00" d="2020-10-30 08:55:00" c="1"><n>The Bouncer</n><t>F</t>    <k>An imprisoned bodyguard is forced to work with the police and infiltrate a dangerous gang in order to secure his release. Jean-Claude Van Damme stars. English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-10-30 08:55:00" d="2020-10-30 11:10:00" c="1"><n>The Sum Of All Fears</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% CIA agent Ben Affleck races to avert nuclear war after a terrorist gets his hands on a missing bomb</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-10-30 11:10:00" d="2020-10-30 12:55:00" c="1"><n>We Die Young</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% When a 10-year-old and his brother flee the cruelty of gang life, a veteran with PTSD takes them under his wing. Jean-Claude Van Damme stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-10-30 12:55:00" d="2020-10-30 15:10:00" c="1"><n>Argo</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Ben Affleck's CIA agent is charged with bringing home six Americans stranded in revolutionary Iran. Oscar-winning thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-10-30 15:10:00" d="2020-10-30 16:40:00" c="1"><n>Kill Ben Lyk</n><t>F</t>    <k>When three people named Ben Lyk are murdered in London over 24 hours, police locate and hide the remaining Ben Lyks until they can figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-10-30 16:40:00" d="2020-10-30 18:55:00" c="1"><n>The Sum Of All Fears</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% CIA agent Ben Affleck races to avert nuclear war after a terrorist gets his hands on a missing bomb</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-10-30 18:55:00" d="2020-10-30 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Argo</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Ben Affleck's CIA agent is charged with bringing home six Americans stranded in revolutionary Iran. Oscar-winning thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-10-30 21:00:00" d="2020-10-30 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Ocean's Eleven</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% A criminal dream team tries to pull off the greatest robbery in Las Vegas history. Caper with George Clooney, Brad Pitt and Matt Damon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-10-30 23:00:00" d="2020-10-31 02:00:00" c="1"><n>Ocean's Twelve</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% George Clooney reassembles his team of conmen and heads to Europe to pull off a series of daring heists. Julia Roberts and Brad Pitt also star</k>  </p>
</a>
