<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-10-30 03:42:27"><p id_tv="1044" o="2020-11-06 06:30:00" d="2020-11-06 08:15:00" c="1"><n>Angel Flight Down</n><t>F</t>    <k>51% A child's life is at stake when an emergency flight crashes in the snowy wilderness. Adventure based on a true story with former Baywatch star David Charvet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-11-06 08:15:00" d="2020-11-06 10:05:00" c="1"><n>The Padre</n><t>F</t>    <k>An ex-con known as the Padre seeks redemption as he flees across Colombia from a US Marshal. Action drama with Tim Roth and Nick Nolte</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-11-06 10:05:00" d="2020-11-06 12:05:00" c="1"><n>Inside Man: Most Wanted</n><t>F</t>    <k>The US Federal Reserve is under siege, so an NYPD negotiator and a federal agent work to try to save the day. Action-packed sequel to Inside Man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-11-06 12:05:00" d="2020-11-06 14:10:00" c="1"><n>The Good Liar</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% A con artist thinks he's hit the jackpot when he meets a well-off widow - but things take a turn when he starts to fall for her. Helen Mirren and Ian McKellen star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-11-06 14:10:00" d="2020-11-06 16:10:00" c="1"><n>Killerman</n><t>F</t>    <k>53% When a money launderer wakes up with millions in stolen cash and drugs, and no memory of how he got it, he sets out to find answers. But a crew of dirty cops are after him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-11-06 16:10:00" d="2020-11-06 18:05:00" c="1"><n>The Intruder</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Michael Ealy and Meagan Good star as a young couple who snap up their dream home and couldn't be happier. until the previous owner begins to make their life a living hell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-11-06 18:05:00" d="2020-11-06 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Greta</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% A young woman befriends a lonely widow, who hides a dark and sinister plan behind maternal charm. A Neil Jordan thriller with Chloe Grace Moretz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-11-06 20:00:00" d="2020-11-06 22:00:00" c="1"><n>The Good Liar</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% A con artist thinks he's hit the jackpot when he meets a well-off widow - but things take a turn when he starts to fall for her. Helen Mirren and Ian McKellen star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-11-06 22:00:00" d="2020-11-07 01:00:00" c="1"><n>The Wolf Hour</n><t>F</t>    <k>As a wave of violence and murder sweeps New York City in 1977, a troubled woman tries to hide from the chaos in her apartment. Psychological drama starring Naomi Watts</k>  </p>
</a>
