<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2020-10-30 03:42:35"><p id_tv="1046" o="2020-11-06 05:05:00" d="2020-11-06 06:30:00" c="1"><n>Look Who's Talking Too</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% Roseanne Barr voices the new addition to Kirstie Alley and John Travolta's family, and is just as opinionated as her toddler brother, voiced by Bruce Willis. Comedy sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-11-06 06:30:00" d="2020-11-06 08:25:00" c="1"><n>Tooth Fairy</n><t>F</t>    <k>Arrogant ice hockey player Dwayne Johnson is turned into the tooth fairy for two weeks. Sweet family comedy with Billy Crystal and Stephen Merchant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-11-06 08:25:00" d="2020-11-06 10:10:00" c="1"><n u="Goosebumps">Goosebumps 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Halloween lurches into life when a group of youngsters unwittingly unleash all manner of monsters from an unpublished RL Stine book. Creepy comedy sequel with Ken Jeong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-11-06 10:10:00" d="2020-11-06 12:10:00" c="1"><n>Four Kids And It</n><t>F</t>    <k>Sky original based on Jacqueline Wilson's novel about four children who find a wish-granting sand creature. With Michael Caine, Russell Brand and Matthew Goode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-11-06 12:10:00" d="2020-11-06 14:05:00" c="1"><n>Step Up</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Rough street dancer Channing Tatum learns to tell his pirouette from his body-popping as he dances for the heart of ballet student Jenna Dewan. With Rachel Griffiths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-11-06 14:05:00" d="2020-11-06 15:45:00" c="1"><n>Mousehunt</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Lee Evans and Nathan Lane are the bumbling brothers whose plans to renovate a valuable building are thwarted by a super smart rodent. Comedy with Christopher Walken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-11-06 15:45:00" d="2020-11-06 17:25:00" c="1"><n>The Pacifier</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% When disgraced Navy SEAL Vin Diesel is assigned to guard five kids in quiet suburbia, family life could prove his hardest mission yet. Family comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-11-06 17:25:00" d="2020-11-06 19:00:00" c="1"><n u="Goosebumps">Goosebumps 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Halloween lurches into life when a group of youngsters unwittingly unleash all manner of monsters from an unpublished RL Stine book. Creepy comedy sequel with Ken Jeong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-11-06 19:00:00" d="2020-11-06 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Four Kids And It</n><t>F</t>    <k>Sky original based on Jacqueline Wilson's novel about four children who find a wish-granting sand creature. With Michael Caine, Russell Brand and Matthew Goode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-11-06 21:00:00" d="2020-11-06 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Step Up</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Rough street dancer Channing Tatum learns to tell his pirouette from his body-popping as he dances for the heart of ballet student Jenna Dewan. With Rachel Griffiths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-11-06 23:00:00" d="2020-11-07 02:00:00" c="1"><n>Look Who's Talking Now</n><t>F</t>    <k>46% Danny DeVito and Diane Keaton voice the new pets of couple Kirstie Alley and John Travolta, and their take on the world makes for some eye-opening insights</k>  </p>
</a>
