<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2020-10-24 04:43:25"><p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-31 05:30:00" d="2020-10-31 07:15:00" c="1"><n>Labyrinth</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A teenage girl embarks on a mind-bending adventure when her wish for her baby brother's disappearance comes true. Musical fantasy with Jennifer Connelly and David Bowie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-31 07:15:00" d="2020-10-31 09:00:00" c="1"><n>Casper</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Christina Ricci is the lonely teen who finds friendship with sweet ghost, Casper, despite the efforts of mean spirits Stinkie, Stretch and Fatso. Family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-31 09:00:00" d="2020-10-31 10:50:00" c="1"><n u="Ghostbusters">Ghostbusters 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% When a ghostly painting wreaks havoc in New York, who you gonna call? Comedy sequel starring Bill Murray and Dan Aykroyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-31 10:50:00" d="2020-10-31 12:25:00" c="1"><n>The Witches</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Orphan Luke stumbles onto a witch's plot to rid the world of children. Can he stop their evil scheme? Splendidly scary adaptation of Roald Dahl's novel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-31 12:25:00" d="2020-10-31 14:10:00" c="1"><n>Coraline</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% A young girl is enticed into a wondrous parallel world, that turns out to be a terrifying trap. Animation voiced by Dakota Fanning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-31 14:10:00" d="2020-10-31 15:45:00" c="1"><n u="Goosebumps">Goosebumps 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Halloween lurches into life when a group of youngsters unwittingly unleash all manner of monsters from an unpublished RL Stine book. Creepy comedy sequel with Ken Jeong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-31 15:45:00" d="2020-10-31 17:10:00"><n>Alvin And The Chipmunks Meet Frankenstein</n>    <k>Alvin, Simon and Theodore learn that looks can be deceiving when they wander into Frankenstein's Castle at a theme park and meet the monster himself!(1999)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-31 17:10:00" d="2020-10-31 18:35:00" c="1"><n>Alvin And The Chipmunks Meet The Wolfman</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Alvin and Simon investigate their creepy neighbour after Alvin has a nightmare, while Theodore must find his inner growl when he's cast in a school play</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-31 18:35:00" d="2020-10-31 20:15:00" c="1"><n>Monster House</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Three kids unearth the alarming truth beyond the doorstep of a creepy old house. Spooky family animation with the voices of Steve Buscemi and Kevin James</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-31 20:15:00" d="2020-10-31 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Coraline</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% A young girl is enticed into a wondrous parallel world, that turns out to be a terrifying trap. Animation voiced by Dakota Fanning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-31 22:00:00" d="2020-11-01 01:00:00" c="1"><n u="Goosebumps">Goosebumps 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Halloween lurches into life when a group of youngsters unwittingly unleash all manner of monsters from an unpublished RL Stine book. Creepy comedy sequel with Ken Jeong</k>  </p>
</a>
