<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2020-10-23 04:47:00"><p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-30 05:10:00" d="2020-10-30 06:45:00" c="1"><n>The Witches</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Orphan Luke stumbles onto a witch's plot to rid the world of children. Can he stop their evil scheme? Splendidly scary adaptation of Roald Dahl's novel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-30 06:45:00" d="2020-10-30 08:20:00" c="1"><n>Monster Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>The first Sky Cinema Original Film sees a young family cursed by a witch and transformed into monsters. Animated comedy with the voices of Emily Watson and Jason Isaacs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-30 08:20:00" d="2020-10-30 10:05:00" c="1"><n>The Addams Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% When a stranger claims to be their long lost uncle, the Addams Family attempt to uncover the truth. Comedy with Christina Ricci</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-30 10:05:00" d="2020-10-30 11:55:00" c="1"><n>Ghostbusters</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Classic 80s comedy starring Bill Murray and Dan Aykroyd as paranormal experts battling the supernatural</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-30 11:55:00" d="2020-10-30 13:55:00" c="1"><n>The Goonies</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% This film has outdated attitudes, language and cultural depictions which may cause offence today. Comedy-adventure with Josh Brolin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-30 13:55:00" d="2020-10-30 15:35:00" c="1"><n>Scooby-Doo!</n><t>F</t>    <k>The cowardly cartoon dog is hungry for adventure with meddling human pals Shaggy and the gang. Spooky fun with Matthew Lillard and Sarah Michelle Gellar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-30 15:35:00" d="2020-10-30 17:20:00" c="1"><n>Scooby Doo 2: Monsters Unleashed</n><t>F</t>    <k>A masked villain lets loose a ghostly gang of Scooby's old enemies on Coolsville. Comedy spookfest with Sarah Michelle Gellar and the cowardly hound</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-30 17:20:00" d="2020-10-30 19:10:00" c="1"><n>Labyrinth</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A teenage girl embarks on a mind-bending adventure when her wish for her baby brother's disappearance comes true. Musical fantasy with Jennifer Connelly and David Bowie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-30 19:10:00" d="2020-10-30 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Casper</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Christina Ricci is the lonely teen who finds friendship with sweet ghost, Casper, despite the efforts of mean spirits Stinkie, Stretch and Fatso. Family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-30 21:00:00" d="2020-10-30 22:30:00" c="1"><n>Scooby-Doo!</n><t>F</t>    <k>The cowardly cartoon dog is hungry for adventure with meddling human pals Shaggy and the gang. Spooky fun with Matthew Lillard and Sarah Michelle Gellar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-10-30 22:30:00" d="2020-10-31 01:30:00" c="1"><n>Scooby Doo 2: Monsters Unleashed</n><t>F</t>    <k>A masked villain lets loose a ghostly gang of Scooby's old enemies on Coolsville. Comedy spookfest with Sarah Michelle Gellar and the cowardly hound</k>  </p>
</a>
