<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-10-30 03:42:38"><p id_tv="1047" o="2020-11-06 05:35:00" d="2020-11-06 07:25:00" c="1"><n>My Girl</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Quirky tomboy Anna Chlumsky endures a summer of growing pains alongside best friend Macaulay Culkin in this warm family drama with Dan Aykroyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-11-06 07:25:00" d="2020-11-06 09:25:00" c="1"><n>Flash Gordon</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% This film has outdated attitudes, language and cultural depictions which may cause offence today. Hero Flash Gordon races to save Earth from the Emperor Ming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-11-06 09:25:00" d="2020-11-06 11:40:00" c="1"><n>Unforgiven</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Best Picture Oscar-winner with Clint Eastwood as a hired killer-turned-farmer, who is tempted out of retirement by a big bounty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-11-06 11:40:00" d="2020-11-06 13:35:00" c="1"><n u="Short Circuit">Short Circuit 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% This film has outdated attitudes, language and cultural depictions which may cause offence today. Rebel robot Johnny Five comes to the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-11-06 13:35:00" d="2020-11-06 15:25:00" c="1"><n>Whiplash</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% Miles Teller's ambitious young jazz drummer enrols at a cut-throat music conservatory. Explosive drama with an Oscar-winning turn from JK Simmons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-11-06 15:25:00" d="2020-11-06 17:30:00" c="1"><n>Glory</n><t>F</t>    <k>Oscar-winning drama chronicling the story of the first all-black regiment to fight in the US Civil war. Starring Matthew Broderick, Morgan Freeman and Denzel Washington</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-11-06 17:30:00" d="2020-11-06 19:25:00" c="1"><n>St. Elmo's Fire</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Rob Lowe and Demi Moore star in this tale of college friends facing up to the real world and looking for love and success in the 80s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-11-06 19:25:00" d="2020-11-06 21:00:00" c="1"><n>All The Right Moves</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% Young football player Tom Cruise hopes a college scholarship will help him escape small-town life, but clashes with his coach threaten to derail his dreams. Sports drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-11-06 21:00:00" d="2020-11-06 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Beverly Hills Cop</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Streetwise Detroit detective Eddie Murphy pursues a colleague's killer to LA, causing mayhem for local cop Judge Reinhold. Action comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-11-06 23:00:00" d="2020-11-07 02:00:00" c="1"><n u="Beverly Hills Cop">Beverly Hills Cop II</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Motor-mouthed cop Axel Foley (Eddie Murphy) returns to LA to solve the 'alphabet robberies' that have been baffling local police. Action comedy</k>  </p>
</a>
