<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-10-28 03:49:36"><p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-04 05:15:00" d="2020-11-04 07:00:00" c="1"><n>The Adventure Of A.R.I.: My Robot Friend</n><t>F</t>    <k>44% After repairing a broken robot, a teenager must help his new friend escape the clutches of a ruthless CEO who wants to turn him into a weapon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-04 07:00:00" d="2020-11-04 08:30:00" c="1"><n>Banana Split</n><t>F</t>    <k>After going through a messy break-up with her high-school boyfriend of two years, April mends her heartbreak by striking up an unlikely friendship with his new girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-04 08:30:00" d="2020-11-04 10:00:00" c="1"><n>Ella Bella Bingo</n><t>F</t>    <k>Ella Bella Bingo and her best friend Henry always have so much fun together, but when Henry forms a fast friendship with a new cool kid, Ella Bella becomes jealous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-04 10:00:00" d="2020-11-04 12:00:00" c="1"><n>Above Suspicion</n><t>F</t>    <k>Thriller based on a true story that lead to the first conviction for murder of an FBI agent. Game of Thrones' Emilia Clarke stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-04 12:00:00" d="2020-11-04 14:10:00" c="1"><n>The Invisible Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% A woman believes her abusive ex's suicide was faked. Can she prove she's still being hunted? Sci-fi horror with Elisabeth Moss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-04 14:10:00" d="2020-11-04 16:35:00" c="1"><n>Ash Is The Purest White</n><t>F</t>    <k>Palme d'Or nominated epic Chinese tragicomedy following a woman and her mobster boyfriend in early 21st-century China. With English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-04 16:35:00" d="2020-11-04 18:45:00" c="1"><n>Resistance</n><t>F</t>    <k>Biopic of the early life of Jewish mime artist Marcel Marceau, who fought with the French Resistance to save orphaned children from the Nazis. Jesse Eisenberg stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-04 18:45:00" d="2020-11-04 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Richard Jewell</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Clint Eastwood directs the biopic of a security guard who saved lives after discovering a bomb during the 1996 Olympics - only to be later accused of planting it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-04 21:00:00" d="2020-11-05 00:00:00" c="1"><n>The Invisible Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% A woman believes her abusive ex's suicide was faked. Can she prove she's still being hunted? Sci-fi horror with Elisabeth Moss</k>  </p>
</a>
