<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2020-10-24 04:43:29"><p id_tv="1048" o="2020-10-31 05:00:00" d="2020-10-31 05:15:00"><n>Top Ten: Car Chases</n>    <k>Enjoy a countdown to delight all petrolheads as Sky Cinema zooms through 10 top car movies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-10-31 05:15:00" d="2020-10-31 07:00:00" c="1"><n>The Adventure Of A.R.I.: My Robot Friend</n><t>F</t>    <k>After repairing a broken robot, a teenager must help his new friend escape the clutches of a ruthless CEO who wants to turn him into a weapon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-10-31 07:00:00" d="2020-10-31 08:45:00" c="1"><n>The Secret Garden</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Unlock your imagination as a young orphan discovers a magical garden when she's sent to live on her uncle's estate. Colin Firth stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-10-31 08:45:00" d="2020-10-31 10:45:00" c="1"><n>Anthem Of A Teenage Prophet</n><t>F</t>    <k>A teenager's gift of premonition becomes a curse when he forsees the death of his best friend and is dubbed The Prophet of Death by the media circus that invades his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-10-31 10:45:00" d="2020-10-31 12:30:00" c="1"><n>Abduction</n><t>F</t>    <k>51% A man with no recollection of who he is or where he came from must piece together clues from his past while dodging the dangerous figures that relentlessly chase him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-10-31 12:30:00" d="2020-10-31 14:45:00" c="1"><n>Richard Jewell</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Clint Eastwood directs the biopic of a security guard who saved lives after discovering a bomb during the 1996 Olympics - only to be later accused of planting it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-10-31 14:45:00" d="2020-10-31 17:00:00" c="1"><n>The Invisible Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% A woman believes her abusive ex's suicide was faked. Can she prove she's still being hunted? Sci-fi horror with Elisabeth Moss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-10-31 17:00:00" d="2020-10-31 17:15:00"><n>Black Performances: The Top Ten Show</n>    <k>Celebrate Black History Month with a countdown of 10 incredible performances from Black stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-10-31 17:15:00" d="2020-10-31 19:00:00" c="1"><n>The Secret Garden</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Unlock your imagination as a young orphan discovers a magical garden when she's sent to live on her uncle's estate. Colin Firth stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-10-31 19:00:00" d="2020-10-31 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Above Suspicion</n><t>F</t>    <k>Thriller based on a true story that lead to the first conviction for murder of an FBI agent. Game of Thrones' Emilia Clarke stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-10-31 21:00:00" d="2020-11-01 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Richard Jewell</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Clint Eastwood directs the biopic of a security guard who saved lives after discovering a bomb during the 1996 Olympics - only to be later accused of planting it</k>  </p>
</a>
