<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2020-10-27 04:08:33"><p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-03 05:15:00" d="2020-11-03 07:00:00" c="1"><n>The Adventure Of A.R.I.: My Robot Friend</n><t>F</t>    <k>44% After repairing a broken robot, a teenager must help his new friend escape the clutches of a ruthless CEO who wants to turn him into a weapon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-03 07:00:00" d="2020-11-03 09:00:00" c="1"><n>Anthem Of A Teenage Prophet</n><t>F</t>    <k>A teenager's gift of premonition becomes a curse when he forsees the death of his best friend and is dubbed The Prophet of Death by the media circus that invades his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-03 09:00:00" d="2020-11-03 09:15:00"><n>Top Ten: Big Screen Preview</n>    <k>Get excited! Sky Cinema counts down 10 fantastic films that will be hitting screens soon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-03 09:15:00" d="2020-11-03 11:15:00" c="1"><n>Above Suspicion</n><t>F</t>    <k>Thriller based on a true story that lead to the first conviction for murder of an FBI agent. Game of Thrones' Emilia Clarke stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-03 11:15:00" d="2020-11-03 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Resistance</n><t>F</t>    <k>Biopic of the early life of Jewish mime artist Marcel Marceau, who fought with the French Resistance to save orphaned children from the Nazis. Jesse Eisenberg stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-03 13:30:00" d="2020-11-03 13:45:00"><n>Top Ten: Car Chases</n>    <k>Enjoy a countdown to delight all petrolheads as Sky Cinema zooms through 10 top car movies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-03 13:45:00" d="2020-11-03 16:00:00" c="1"><n>The Invisible Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% A woman believes her abusive ex's suicide was faked. Can she prove she's still being hunted? Sci-fi horror with Elisabeth Moss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-03 16:00:00" d="2020-11-03 17:45:00" c="1"><n>Killer Instinct</n><t>F</t>    <k>After losing her job, a woman flees the city for a relaxing weekend, but things take a scary turn when she rents a house from an eccentric widower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-03 17:45:00" d="2020-11-03 18:00:00"><n>Top Ten: Denzel Washington</n>    <k>Sky Cinema counts down the top 10 films featuring the Oscar-winning Denzel Washington</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-03 18:00:00" d="2020-11-03 19:30:00" c="1"><n>Ella Bella Bingo</n><t>F</t>    <k>Ella Bella Bingo and her best friend Henry always have so much fun together, but when Henry forms a fast friendship with a new cool kid, Ella Bella becomes jealous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-03 19:30:00" d="2020-11-03 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Banana Split</n><t>F</t>    <k>After going through a messy break-up with her high-school boyfriend of two years, April mends her heartbreak by striking up an unlikely friendship with his new girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-11-03 21:00:00" d="2020-11-04 00:00:00" c="1"><n>The Invisible Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% A woman believes her abusive ex's suicide was faked. Can she prove she's still being hunted? Sci-fi horror with Elisabeth Moss</k>  </p>
</a>
