<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-10-27 04:08:18"><p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-03 05:20:00" d="2020-11-03 07:20:00" c="1"><n>Judy</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Academy Award winner Renée Zellweger stars as showbiz legend Judy Garland in this dramatic biopic focusing on the icon's later years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-03 07:20:00" d="2020-11-03 09:20:00" c="1"><n>Always</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Firefighting pilot Richard Dreyfuss dies but returns to watch over Holly Hunter. Steven Spielberg's fantasy romance features Audrey Hepburn's last role</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-03 09:20:00" d="2020-11-03 10:55:00" c="1"><n>Changeland</n><t>F</t>    <k>Following a devastating personal crisis, a man jets off on a Thailand adventure with a childhood friend in a bid to cure his blues. Comedy-drama with Macaulay Culkin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-03 10:55:00" d="2020-11-03 12:25:00" c="1"><n>The Assistant</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% A young graduate lands her dream job as a junior assistant to a commanding entertainment mogul, but must take a stand when things take a dark turn and power is abused</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-03 12:25:00" d="2020-11-03 15:05:00" c="1"><n>Almost Famous</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Extended edition of the Oscar-winning comedy-drama following a wannabe journalist who heads on tour with a rising rock band. Kate Hudson and Billy Crudup star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-03 15:05:00" d="2020-11-03 17:00:00" c="1"><n>Hands Of Stone</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Boxing biopic charting the life and career of former world champion Roberto Duran, and the lead-up to his history-making fight with Sugar Ray Leonard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-03 17:00:00" d="2020-11-03 18:50:00" c="1"><n>That Thing You Do!</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Tom Hanks makes his directing debut with an upbeat tale about a 60s boy band. Comedy featuring early roles for Liv Tyler and Charlize Theron</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-03 18:50:00" d="2020-11-03 21:00:00" c="1"><n>A League Of Their Own</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% In WWII, while the men are on the battlefield, the women are on the playing field. Tom Hanks and Madonna star in a feelgood tale about the first female baseball league</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-03 21:00:00" d="2020-11-04 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Almost Famous</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Extended edition of the Oscar-winning comedy-drama following a wannabe journalist who heads on tour with a rising rock band. Kate Hudson and Billy Crudup star</k>  </p>
</a>
