<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-10-28 03:49:25"><p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-04 05:25:00" d="2020-11-04 07:35:00" c="1"><n>A League Of Their Own</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% In WWII, while the men are on the battlefield, the women are on the playing field. Tom Hanks and Madonna star in a feelgood tale about the first female baseball league</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-04 07:35:00" d="2020-11-04 09:10:00" c="1"><n>Chasing Bullitt</n><t>F</t>    <k>Hollywood icon Steve McQueen searches for the iconic Mustang from his film BULLITT, reflecting on his life's highs and lows along the way. Biopic drama with Andre Brooks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-04 09:10:00" d="2020-11-04 11:05:00" c="1"><n>The Front Runner</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Hugh Jackman stars as a promising presidential candidate who suffers a profound fall from grace when scandalous rumours begin to derail his campaign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-04 11:05:00" d="2020-11-04 13:10:00" c="1"><n>Notting Hill</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Bookshop owner Hugh Grant forms an unlikely romance with superstar actress Julia Roberts in this hit Richard Curtis romcom. Co-stars Rhys Ifans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-04 13:10:00" d="2020-11-04 15:25:00" c="1"><n>American Sniper</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Bradley Cooper takes on the role of Chris Kyle, the deadliest marksman in US military history. Oscar-nominated biopic from director Clint Eastwood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-04 15:25:00" d="2020-11-04 17:15:00" c="1"><n>Field Of Dreams</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Moving fantasy starring Kevin Costner as a Iowa farmer who, in answer to a mystical voice, turns his cornfield into a baseball pitch, with miraculous results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-04 17:15:00" d="2020-11-04 18:55:00" c="1"><n>The Truth About Cats &amp; Dogs</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Shy talks how host Janeane Garofalo makes a date with caller Ben Chaplin, but chickens out and sends gorgeous Uma Thurman in her place. Romcom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-04 18:55:00" d="2020-11-04 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Notting Hill</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Bookshop owner Hugh Grant forms an unlikely romance with superstar actress Julia Roberts in this hit Richard Curtis romcom. Co-stars Rhys Ifans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-11-04 21:00:00" d="2020-11-05 00:00:00" c="1"><n>American Sniper</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Bradley Cooper takes on the role of Chris Kyle, the deadliest marksman in US military history. Oscar-nominated biopic from director Clint Eastwood</k>  </p>
</a>
