<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2020-10-28 03:49:02"><p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 05:00:00" d="2020-11-04 05:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Who's Got The Lady?
When a piece of art is stolen, the gallery owner gets his girlfriend to make copies of it to sell. But did the work ever really leave the building?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 05:30:00" d="2020-11-04 06:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Skeleton Key
A woman discovers a nasty side to her husband's personality when he goes into hospital before a holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 06:00:00" d="2020-11-04 06:30:00"><n u="Zaha Hadid: The South Bank Show Originals">Zaha Hadid: The South Bank Show Originals IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Melvyn Bragg looks back on his eye-opening 2007 meeting with the world-renowned Iraqi-British architect Zaha Hadid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 06:30:00" d="2020-11-04 07:00:00"><n u="Auction">Auction V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A painting from Monet's watercolour series fetches an impressive price at Sotheby's. Elsewhere in London, rare pieces by French glassmaker Rene Lalique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 07:00:00" d="2020-11-04 08:15:00"><n>Anoushka Shankar In Concert</n>    <k>Sitar star Anoushka Shankar honours her father's friendship with Yehudi Menuhin with Indian music and traditional raggas in Berlin. With violinist Patricia Kopatchinskaja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 08:15:00" d="2020-11-04 10:00:00"><n>A Tuba To Cuba</n>    <k>Critically acclaimed documentary following the leader of New Orleans' renowned Preservation Hall Jazz Band, as he ventures to Cuba to trace the band's musical roots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 10:00:00" d="2020-11-04 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Who's Got The Lady?
When a piece of art is stolen, the gallery owner gets his girlfriend to make copies of it to sell. But did the work ever really leave the building?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 10:30:00" d="2020-11-04 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Skeleton Key
A woman discovers a nasty side to her husband's personality when he goes into hospital before a holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 11:00:00" d="2020-11-04 11:30:00"><n u="Primal Scream: Music Icons">Primal Scream: Music Icons III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look into the unique sound of rock band Primal Scream, formed by Bobby Gillespie and Jim Beattie in the 80s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 11:30:00" d="2020-11-04 12:00:00"><n u="Bjork: Video Killed The Radio Star">Bjork: Video Killed The Radio Star VI (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the creative processes behind some of Bjork's most iconic music videos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 12:00:00" d="2020-11-04 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Walter Matthau">Discovering: Walter Matthau V (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Film experts reflect on the life and career of Oscar-winning actor Walter Matthau, who starred in the comedies Fortune Cookie, The Odd Couple and Grumpy Old Men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 13:00:00" d="2020-11-04 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Shirley Maclaine">Discovering: Shirley Maclaine V (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of Shirley MacLaine, one of Hollywood's legendary leading ladies, who starred in films including The Apartment and Sweet Charity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 14:00:00" d="2020-11-04 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Passing Opportunity
Frank is struggling financially and will do anything for money. When he meets a rich and successful schoolmate, he realises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 14:30:00" d="2020-11-04 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Memory Man
Down on his luck, 'Memory Man' Colin agrees to help a shady character remember the number of a station locker. But then Colin becomes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 15:00:00" d="2020-11-04 16:00:00"><n u="The Adventurers Of Modern Art">The Adventurers Of Modern Art I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Libertad!
In 1936, war erupts in Spain. While Malraux and Hemingway cover the Republicans' struggle as journalists, Picasso creates a monumental canvas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 16:00:00" d="2020-11-04 16:30:00"><n u="Cher: The South Bank Show Originals">Cher: The South Bank Show Originals IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>71% Melvyn Bragg recalls his 1999 meeting with iconic singer and actress Cher, who candidly discussed her career highs and lows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 16:30:00" d="2020-11-04 17:00:00"><n u="Auction">Auction V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A French Second Empire mirror is the star of a London sale. Photographs by the late Elsbeth Juda go up for grabs. Plus, will anyone pay over ?100,000</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 17:00:00" d="2020-11-04 17:30:00"><n u="Smokey Robinson: Music Icons">Smokey Robinson: Music Icons III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A glimpse into the life of the soulful superstar who founded and fronted The Miracles before embarking on a solo career and working as vice president of Motown Records</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 17:30:00" d="2020-11-04 18:00:00"><n u="Depeche Mode: Video Killed The Radio Star">Depeche Mode: Video Killed The Radio Star VI (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An eye-opening behind-the-scenes look at the making of Depeche Mode's most notable music videos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 18:00:00" d="2020-11-04 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Charles Bronson">Discovering: Charles Bronson V (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Film experts reflect on the work of Charles Bronson, who became a Hollywood star with his tough-guy, vigilante roles in films such as The Magnificent Seven and Death Wish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 19:00:00" d="2020-11-04 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Peter O'Toole">Discovering: Peter O'Toole VI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and work of Peter O'Toole, the late stage and film actor who shot to fame by playing TE Lawrence in Lawrence of Arabia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 20:00:00" d="2020-11-04 21:00:00"><n u="The Art Of Architecture">The Art Of Architecture I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at Ptolemy Dean's Weston Tower, which lies within Westminster Abbey. What went into designing the most significant addition to this historic site in 240 years?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 21:00:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00"><n u="New: Portrait Artist Of The Year">New: Portrait Artist Of The Year VII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Ray BLK, James Nesbitt, Pam Hogg
As the fourth heat kicks off, musician Ray BLK, actor James Nesbit and designer Pam Hogg all sit down for portraits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 23:00:00"><n u="The Sixties">The Sixties I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Long March to Freedom
An in-depth look into Martin Luther King Jr and his courageous efforts to lead the civil rights movement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-04 23:00:00" d="2020-11-05 02:00:00"><n u="New: Life &amp; Rhymes">New: Life &amp; Rhymes (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Harry Baker, Fury WD, 2 Badda, Lams and Gecko join Benjamin Zephaniah at London's Battersea Park for a celebration of poetry in a unique spoken-word performance show</k>  </p>
</a>
