<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-10-27 04:07:40"><p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 05:05:00" d="2020-11-03 05:35:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In The Bag
Cara hires safecracker Sam to get back her confiscated jewels. But when she insists on joining him on the job, Sam could be making the biggest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 05:35:00" d="2020-11-03 06:05:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Man With A Fortune
A rich and lonely American ventures to England in search of his long-lost family. But when he meets Jane and her flatmate Eva, things begin to go wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 06:05:00" d="2020-11-03 06:30:00"><n u="Eric Clapton: The South Bank Show Originals">Eric Clapton: The South Bank Show Originals IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>72% Melvyn Bragg looks back to 1987 and 2007 when he met singer-songwriter Eric Clapton to discuss his music and influences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 06:30:00" d="2020-11-03 07:00:00"><n u="Auction">Auction V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at some of the most valuable and iconic pieces to recently be sold at the world's greatest auction houses. A painting by Francesco Guardi goes under the hammer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 07:00:00" d="2020-11-03 08:00:00"><n>Raphael: In Search Of Beauty</n>    <k>This intriguing look at the life and art of Raphael explores the High Renaissance master's quest for beauty, reflected most notably in his work Portrait of a Young Woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 08:00:00" d="2020-11-03 10:00:00"><n>Giselle</n>    <k>Peter Wright's production of Marius Petipa's classic romantic ballet is a tale of betrayal, the supernatural and love that transcends death. From London's Royal Opera House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 10:00:00" d="2020-11-03 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In The Bag
Cara hires safecracker Sam to get back her confiscated jewels. But when she insists on joining him on the job, Sam could be making the biggest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 10:30:00" d="2020-11-03 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Man With A Fortune
A rich and lonely American ventures to England in search of his long-lost family. But when he meets Jane and her flatmate Eva, things begin to go wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 11:00:00" d="2020-11-03 11:30:00"><n u="Pat Benatar: Music Icons">Pat Benatar: Music Icons III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look into the life and career of the four-time Grammy Award-winning rock singer, who gained popularity with songs like We Belong and Hit Me With Your Best Shot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 11:30:00" d="2020-11-03 12:00:00"><n u="ZZ Top: Video Killed The Radio Star">ZZ Top: Video Killed The Radio Star VI (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Directors and musicians reveal the ideas and inspirations that helped create ZZ Top's most memorable music videos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 12:00:00" d="2020-11-03 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Gregory Peck">Discovering: Gregory Peck V (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An eye-opening look at the life and films of American film legend Gregory Peck, the Academy Award-winning star of the 1962 drama To Kill a Mockingbird</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 13:00:00" d="2020-11-03 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Claudia Cardinale">Discovering: Claudia Cardinale V (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intriguing profile of Tunisian-born Italian film actress Claudia Cardinale, who appeared in some of the most acclaimed European films of the 1960s and 1970s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 14:00:00" d="2020-11-03 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Who's Got The Lady?
When a piece of art is stolen, the gallery owner gets his girlfriend to make copies of it to sell. But did the work ever really leave the building?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 14:30:00" d="2020-11-03 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Skeleton Key
A woman discovers a nasty side to her husband's personality when he goes into hospital before a holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 15:00:00" d="2020-11-03 16:00:00"><n u="River Phoenix: Too Young To Die">River Phoenix: Too Young To Die I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life of Stand By Me actor River Phoenix, who died outside LA nightclub The Viper Room due to a drug overdose in 1993, aged just 23</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 16:00:00" d="2020-11-03 16:30:00"><n u="Zaha Hadid: The South Bank Show Originals">Zaha Hadid: The South Bank Show Originals IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Melvyn Bragg looks back on his eye-opening 2007 meeting with the world-renowned Iraqi-British architect Zaha Hadid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 16:30:00" d="2020-11-03 17:00:00"><n u="Auction">Auction V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A painting from Monet's watercolour series fetches an impressive price at Sotheby's. Elsewhere in London, rare pieces by French glassmaker Rene Lalique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 17:00:00" d="2020-11-03 17:30:00"><n u="Primal Scream: Music Icons">Primal Scream: Music Icons III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look into the unique sound of rock band Primal Scream, formed by Bobby Gillespie and Jim Beattie in the 80s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 17:30:00" d="2020-11-03 18:00:00"><n u="Bjork: Video Killed The Radio Star">Bjork: Video Killed The Radio Star VI (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the creative processes behind some of Bjork's most iconic music videos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 18:00:00" d="2020-11-03 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Walter Matthau">Discovering: Walter Matthau V (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Film experts reflect on the life and career of Oscar-winning actor Walter Matthau, who starred in the comedies Fortune Cookie, The Odd Couple and Grumpy Old Men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 19:00:00" d="2020-11-03 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Shirley Maclaine">Discovering: Shirley Maclaine V (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of Shirley MacLaine, one of Hollywood's legendary leading ladies, who starred in films including The Apartment and Sweet Charity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 20:00:00" d="2020-11-03 21:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Home Sweet Home
The photographers return home as they are challenged to capture themselves, their families and their roots. Johnny Briggs assists them back in the studio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 21:00:00" d="2020-11-03 21:30:00"><n u="New: Rankin's">New: Rankin's 2020 (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Fun
In the final episode, Rankin takes a stunning action portrait of a tennis star, and is re-joined by Brett Rogers and Layton Williams to choose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 21:30:00" d="2020-11-03 22:00:00"><n u="The British">The British I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Nations
An insightful look into the Celtic nations' view of the union today, with a musical sketch show in Glasgow and a new take on the Union Jack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 22:00:00" d="2020-11-03 23:00:00"><n>New: The Grapes Of Wrath: The Ghost of Modern America</n>    <k>New. Eye-opening film examining the scandalous, cult book by John Steinbeck. 80 years later, the themes in the novel are more current than ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-11-03 23:00:00" d="2020-11-04 02:00:00"><n>New: The Booksellers</n>    <k>New. A celebration of literary culture, and a fascinating look at New York's rare book world. Meet its remarkable inhabitants, from writers and collectors</k>  </p>
</a>
