<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-10-23 04:46:30"><p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 05:00:00" d="2020-10-30 05:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Light Fingers
Tired of gloves vanishing from his factory, Ralph hires a detective. Then, when he tells his wife about the thefts, gloves begin appearing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 05:30:00" d="2020-10-30 06:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Death In The Morning
Karen marries a rich landowner with a huge house in the country. But after moving in, she senses an evil spirit. and it's out to get her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 06:00:00" d="2020-10-30 06:30:00"><n u="Elizabeth Taylor: The South Bank Show Originals">Elizabeth Taylor: The South Bank Show Originals III (29)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Melvyn Bragg looks back on his 1992 meeting with Elizabeth Taylor, offering a fascinating insight into the real woman behind the Hollywood facade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 06:30:00" d="2020-10-30 07:00:00"><n u="Auction">Auction IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A still life painted on the back of one of Francis Bacon's discarded works goes on sale in the UK, along with rare travel books and Winston Churchill memorabilia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 07:00:00" d="2020-10-30 08:00:00"><n u="Darbar Festival">Darbar Festival 2017 (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mridangam sensation Patri Satish Kumar is joined by Tavil Triplicane Sekar and Amrit Khanjira in this uplifting performance at the 2017 Darbar festival in London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 08:00:00" d="2020-10-30 10:00:00"><n>Celtic Woman: Believe</n>    <k>The Irish all-female ensemble give a magical performance in America, featuring incredible visual effects and all their best-loved songs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 10:00:00" d="2020-10-30 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Light Fingers
Tired of gloves vanishing from his factory, Ralph hires a detective. Then, when he tells his wife about the thefts, gloves begin appearing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 10:30:00" d="2020-10-30 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Death In The Morning
Karen marries a rich landowner with a huge house in the country. But after moving in, she senses an evil spirit. and it's out to get her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 11:00:00" d="2020-10-30 11:30:00"><n u="Journey: Music Icons">Journey: Music Icons III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The story of Journey, one of the world's best-selling bands of all time. Many of their hits, including Don't Stop Believin', remain firmly embedded in popular culture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 11:30:00" d="2020-10-30 12:00:00"><n u="Lou Reed: Video Killed The Radio Star">Lou Reed: Video Killed The Radio Star VI (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Directors and musicians discuss the secrets behind creating some of Lou Reed's best-loved music videos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 12:00:00" d="2020-10-30 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Buster Keaton">Discovering: Buster Keaton V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate profile of silent film pioneer Buster Keaton, whose stone-faced physical comedy turned him into a Hollywood superstar in the 1920s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 13:00:00" d="2020-10-30 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Olivia De Havilland">Discovering: Olivia De Havilland V (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A profile of Olivia de Havilland, who has sadly passed away. Best known as Melanie in Gone with the Wind, she won Academy Awards for her roles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 14:00:00" d="2020-10-30 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>What Have You Been Up To Lately?
Richard and Fergus meet after 25 years. Pondering a girl they both loved, they discover that their marriages failed along with their careers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 14:30:00" d="2020-10-30 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Absence Of Emily
Norma owns a big house and lets her sister Emily and her husband live there. But when Emily disappears, Norma makes too much fuss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 15:00:00" d="2020-10-30 16:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Irish Landscape
In Ireland, the contestants attempt to capture the beauty of Kerry County's landscape with the help of renowned Italian photographer Franco Fontana</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 16:00:00" d="2020-10-30 16:30:00"><n u="Jodie Foster: The South Bank Show Originals">Jodie Foster: The South Bank Show Originals III (30)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Melvyn Bragg looks back on a classic 1995 episode of The South Bank Show, in which he spent time with Oscar-winning actress Jodie Foster. Last in series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 16:30:00" d="2020-10-30 17:00:00"><n u="Auction">Auction IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A collection of Picasso ceramics goes up for grabs at London's Sothebys. Plus, needlework telling the story of the US goes on sale in an 'Americana' auction in New York</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 17:00:00" d="2020-10-30 17:30:00"><n u="Marvin Gaye: Music Icons">Marvin Gaye: Music Icons III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look into the life and career of The Prince of Soul, and his many famous hits, from the sultry Sexual Healing to the heartfelt What's Going On</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 17:30:00" d="2020-10-30 18:00:00"><n u="Crowded House: Video Killed The Radio Star">Crowded House: Video Killed The Radio Star VI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A unique insight into the ideas and vision behind the music videos of BRIT Award-winning rock band Crowded House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 18:00:00" d="2020-10-30 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: William Holden">Discovering: William Holden V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of William Holden, an actor who became one of Hollywood's biggest box office draws from the 1950s through to the 1970s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 19:00:00" d="2020-10-30 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Barbara Stanwyck">Discovering: Barbara Stanwyck V (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A profile of Barbara Stanwyck, an actress who enjoyed a 60-year career in film and television, best known for her strong female roles in films, such as Double Indemnity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 20:00:00" d="2020-10-30 21:00:00"><n u="Trailblazers: Nuclear Protest">Trailblazers: Nuclear Protest I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the politics behind - and evolution of - anti-nuclear songs, from western swing and country to gospel, jazz and rockabilly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 21:00:00" d="2020-10-30 22:00:00"><n u="Soundtracks: Songs That Defined History">Soundtracks: Songs That Defined History I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Battle of the Sexes
Billie Jean King's tennis victory against Bobby Riggs in 1973 ushered in music that delivered messages of female empowerment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-10-30 22:00:00" d="2020-10-31 01:00:00"><n>Brian Johnson Meets Dave Grohl</n>    <k>. rohl. Two rock 'n' roll Hall of Famers come together at the Foo Fighters' studio in Los Angeles as the AC/DC frontman chats with the Nirvana drummer</k>  </p>
</a>
