<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2020-10-24 04:43:57"><p id_tv="1056" o="2020-10-31 07:00:00" d="2020-10-31 07:15:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Man U/L'Pool '95</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches in the Premier League. Here, Man United host Liverpool in October 1995, as Eric Cantona returned from his lengthy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-10-31 07:15:00" d="2020-10-31 07:30:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:L'Pool/Man U '97</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches in the Premier League. Here, Liverpool meet Manchester United at Anfield in 1997, in a match that had a happy outcome for the Red Devils</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-10-31 07:30:00" d="2020-10-31 07:45:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:L'Pool/Man U '01</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches in the Premier League. Here, Liverpool meet Manchester United in 2001, as a Michael Owen brace guided the home side to victory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-10-31 07:45:00" d="2020-10-31 08:00:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Man U/L'Pool '10</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches in the Premier League. Here, Manchester United meet Liverpool in 2010, with a Dimitar Berbatov hat-trick proving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-10-31 08:00:00" d="2020-10-31 08:30:00"><n>PL Legends: Paul Ince</n><t>O</t>    <k>Series profiling some of the greatest players to grace the Premier League. As part of Black History Month, here the focus is on former Manchester United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-10-31 08:30:00" d="2020-10-31 09:30:00"><n>Premier League World</n><t>O</t>    <k>Head behind the scenes of the Premier League, catch up with former stars and get the full picture of life in the top flight, with interviews, features and much more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-10-31 09:30:00" d="2020-10-31 10:00:00"><n>Premier League Matchpack</n><t>O</t>    <k>A game-by-game breakdown of all the weekend's Premier League action, with all the key stats and insight. Matches include Liverpool v West Ham and Man Utd v Arsenal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-10-31 10:00:00" d="2020-10-31 10:30:00"><n>Premier League Preview</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look ahead to the weekend's matches in the Premier League, with analysis of all the key talking points. Matches include Man Utd v Arsenal and Sheffield United v Man City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-10-31 10:30:00" d="2020-10-31 11:30:00"><n>Saturday Social</n><t>O</t>    <k>A fresh take on the beautiful game. Hear about football's hot topics on social media and look at footballers' lives off the pitch, with musicians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-10-31 11:30:00" d="2020-10-31 18:00:00"><n>New: Soccer A.M - Live</n><t>O</t>    <k>John Fendley and Jimmy Bullard are joined by guests from the world of sports and entertainment for the ever-popular Saturday morning football show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-10-31 18:00:00" d="2020-10-31 21:00:00"><n>Live SNF: Liverpool v West Ham</n><t>O</t>    <k>Liverpool welcome West Ham United to Anfield in Saturday evening action from the Premier League. The Reds were 3-2 winners in this fixture last season</k>  </p>
</a>
