<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2020-10-30 03:43:25"><p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 05:00:00" d="2020-11-06 06:00:00"><n>Best Premier League Goals 04/05</n><t>O</t>    <k>Enjoy some of the best Premier League goals from years gone by. Here, the finest strikes from the 2004-2005 season, a year in which Chelsea strolled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 06:00:00" d="2020-11-06 06:30:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Man Utd/Newcastle</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take a look back at some of the best goals from Premier League meetings between Manchester United and Newcastle United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 06:30:00" d="2020-11-06 07:00:00"><n>PL 100 Club: Ryan Giggs</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Premier League history. Here the focus is on Manchester United great Ryan Giggs. Tweet your favourite #pl100club</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 07:00:00" d="2020-11-06 07:15:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Man U/L'Pool '14</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches in the Premier League. Here, Man United host Liverpool in March 2014 in a remarkable contest that saw the visitors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 07:15:00" d="2020-11-06 07:30:00"><n>PL Greatest : Chelsea/Man Utd 2012</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, rewind to 2012 for a memorable, ill-tempered clash between high-flying Chelsea and Man Utd at Stamford Bridge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 07:30:00" d="2020-11-06 07:45:00"><n>PL Greatest : Man Utd/Chelsea 2014</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, rewind to 2014 for a pulsating encounter between Manchester United and Chelsea at Old Trafford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 07:45:00" d="2020-11-06 08:00:00"><n>PL Greatest : Chelsea/Man Utd 2016</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, rewind to 2016 as Jose Mourinho returns to Stamford Bridge with his Manchester United side to face Chelsea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 08:00:00" d="2020-11-06 08:30:00"><n>PL Legends: Sol Campbell</n><t>O</t>    <k>Series profiling some of the greatest players to grace the Premier League. As part of Black History Month, here the focus is on former Tottenham Hotspur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 08:30:00" d="2020-11-06 09:00:00"><n>PL Legends: Robert Pires</n><t>O</t>    <k>Series profiling some of the greatest players to have graced the Premier League. Here the focus is on former Arsenal winger Robert Pires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 09:00:00" d="2020-11-06 09:30:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Manchester United</n><t>O</t>    <k>Enjoy the best Premier League goals scored by Manchester United over the years. See strikes from legends of the game including Ryan Giggs, David Beckham and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 09:30:00" d="2020-11-06 10:00:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Manchester City</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at the very best goals scored by Manchester City in the history of the Premier League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 10:00:00" d="2020-11-06 10:30:00"><n>PL 100 Club: Les Ferdinand</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Premier League history. As part of Black History Month, here the focus is on former Newcastle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 10:30:00" d="2020-11-06 11:00:00"><n>PL 100 Club: Andy Cole</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Premier League history. As part of Black History Month, this episode features the best of Andy Cole's goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 11:00:00" d="2020-11-06 12:00:00"><n>Live: The Football Show</n><t>O</t>    <k>Round-up of the sports news with live analysis and comment plus extended interviews with the headline makers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 12:00:00" d="2020-11-06 13:00:00"><n>Live: The Football Show</n><t>O</t>    <k>Round-up of the sports news with live analysis and comment plus extended interviews with the headline makers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 13:00:00" d="2020-11-06 13:30:00"><n>Soccerbox: John Barnes</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with Liverpool legend John Barnes as they look back at some of the most memorable matches from their careers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 13:30:00" d="2020-11-06 14:00:00"><n>Soccerbox: Matt Le Tissier</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with Southampton great Matt Le Tissier as they relive some of the most compelling matches where they played each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 14:00:00" d="2020-11-06 16:00:00"><n>Premier League Years 1999/00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take a look back at all the most memorable moments from the 1999-2000 season. Alex Ferguson's Red Devils were the team everybody feared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 16:00:00" d="2020-11-06 17:00:00"><n>Best Premier League Goals 95/96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sky Sports takes a look at some of the best goals from Premier League seasons in years gone by. Here, enjoy some of the best goals from the 95-96 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 17:00:00" d="2020-11-06 17:15:00"><n u="PL Greatest Games:Arsenal/Spurs">PL Greatest Games:Arsenal/Spurs 08</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the Premier League. Here, Arsenal meet Tottenham Hotspur in the north London derby in 2008-09 season, in a match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 17:15:00" d="2020-11-06 17:30:00"><n>Best of Wenger: Man U/Arsenal '98</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember a classic match from the Premier League. Here, Arsenal visit Alex Ferguson's Manchester United at Old Trafford back in the 1997-98 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 17:30:00" d="2020-11-06 17:45:00"><n>PL Greatest: Man Utd/Everton 2012</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the Premier League. Here, Man Utd host Everton at Old Trafford in a captivating eight-goal thriller back in 2012</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 17:45:00" d="2020-11-06 18:00:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Newc/Leics '97</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, Newcastle United host Leicester City in a seven-goal thriller at St James' Park in the 1996-97 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 18:00:00" d="2020-11-06 18:30:00"><n>PL 100 Club: Les Ferdinand</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Premier League history. As part of Black History Month, here the focus is on former Newcastle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 18:30:00" d="2020-11-06 19:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n><t>O</t>    <k>Head behind the scenes of the Premier League, catch up with former stars and get the full picture of life in the top flight, with interviews, features and much more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 19:00:00" d="2020-11-06 19:30:00"><n>Premier League Matchpack</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look ahead to the weekend's matches in the Premier League, with all the key facts and stats needed. Games include Everton v Man United, Man City v Liverpool and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 19:30:00" d="2020-11-06 20:00:00"><n>New: Premier League Preview</n><t>O</t>    <k>A preview of the weekend's matches in the Premier League, with a look at all the key talking points. Matches include Everton v Manchester United and Man City v Liverpool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 20:00:00" d="2020-11-06 20:30:00"><n>New: Premier League Specials</n><t>O</t>    <k>A team of pundits and guests go through the stats and the fan votes to choose their ultimate Premier League team of the month</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2020-11-06 20:30:00" d="2020-11-06 23:30:00"><n>Live FNF: Southampton v Newcastle</n><t>O</t>    <k>Ralph Hasenhuttl's Southampton welcome Newcastle United to St Mary's Stadium for Friday Night Football from the Premier League. With Sky Sports Crowds</k>  </p>
</a>
