<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-10-28 03:43:45"><p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 05:00:00" d="2020-11-04 06:00:00"><n u="Fear Thy Neighbour">Fear Thy Neighbour V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Deadly Duplex
A retiree rents out half his duplex to a troubled family and becomes smitten with the wife after sending her abusive husband packing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 06:00:00" d="2020-11-04 06:30:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Bound to Die
The tragic story of Elizabeth Marriott, who was lured to a co-worker's New Hampshire home as a sex offering for her domineering killer boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 06:30:00" d="2020-11-04 07:00:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Co-Ed Killer
Police attempt to track down a serial killer when young, female students disappear with alarming frequency from the college town of Santa Cruz, California</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 07:00:00" d="2020-11-04 08:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Stolen Innocence
Detectives race against the clock in the wake of a homicide, desperate to find a lead within the first 48 hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 08:00:00" d="2020-11-04 09:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% The Standing Ground
A dangerous decision sees a high-school student shot to the ground. But who fired the fatal bullet? Detectives race the clock to unearth the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 09:00:00" d="2020-11-04 10:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Make My Day
The documentary series continues as retired Colorado Springs police detective Joseph Kenda reflects on another harrowing case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 10:00:00" d="2020-11-04 11:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Secret Life
Joe Kenda is stumped for suspects when a woman is found dead in her car. Can he uncover and unravel her mysterious double life in order to find her killer?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 11:00:00" d="2020-11-04 12:00:00"><n u="Unusual Suspects">Unusual Suspects IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Killings In Kentucky
A respected vet, his wife and son are viciously gunned down in their home. Can detectives unearth the bitter truth behind this tragic crime?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 12:00:00" d="2020-11-04 12:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (34)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Late Night Killer
Police are baffled when a woman is found dead in her home. Her four-year-old son saw the crime. But can his testimony be trusted?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 12:30:00" d="2020-11-04 13:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (35)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Family Night Nightmare
Police investigate when a woman is sprung awake by a shotgun blast. She finds her husband dead beside her. but claims she didn't see anything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 13:00:00" d="2020-11-04 14:00:00"><n u="Nightmare In Suburbia">Nightmare In Suburbia I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Death For Dinner
In a smart suburb of Stoke-on-Trent, Kate Knight was preparing to celebrate her wedding anniversary, but why had she laced her husband's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 14:00:00" d="2020-11-04 15:00:00"><n u="What The Killer Did Next">What The Killer Did Next I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Norma Bell
Police are at a loss when a 79-year-old is killed in her Hartlepool home. But when the evidence mounts and the killer's movements are tracked, the net closes in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 15:00:00" d="2020-11-04 16:00:00"><n u="Meet, Marry, Murder">Meet, Marry, Murder I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Mahmuda Khatun
After just 33 days of marriage, Mahmuda Khatun fatally stabbed her husband in the chest on his 28th birthday. What drove her to commit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 16:00:00" d="2020-11-04 17:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Powder Keg
When uninvited guests crash a barrio birthday party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 17:00:00" d="2020-11-04 18:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Michael Faast
Series showcasing the career of Colorado detective Joe Kenda. Here, he tracks the killer of a furniture salesman who was shot point-blank in the temple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 18:00:00" d="2020-11-04 19:00:00"><n u="Homicide: Hours To Kill">Homicide: Hours To Kill II (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Peace, Love and Murder
A nationwide manhunt ensues when a yoga teacher is shot to death by someone who turns out to be very close to home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 19:00:00" d="2020-11-04 20:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% End of the Road
It's a race against time for detectives in Tulsa when new evidence casts fresh light on an unsolved murder case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 20:00:00" d="2020-11-04 21:00:00"><n u="New: Fear Thy Neighbour">New: Fear Thy Neighbour V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Head in the Oven
Two neighbouring bachelors start out as friends, but soon their harmless banter grows into all-out war and the ending is horrifying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 21:00:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00"><n u="New: Meet, Marry, Murder">New: Meet, Marry, Murder I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Thomas Infante
Divorce proceedings turned deadly when Lisa Infante began to get her life together following a split from Thomas, as he shot her in their home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 23:00:00"><n u="Norcal Rapist: Very Scary People">Norcal Rapist: Very Scary People I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Norcal Rapist
Phantom Predator (Part One): The story of the serial rapist who managed to evade justice for decades, until he was finally caught out by his DNA</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-04 23:00:00" d="2020-11-05 02:00:00"><n u="Norcal Rapist: Very Scary People">Norcal Rapist: Very Scary People I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Norcal Rapist
Phantom Predator (Part Two): The story of the Norcal Rapist continues, as he finally faces justice after 27 years on the loose</k>  </p>
</a>
