<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-10-30 03:36:18"><p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 05:00:00" d="2020-11-06 06:00:00"><n u="Fear Thy Neighbour">Fear Thy Neighbour V (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Cock-a-Doodle-Dead
A homeowner is feeling hopeful about the renters who move in next door, but his positivity is short-lived when an act of violence threatens lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 06:00:00" d="2020-11-06 06:30:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Killer Nurse
At hospitals in New Jersey and Pennsylvania, patients are mysteriously dying. Then a rumour spreads that a serial killer is at work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 06:30:00" d="2020-11-06 07:00:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Doctor Death
An English doctor who makes house calls has the bedside manner of a saint for his elderly female patients. But the terrifying truth eventually surfaces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 07:00:00" d="2020-11-06 08:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXII (32)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Gangland
A young man is gunned down at a notorious apartment complex that comes under investigation when a rap video goes viral</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 08:00:00" d="2020-11-06 09:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% The Predator
Every hour is crucial for sergeant James Dousay when the discovery of a woman's body suggests a depraved serial killer has struck Harris County</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 09:00:00" d="2020-11-06 10:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sacrificial Lamb
When 13-year-old PJ Grant is found dead from a single gunshot wound to the head, Lt Joe Kenda must determine whether it's suicide or murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 10:00:00" d="2020-11-06 11:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bad Things Come In Threes
Lt Kenda investigates the murder of two young mothers who were gunned down behind a crowded bar. But the case quickly takes a bizarre turn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 11:00:00" d="2020-11-06 12:00:00"><n u="Unusual Suspects">Unusual Suspects IV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maritime Murder
Investigators scrutinise a ship full of suspects when a naval officer is poisoned at sea. Which of the many theories surrounding his death is true?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 12:00:00" d="2020-11-06 12:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (38)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Satanic Homicide
Two dead friends, a shrine to the devil and a slogan written in blood points police to a case of Satan worship. But all may not be as it seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 12:30:00" d="2020-11-06 13:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (39)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Blood on the Ranch
Armed with very few clues, police face an uphill battle to bring 55-year-old jogger Bob Dorotick's killer to justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 13:00:00" d="2020-11-06 14:00:00"><n u="Nightmare In Suburbia">Nightmare In Suburbia II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>For The Love Of Money
When a young mother vanished in Hertfordshire, police suspected she'd run off with a lover. So when they found her body</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 14:00:00" d="2020-11-06 15:00:00"><n u="Crimes That Shook Britain">Crimes That Shook Britain VIII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% Ann Maguire
The tragic story of Ann Maguire, who was stabbed to death by a pupil while teaching a Spanish lesson at Corpus Christi Catholic College in Leeds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 15:00:00" d="2020-11-06 16:00:00"><n u="Meet, Marry, Murder">Meet, Marry, Murder I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Malcolm Webster
The story of a man who murdered his first wife and staged a car crash, attempting to do the same to his second wife - all for life insurance money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 16:00:00" d="2020-11-06 17:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter V (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tighten the Screws
The death of an Iraq War veteran is investigated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 17:00:00" d="2020-11-06 18:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Blood Innocence
When a war hero is beaten to death for no apparent reason, Joe Kenda enlists a team of engineers to help him identify the murder weapon and crack the case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 18:00:00" d="2020-11-06 19:00:00"><n u="Homicide: Hours To Kill">Homicide: Hours To Kill II (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An Eye For An Eye
When a mother is gunned down in her garage, a host of people emerge as suspects. But it's a life insurance policy that lead police to the killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 19:00:00" d="2020-11-06 20:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% The Lost Boys
Detective John Brown races the clock when an innocent grandma is gunned down in Tulsa. Could teenagers be behind her tragic death?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 20:00:00" d="2020-11-06 21:00:00"><n u="New: Fear Thy Neighbour">New: Fear Thy Neighbour V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Roadkill
A single woman and her daughters are happy when a single man and his daughters move in next door - but a molestation charge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 21:00:00" d="2020-11-06 22:00:00"><n u="New: Meet, Marry, Murder">New: Meet, Marry, Murder I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Stephen Searle
He had an affair with his son's partner - the mother of his grandchild - but it was his wife who paid the final price when he was caught out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 22:00:00" d="2020-11-06 22:30:00"><n>Court Cam</n>    <k>Dan Abrams hosts as series two walks you through the most dramatic outbursts and extraordinary moments to ever take place in US courtrooms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 22:30:00" d="2020-11-06 23:00:00"><n>Court Cam</n>    <k>Dan Abrams hosts as series two walks you through the most dramatic outbursts and extraordinary moments to ever take place in US courtrooms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-06 23:00:00" d="2020-11-07 02:00:00"><n u="I Am A Killer">I Am A Killer II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mark Sam Arthur
He got the death sentence at just at 18 and claims he murdered to defend an abused woman - but the courts think he had a more sinister motive</k>  </p>
</a>
