<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-10-23 04:35:04"><p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 05:00:00" d="2020-10-30 06:00:00"><n u="On The Case with Paula Zahn">On The Case with Paula Zahn VIII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>72% New. The East Area Rapist
Paula Zahn investigates the case of a sexual sadist in California, who evaded law enforcement officers for decades</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 06:00:00" d="2020-10-30 06:30:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>South African Strangler
Detectives get to work on a shocking case when a mass grave of women is discovered just outside of Johannesburg, South Africa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 06:30:00" d="2020-10-30 07:00:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Texas Teen Love Triangle
When the body of a beautiful Texas school girl is discovered, rumours buzz around the high school that a killer is walking the halls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 07:00:00" d="2020-10-30 08:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% New. Score to Settle/In Her Arms
A father is killed when a man opens fire in a shop in Atlanta. Meanwhile in Oklahoma, groom-to-be is gunned down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 08:00:00" d="2020-10-30 09:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Deadly Secrets &amp; True Lies
Detectives need a witness to come clean if they're to solve a Minneapolis double murder. In Tulsa, a woman is found dead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 09:00:00" d="2020-10-30 10:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter VI (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Joker in the Pack
A card game is interrupted by gunfire, leaving a young man dead. Elsewhere, lieutenant Joe Kenda responds to a double shooting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 10:00:00" d="2020-10-30 11:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Everybody Lies
Detectives investigate the fatal beating of a deacon in a public park. What was the motive? And could the deeply religious man have harboured a dark side?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 11:00:00" d="2020-10-30 12:00:00"><n u="Unusual Suspects">Unusual Suspects IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Murder On The Menu
Detectives grill a host of suspects when they discover the dumped and dismembered body of a chef. Can forensics confirm his unlikely killer?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 12:00:00" d="2020-10-30 12:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (27)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Secrets Can Kill
When police informant Susan Smith vanishes, her sister points the finger at her mystery boyfriend. As time goes by, it starts to look like she was right</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 12:30:00" d="2020-10-30 13:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (29)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Terrified to Death
Police investigate Robert Spangler who has bad luck when it comes to his wives - they all wind up dead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 13:00:00" d="2020-10-30 14:00:00"><n u="Nightmare In Suburbia">Nightmare In Suburbia V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Babysitter &amp; The Cyber Killer
The tragic story of 19-year-old Katy Briscoe, who was stabbed to death after her killer set up fake Facebook identities to gain her trust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 14:00:00" d="2020-10-30 15:00:00"><n u="What The Killer Did Next">What The Killer Did Next I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bei Carter
Philip Glenister explores the aftermath of Bei Carter's murder in Bridlington. The investigation hinged on the public's sightings after her killer vanished</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 15:00:00" d="2020-10-30 16:00:00"><n u="Buried In The Backyard">Buried In The Backyard II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% He Wasn't Alone
When a teen digs up something gory while doing some yard work, investigators find themselves chasing a wild trail of evidence leading to a shocking truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 16:00:00" d="2020-10-30 17:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter VI (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bring My Baby Home
When newborn girl is kidnapped, lieutenant Joe Kenda fears fear she's been sold on the black market or worse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 17:00:00" d="2020-10-30 18:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Chance Encounter
Detective Joe Kenda tracks down one of Colorado's most notorious serial killers. But if he can't extract a confession, his murderer will walk free</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 18:00:00" d="2020-10-30 19:00:00"><n u="Snapped: Women Who Kill">Snapped: Women Who Kill XIV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Selena
Death Of A Superstar: The 1995 murder of Latin popstar Selena Quintanilla-Pérez shocked the world. This special episode explores her tragic and untimely death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 19:00:00" d="2020-10-30 20:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Last Hope &amp; Truth and Consequences
A teenager's life is cut short in Atlanta. Meanwhile, a young women goes missing in Tulsa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 20:00:00" d="2020-10-30 21:00:00"><n u="On The Case with Paula Zahn">On The Case with Paula Zahn VIII (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>72% Deadly Riddle
After 11-year-old Mary Stiles goes missing, police are sent a sinister series of riddles they must decipher before the killer strikes again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 21:00:00" d="2020-10-30 22:00:00"><n u="Buried In The Backyard">Buried In The Backyard II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Garden of Evil
Investigators dig into the life of a single mother when it emerges that a beautiful garden holds a dark secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 22:00:00" d="2020-10-30 23:00:00"><n u="New: Killer Britain With Dermot Murnaghan">New: Killer Britain With Dermot Murnaghan I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Levi Bellfield
For the final episode in the series, Dermot investigates the serial killer known for the brutal murders of at least three young women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-10-30 23:00:00" d="2020-10-31 02:00:00"><n u="I Am A Killer">I Am A Killer II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Toby Lynn Williams
He took the life of a young mother when his plan to rob her and her family went wrong. But after three decades spent behind bars, is he a changed man?</k>  </p>
</a>
