<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-10-27 03:59:13"><p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 05:00:00" d="2020-11-03 06:00:00"><n u="Fear Thy Neighbour">Fear Thy Neighbour V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Desperate Houseknives
Two families with several children get on great, until relationships begin to sour as one mother starts to get a little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 06:00:00" d="2020-11-03 06:30:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Camden Ripper
When a homeless man found bloody, body parts in a north London dumpster in December 2002, police realised they had a serial killer in the neighbourhood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 06:30:00" d="2020-11-03 07:00:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Texas Tower Sniper
The disturbing story of Charles Whitman, an ex-marine who went on a killing spree at the University of Texas at Austin in 1966</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 07:00:00" d="2020-11-03 08:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Trap House
When a man is murdered just before Christmas, his family helps detectives in Tulsa, Oklahoma, search for his killers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 08:00:00" d="2020-11-03 09:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% New. Bad Lick &amp; Red Dawn
After an Atlanta man is murdered, Detective Egbert suspects he may have been a victim of his own kindness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 09:00:00" d="2020-11-03 10:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Avert Your Eyes
When Pamela Edwards is found shot through the heart, Joe Kenda must shield her young daughters from the horrendous scene before finding the killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 10:00:00" d="2020-11-03 11:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Killer Always Rings Twice
Detective Kenda investigates two murders in the same apartment block. Are they linked? And if so, can he catch the culprit?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 11:00:00" d="2020-11-03 12:00:00"><n u="Unusual Suspects">Unusual Suspects IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Bike Ride To Murder
When the brutalised body of a San Diego girl was found in a canyon in 1991, detectives unearthed a shocking truth that no one could believe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 12:00:00" d="2020-11-03 12:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Luxury, Jealousy And Murder
There must be a murderer on the guest list when a business convention's rich organiser is bludgeoned with a barbell in his room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 12:30:00" d="2020-11-03 13:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (28)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Murder in the Cabin
A multi-millionaire's wife blames a robber when her husband is killed. But then the investigation turns up millions of missing dollars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 13:00:00" d="2020-11-03 14:00:00"><n u="Nightmare In Suburbia">Nightmare In Suburbia I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kidnapped
When 15-year-old Jenna Baldwin went missing, her parents and the police thought she'd run away. Was it teenage rebellion or something much more sinister?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 14:00:00" d="2020-11-03 15:00:00"><n u="What The Killer Did Next">What The Killer Did Next I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Sian Roberts
Police thought Manchester mum Sian Roberts's murder was a cut-and-dried case when they got a frantic 999 call from her ex. They couldn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 15:00:00" d="2020-11-03 16:00:00"><n u="Meet, Marry, Murder">Meet, Marry, Murder I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Kelly Cochran
The story of a woman who carried out the chilling murder of her lover with her husband, before killing her husband too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 16:00:00" d="2020-11-03 17:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Make My Day
The documentary series continues as retired Colorado Springs police detective Joseph Kenda reflects on another harrowing case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 17:00:00" d="2020-11-03 18:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Secret Life
Joe Kenda is stumped for suspects when a woman is found dead in her car. Can he uncover and unravel her mysterious double life in order to find her killer?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 18:00:00" d="2020-11-03 19:00:00"><n u="Homicide: Hours To Kill">Homicide: Hours To Kill II (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Mutant
A mother of eight-year-old triplets is found dead at her home. There are three suspects: her estranged husband, her current boyfriend and a stalker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 19:00:00" d="2020-11-03 20:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% The Standing Ground
A dangerous decision sees a high-school student shot to the ground. But who fired the fatal bullet? Detectives race the clock to unearth the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 20:00:00" d="2020-11-03 21:00:00"><n u="New: Fear Thy Neighbour">New: Fear Thy Neighbour V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Deadly Duplex
A retiree rents out half his duplex to a troubled family and becomes smitten with the wife after sending her abusive husband packing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 21:00:00" d="2020-11-03 22:00:00"><n u="New: Meet, Marry, Murder">New: Meet, Marry, Murder I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Mahmuda Khatun
After just 33 days of marriage, Mahmuda Khatun fatally stabbed her husband in the chest on his 28th birthday. What drove her to commit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 22:00:00" d="2020-11-03 23:00:00"><n u="New: Murdered By Morning">New: Murdered By Morning I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Gambling with Death
A woman is abducted when an evening at the casino turns into a nightmare, and it's not long before a shocking arrest is made</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-11-03 23:00:00" d="2020-11-04 02:00:00"><n>New: The Redemption Project</n>    <k>. ith Van Jones. New. Small Town Reckoning: Van Jones meets Michelle Walter, a teacher who immediately recognises the man who killed her son in a tragic car accident</k>  </p>
</a>
