<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-10-28 03:47:02"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 07:00:00" d="2020-11-04 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 10:00:00" d="2020-11-04 11:00:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 11:00:00" d="2020-11-04 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 13:30:00" d="2020-11-04 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 14:30:00" d="2020-11-04 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 14:55:00" d="2020-11-04 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 15:00:00" d="2020-11-04 16:00:00"><n>New: Judge Rinder's Crime Stories</n>    <k>When young mum Helen Hill's husband didn't come home after a night out, panic set in, but nothing could have prepared her for the truth behind his absence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 16:00:00" d="2020-11-04 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable IV (38)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Legion of Quiz
A team of five quizzers get a chance to win a bumper cash prize by answering a series of Top 10 list questions. Hosted by Warwick Davis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 17:00:00" d="2020-11-04 18:00:00"><n u="New: Tipping Point">New: Tipping Point X (93)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 18:00:00" d="2020-11-04 19:00:00"><n u="New: The Chase">New: The Chase XIV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bradley Walsh is behind Nathan, Victoria, Rich and Pam all the way as they try to beat one of the country's finest quiz brains and take home thousands of pounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 19:00:00" d="2020-11-04 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 19:30:00" d="2020-11-04 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 20:00:00" d="2020-11-04 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Mackenzie watches from the shadows. Paddy discovers Chas is back. Moira makes an olive branch phone call</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 20:30:00" d="2020-11-04 21:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Debbie stirs up hostilities between Tim and Geoff. Dev jumps to a conclusion about Asha. Steve informs Leanne of Emma's blunder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 21:00:00" d="2020-11-04 21:30:00"><n u="New: Heathrow: Britain's Busiest Airport">New: Heathrow: Britain's Busiest Airport VI (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In this last episode of the current series, there's something smelly in Cargo that Border Force have to get to the bottom of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 21:30:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Dev accuses Corey of putting pressure on Asha. Imran instructs Emma to be honest with the police. Faye shares her heartache with Craig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 23:00:00"><n u="New: Don't Rock the Boat">New: Don't Rock the Boat I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>As the celebrities reach Northern Ireland and the Scottish islands, tensions emerge on board as the celebrities face rough waters at sea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-04 23:00:00" d="2020-11-05 02:00:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
</a>
