<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="16" t="2020-10-23 04:35:32"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 06:05:00" d="2020-10-30 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VIII (65)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% Arbitration show in which real small-claims cases are adjudicated over within a studio courtroom by Judge Robert Rinder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 07:00:00" d="2020-10-30 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 10:00:00" d="2020-10-30 11:00:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 11:00:00" d="2020-10-30 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 13:30:00" d="2020-10-30 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 14:30:00" d="2020-10-30 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 14:55:00" d="2020-10-30 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 15:00:00" d="2020-10-30 16:00:00"><n u="New: Judge Rinder">New: Judge Rinder VIII (66)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Arbitration show in which real small-claims cases are adjudicated over within a studio courtroom by Judge Robert Rinder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 16:00:00" d="2020-10-30 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable IV (35)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Baseballers
A baseball team from Newport answer a series of Top 10 list questions. Can they land a Perfect 10 and take home a bumper cash prize? Hosted by Warwick Davis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 17:00:00" d="2020-10-30 18:00:00"><n u="New: Tipping Point">New: Tipping Point X (90)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 18:00:00" d="2020-10-30 19:00:00"><n u="New: The Chase">New: The Chase XIII (200)</n><t>S</t>    <k>All that stands between Ken, Zoe, Keith and Amber and thousands of pounds is the not-so-small matter of one of the country's finest quiz brains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 19:00:00" d="2020-10-30 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 19:30:00" d="2020-10-30 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 20:00:00" d="2020-10-30 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Tracy gets a call from Vanessa. Cain is shocked. Matty worries for Moira</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 20:30:00" d="2020-10-30 21:30:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Scott embroils Emma and Jenny in his crimes. Alya falls into Geoff's trap. Evelyn is perturbed to hear of Arthur's secret hospital visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-30 21:30:00" d="2020-10-31 00:30:00"><n u="Vera">Vera VIII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Home
Quiet life in suburbia takes a dark turn when a woman is found murdered in her garden, and DCI Vera Stanhope discovers that the neighbours aren't all that they seem</k>  </p>
</a>
