<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-10-24 04:33:14"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 07:00:00" d="2020-10-31 07:10:00"><n u="Dino Dana">Dino Dana II (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% The Dino Giver
The adventures of eight-year-old Dana, palaeontologist in training. Dana learns how male dromaeosaurs would give the females gifts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 07:10:00" d="2020-10-31 07:20:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>They Are Among Us
Busy observing the sky in search of UFOs, Magoo accidentally finds himself wandering over to Fizz's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 07:20:00" d="2020-10-31 07:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Halloween Hold-Up
Magoo is out trick-or-treating for Halloween, but he ends up unwittingly robbing a bank</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 07:25:00" d="2020-10-31 07:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ghost Hunt
Fizz has invented a machine which stops toast from landing butter-side down. Magoo sees some floating toast and believes a ghost is haunting their house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 07:35:00" d="2020-10-31 08:00:00"><n u="Thunderbirds Are Go">Thunderbirds Are Go II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Deep Search
Alan makes first contact with an alien lifeform when Thunderbird 3 is called out to a moon of Jupiter to save a pair of documentarians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 08:00:00" d="2020-10-31 08:05:00"><n u="Dare Master at Home">Dare Master at Home I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Baked beans and chopsticks, a bottle top challenge and 30 seconds to get 150 steps on a pedometer. Who will win and who faces a messy forfeit!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 08:05:00" d="2020-10-31 08:15:00"><n u="Mr. Bean: The Animated Series">Mr. Bean: The Animated Series I (38)</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% Scaredy Bean
The animated antics of the hapless bumbler Mr Bean. A trip to the cinema makes Mr Bean's imagination play tricks on him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 08:15:00" d="2020-10-31 08:30:00"><n u="Mr. Bean: The Animated Series">Mr. Bean: The Animated Series II (35)</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% Halloween
Mr Bean loves Halloween and prepares to give the neighbourhood kids some tricks and treats they will not forget</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 08:30:00" d="2020-10-31 08:35:00"><n>Scrambled!</n>    <k>Bitesize TV that fills your morning with a blast of excitement and fun, Scrambled! is the place to go for the best of CITV's current and original shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 08:35:00" d="2020-10-31 08:55:00"><n u="Scrambled! The Tom and Jerry Show">Scrambled! The Tom and Jerry Show IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Werewolf of Catsylvania
There's a new monster in town, and Tom may have met his ultimate match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 08:55:00" d="2020-10-31 09:10:00"><n u="Scrambled! Hotel Transylvania">Scrambled! Hotel Transylvania I (31)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Legend of Pumpkin Guts Part 1
Animated series serving as a prequel to the popular film series. Mavis and her friends learn the true meaning of Halloween</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 09:10:00" d="2020-10-31 09:30:00"><n u="Scrambled! Craig of the Creek">Scrambled! Craig of the Creek I (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Last Kid in the Creek
A terrible curse leaves Craig as the only kid in the creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 09:30:00" d="2020-10-31 10:05:00"><n u="Scrambled! Scooby-Doo and Guess Who? Ollie Ollie In-Come Free!">Scrambled! Scooby-Doo and Guess Who? Ollie Ollie In-Come Free! I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The mystery-solving gang agrees to help Ricky Gervais with a haunted antique Egyptian statue of a cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 10:05:00" d="2020-10-31 10:25:00"><n u="Scrambled! Teen Titans Go!">Scrambled! Teen Titans Go! V (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Monster Squad!
The Titans want to be the scariest trick-or-treaters in town, so Raven casts a spell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 10:25:00" d="2020-10-31 10:30:00"><n>ITV News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 10:30:00" d="2020-10-31 12:40:00"><n u="New: James Martin's Saturday Morning">New: James Martin's Saturday Morning III (42)</n><t>S</t>    <k>James is back in the kitchen on a Saturday morning with his guest, Emily Atack. Chef Dipna Anand will be serving up tandoori lamb chops</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 12:40:00" d="2020-10-31 13:45:00"><n u="New: Ainsley's Food We Love">New: Ainsley's Food We Love I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Special Occasions
Ainsley is inspired by dishes for those special occasions - date nights, anniversaries, dinner parties and festivals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 13:45:00" d="2020-10-31 14:45:00"><n u="James Martin's Great British Adventure">James Martin's Great British Adventure I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Blair Castle
James' culinary tour of Britain continues in Scotland with a trip to Blair Castle where they get an incredible tour of the grounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 14:45:00" d="2020-10-31 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 14:55:00" d="2020-10-31 17:00:00"><n>Zookeeper</n>    <k>Romantic comedy starring Kevin James and Rosario Dawson, 2011. A zookeeper is taught by his animals how to win back his ex-girlfriend after she dumps him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 17:00:00" d="2020-10-31 20:00:00"><n u="Six Nations: Italy v England Live">Six Nations: Italy v England Live V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nearly eight months on from their last game, England complete their disrupted Six Nations campaign against Italy at the Stadio Olimpico in Rome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 20:00:00" d="2020-10-31 20:10:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 20:10:00" d="2020-10-31 20:15:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 20:15:00" d="2020-10-31 21:00:00"><n u="Catchphrase">Catchphrase VI (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hoping to 'Say What They See' and press and guess their way to success are Becky, Roger, and Sharlene who are playing for a massive 50,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 21:00:00" d="2020-10-31 22:00:00"><n u="New: The Chase: Celebrity Special">New: The Chase: Celebrity Special XI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Actress Su Pollard, dancer Jordan Banjo, TV presenter AJ Odudu and TV legend Jonathan Ross take on the challenge hoping to win thousands of pounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 22:00:00" d="2020-10-31 23:00:00"><n u="New: The Voice: The Semi-Finalists">New: The Voice: The Semi-Finalists (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Emma Willis takes us on the journeys of the eight remaining hopefuls, from their first Blind Audition to their Knockout Performance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-10-31 23:00:00" d="2020-11-01 02:00:00"><n u="New: Spitting Image: US Election Special">New: Spitting Image: US Election Special (Part 1)</n>    <k>Puppet-based sketch show that skewers the politicians and celebrities who need it the most. This episode is the first part of a US election special</k>  </p>
</a>
