<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-10-30 03:31:59"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 06:05:00" d="2020-11-06 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VIII (66)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% Arbitration show in which real small-claims cases are adjudicated over within a studio courtroom by Judge Robert Rinder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 07:00:00" d="2020-11-06 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 10:00:00" d="2020-11-06 11:00:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 11:00:00" d="2020-11-06 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 13:30:00" d="2020-11-06 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 14:30:00" d="2020-11-06 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 14:55:00" d="2020-11-06 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 15:00:00" d="2020-11-06 16:00:00"><n>New: Judge Rinder's Crime Stories</n>    <k>Ground-breaking forensic technology is used to track down the killer of an 87-year-old woman who was brutally murdered in her own home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 16:00:00" d="2020-11-06 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable IV (40)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Herd Mentality
A team of 5 family and friends team up to take on the Tenable Tower. Will they be victorious and head home with a tasty cash prize? Hosted by Warwick Davis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 17:00:00" d="2020-11-06 18:00:00"><n u="New: Tipping Point">New: Tipping Point X (95)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 18:00:00" d="2020-11-06 19:00:00"><n u="New: The Chase">New: The Chase XIII (166)</n><t>S</t>    <k>All that stands between Andrew, Mali, Ben, Rosie and thousands of pounds is the not so small matter of one of the country's finest quiz brains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 19:00:00" d="2020-11-06 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 19:30:00" d="2020-11-06 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 20:00:00" d="2020-11-06 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Chas is upset Paddy stayed out. Gabby worries. Nate gets a worrying call</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 20:30:00" d="2020-11-06 21:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Simon seizes an opportunity to help Leanne's cause. Sally's plans give Abi cause for concern. Michael pays a visit to Grace in prison</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 21:00:00" d="2020-11-06 21:30:00"><n>Britain's Best Walks with Julia Bradbury</n>    <k>Countryside Walk: Sandstone Trail, Cheshire: Julia Bradbury travels through the rolling plains of Cheshire on a walk for dog-walkers and sports folk alike. Ep4/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 21:30:00" d="2020-11-06 22:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Debbie advises Sally on the sale of her house. Dev decides to listen to the twins' wishes. Sean vows to change his life to make Dylan proud</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 22:00:00" d="2020-11-06 23:00:00"><n u="New: Don't Rock the Boat">New: Don't Rock the Boat I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>As their epic journey to row the length of Britain comes to an end, the celebrity crews all have one final race to determine who gets to row to glory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-06 23:00:00" d="2020-11-07 02:00:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
</a>
