<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-10-27 04:04:29"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 05:15:00" d="2020-11-03 06:05:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 06:05:00" d="2020-11-03 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VII (117)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% James is in court to claim rent arrears from a former tenant, while Plum is in court to claim for the costs incurred replacing a phone her friend damaged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 07:00:00" d="2020-11-03 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 10:00:00" d="2020-11-03 11:00:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 11:00:00" d="2020-11-03 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 13:30:00" d="2020-11-03 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 14:30:00" d="2020-11-03 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 14:55:00" d="2020-11-03 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 15:00:00" d="2020-11-03 16:00:00"><n>New: Judge Rinder's Crime Stories</n>    <k>A woman's life is in the balance after she escapes years of coercive control and domestic abuse. And the tragic case of Thomas Edwards, who was killed in a hit and run</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 16:00:00" d="2020-11-03 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable IV (37)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Study Buddies
A team of university friends join forces to take on the Tenable tower. Have they got what it takes to win a cash prize? Hosted by Warwick Davis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 17:00:00" d="2020-11-03 18:00:00"><n u="New: Tipping Point">New: Tipping Point X (92)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 18:00:00" d="2020-11-03 19:00:00"><n u="New: The Chase">New: The Chase XIII (167)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Four people who have never met before - Rozie, Annie, Kaan and Paul - become a team in the hope of taking home thousands of pounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 19:00:00" d="2020-11-03 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 19:30:00" d="2020-11-03 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 20:00:00" d="2020-11-03 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Cain and Sam plan revenge on Jamie. Charity starts to spiral out of control. Rhona reminds Moira that she's there if she needs her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 20:30:00" d="2020-11-03 21:15:00"><n u="Catchphrase">Catchphrase VI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Joining host Stephen Mulhern and Mr Chips are Pete, Suzy, and Dan. They'll be trying to 'Say What They See' as one of them could be saying hello</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 21:15:00" d="2020-11-03 22:15:00"><n u="Who Wants To Be A Millionaire? Host Jeremy Clarkson offers six more contestants the chance to win one million pounds">Who Wants To Be A Millionaire? Host Jeremy Clarkson offers six more contestants the chance to win one million pounds XXXIII (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Four lifelines can help them along the way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-11-03 22:15:00" d="2020-11-04 01:15:00"><n u="New: Don't Rock the Boat">New: Don't Rock the Boat I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The celebrities tackle wild Welsh water as they row up the coast of Wales. Former politician Tom Watson confronts his fear of heights as he tackles a 130ft</k>  </p>
</a>
