<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="40" t="2020-10-30 03:37:05"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 05:15:00" d="2020-11-06 05:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory III (22)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Staircase Implementation: This episode flashes back to the start of Sheldon and Leonard's friendship seven years earlier and explains the roommate agreement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 05:40:00" d="2020-11-06 06:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory III (23)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Lunar Excitation: Raj registers Sheldon for online dating and finds the perfect match: the female version of Sheldon. Penny seduces Leonard while she's drunk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 06:05:00" d="2020-11-06 06:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Bus Pants Utilization: Leonard's idea for a smartphone application derails his friendship with Sheldon as they fight for control of the project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 06:30:00" d="2020-11-06 07:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Love Car Displacement: Tensions are high when Bernadette runs into her hulk of an ex-boyfriend at a science conference, leaving Howard feeling threatened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 07:00:00" d="2020-11-06 08:00:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In rural New Jersey, Gordon Ramsay visits Flamangos, where mother and daughter Adele and Cheryl are stuck in their tropical ways. But their restaurant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 08:00:00" d="2020-11-06 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Doll's Story: Despite Hilda and Zelda's warnings, Sabrina seizes the opportunity to earn 100 dollars by babysitting her bratty cousin, Amanda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 08:30:00" d="2020-11-06 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Sabrina, the Teenage Boy: Fed up with Harvey for spending all his time with his friends, Sabrina persuades her aunts to teach her about the mysteries of men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 09:00:00" d="2020-11-06 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Hooked: Ted is humiliated when he sees a woman he's dating on another date on the night they were supposed to meet. Marshall is charmed by a man who is smitten with Lily</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 09:30:00" d="2020-11-06 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Say Cheese: Lily is annoyed with Ted for inviting his new date Amanda to her birthday dinner, complaining about the run of short-lived girlfriends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 10:00:00" d="2020-11-06 10:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>S-h--Shipping: JJ is under pressure to date a new student. Maya and Jimmy want Ray and Taylor to be more carefree. Dylan rebels against a no-prank initiative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 10:30:00" d="2020-11-06 11:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>B-r-i--British I-n-v--Invasion: Maya's regal mother pays a visit at Thanksgiving and the family struggle to impress her. Kenneth's overbearing father arrives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 11:00:00" d="2020-11-06 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Thespian Catalyst: Sheldon lectures at the university but worries that the students don't seem to like him. Raj fantasises about his best friend's girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 11:30:00" d="2020-11-06 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Benefactor Factor: A wealthy benefactor at the university makes Leonard consider how far he's willing to go in the name of science</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 12:00:00" d="2020-11-06 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Parents Thursday: At school, Erica tries to fool Beverly into thinking that parents weekend has been rescheduled. Adam joins the school production of Romeo &amp; Juliet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 12:30:00" d="2020-11-06 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A 100% True Ghost Story: After discovering The Rocky Horror Picture Show, Barry resolves to throw a Halloween party for the ages - no matter what Erica says</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 13:00:00" d="2020-11-06 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Puzzle Master: Peralta and Santiago investigate arson attacks connected to a crossword puzzle author. Gina helps Holt with his Commissioner presentation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 13:30:00" d="2020-11-06 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Nutriboom: Peralta and Boyle realise that they have been fooled into joining a cult-like pyramid scheme and they struggle to terminate their contracts with it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 14:00:00" d="2020-11-06 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Fortification Implementation: When Sheldon and Amy build a blanket fort, they come to a major crossroads in their relationship. Howard meets his half-brother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 14:30:00" d="2020-11-06 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Communication Deterioration: Raj is asked to create a message for Nasa to use if one of their missions finds alien life. Penny considers taking up acting again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 15:00:00" d="2020-11-06 15:30:00"><n u="Scrubs">Scrubs II (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>His Story: Everything has started going well for JD, so Dr Cox gets a chance to air his own grievances about his relationship with his psychiatrist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 15:30:00" d="2020-11-06 16:00:00"><n u="Scrubs">Scrubs II (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>My Karma: Elliot tries to maintain a façade with her new man, Jordan tells JD who the father of her baby is, and JD and Turk worry that their golfing caused a car crash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 16:00:00" d="2020-11-06 16:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>One A-n--Angry M--Maya: Maya must do jury service at the same time as Taylor's mother. JJ is less than truthful in his profile on an online dating website</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 16:30:00" d="2020-11-06 17:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>A-c--Action!: JJ is chosen to film a horror movie project, but the pressure of directing becomes too much. Dylan's class assignment reveals a family secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 17:00:00" d="2020-11-06 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Tattler: Peralta and Gina attend their 20-year high school reunion. Boyle helps Diaz with a decision. A radio show mystery sound contest baffles the guys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 17:30:00" d="2020-11-06 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Four Movements: Gina plays a game of chess with Captain Holt, goes out for lunch with Diaz and Santiago and infiltrates an expensive social club with Peralta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 18:00:00" d="2020-11-06 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Dave Kim's Party: With Dave Kim's parents out of town for the weekend, Adam decides to throw a giant party to impress Brea. Ep15)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 18:30:00" d="2020-11-06 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Body Swap: Adam is thrilled about William Penn's new open lunch policy. And Geoff gets more than he bargained for when he uses Barry's student ID. Ep16)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 19:00:00" d="2020-11-06 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Helium Insufficiency: Sheldon and Leonard struggle to find the supplies they need for an experiment. Penny and Bernadette download a dating app for Amy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 19:30:00" d="2020-11-06 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Spock Resonance: While he's being interviewed for a documentary about Star Trek character Mr Spock, Sheldon can't suppress his emotions about his split from Amy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 20:00:00" d="2020-11-06 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks Favourites</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Hollyoaks Friday Favourites
A classic episode from 2005. Can Mandy win back Tony after breaking his heart? Jack is furious when some money goes missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 20:30:00" d="2020-11-06 21:00:00"><n u="Schooled">Schooled II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>48% Outbreak: When a bad flu epidemic hits, Coach Mellor is sent to his sick bed and Principal Glascott must step it up as the wrestling coach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 21:00:00" d="2020-11-06 22:00:00"><n u="Taskmaster">Taskmaster III (4)</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>Comedy game show. In the penultimate episode of the series, can the comedians impress Greg Davies by giving an item of clothing to a passing cyclist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 22:00:00" d="2020-11-07 00:20:00"><n>Spy</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy action-thriller starring Melissa McCarthy. A CIA intelligence officer abandons her desk job to track down a stolen nuclear weapon. Very strong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-07 00:20:00" d="2020-11-07 00:55:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Robotic Manipulation: Penny tags along to Sheldon's first date with a woman he's been texting for months. Howard finds a new use for a robotic arm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-07 00:55:00" d="2020-11-07 01:20:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Cruciferous Vegetable Amplification: Sheldon realises that he won't live long enough to download his consciousness into a robot body, so he tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-07 01:20:00" d="2020-11-07 02:25:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction I</n><e>R</e>    <k>DJ Darryl is used to seeing women all dressed up in clubs. Will stripping everything back help? And Ania is looking for a mate who won't disappoint</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-07 02:25:00" d="2020-11-07 02:55:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty III (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>92% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Vindicators 3: The Return of Worldender: Rick and Morty are summoned by superhero team the Vindicators to thwart the plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-07 02:55:00" d="2020-11-07 03:50:00"><n u="Angel">Angel II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Happy Anniversary: The Host asks for Angel's help when one of Caritas's patrons sings a song that signals the end of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-07 03:50:00" d="2020-11-07 04:45:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates XII</n>    <k>Italian restaurant owner Giovanni, who's 61, sets out to give Fred Sirieix a run for his money on the charm front. And can Jason see past prison officer Tyrone's ADHD? Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-07 04:45:00" d="2020-11-07 05:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Thespian Catalyst: Sheldon lectures at the university but worries that the students don't seem to like him. Raj fantasises about his best friend's girlfriend</k>  </p>
</a>
