<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="41" t="2020-10-27 04:00:26"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 05:15:00" d="2020-11-03 05:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Irish Pub Formulation: A visit from Raj's sister Priya creates tension among the guys, especially when Leonard asks Sheldon to conceal his romantic past with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 05:40:00" d="2020-11-03 06:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Apology Insufficiency: Leonard thinks his dating problems are due to a lack of confidence and vows to be self-assured around attractive females</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 06:05:00" d="2020-11-03 06:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Bagpipes: Barney mistakenly thinks that Marshall and Lily are heading for divorce and offers his help. Ted unearths some home truths for Robin and Barney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 06:30:00" d="2020-11-03 07:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% The Playbook: Barney reverts back to his bachelor ways when he and Robin break up and he is soon on the prowl looking for new women, but Lily objects to his behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 07:00:00" d="2020-11-03 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sienna must choose between her past and her future, while Liberty and Warren take action after Sienna and Brody's deceit. Romeo throws Tom a surprise stag do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 07:30:00" d="2020-11-03 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>R</e>    <k>Verity is lost for words when she sees Diane's new look and knows that Edward is behind the drastic change. Tom and Yazz have very different ideas about their wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 08:00:00" d="2020-11-03 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch I (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Crucible: Sabrina's class takes a field trip to historical Salem where each student is assigned a role to play. Most of the students are given the role of townsperson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 08:30:00" d="2020-11-03 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Troll Bride: Sabrina panics when she and Harvey are voted 'cutest couple'. According to Libby, every couple previously given the award broke up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 09:00:00" d="2020-11-03 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% Slapsgiving 2: Revenge of the Slap: When Lily's dad shows up unannounced at Thanksgiving, she reveals the real reason she stopped speaking to him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 09:30:00" d="2020-11-03 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% The Window: Ted's friends try to help him woo the perfect woman from his college days, but Barney and Robin spoil his big chance. Will he still get his girl?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 10:00:00" d="2020-11-03 10:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless I (23)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>C-a--Camp: As the family prepares for their flight to JJ's summer camp, Maya receives a shock at the airport. Ray spies an opportunity to reinvent himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 10:30:00" d="2020-11-03 11:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>W-e--We're B-a--Back!: Maya, Jimmy and Dylan make dramatic changes in their lives. When JJ comes home from summer camp, Dylan finds a love note in his bag</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 11:00:00" d="2020-11-03 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The 21-Second Excitation: The gang's plans to attend a film screening are scuppered by Sheldon's nemesis Wil Wheaton. Penny and Bernadette invite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 11:30:00" d="2020-11-03 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Boyfriend Complexity: When Penny's father comes to visit, Leonard discovers her parents still think that he and Penny are a couple, so he takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 12:00:00" d="2020-11-03 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI</n><e>R</e>    <k>Mom Trumps Willow: Adam decides to see the movie Willow instead of spending Mother's Day with Beverly. Barry tires of his status as the family's middle child. Ep22)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 12:30:00" d="2020-11-03 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI (23)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Breakin': Adam reveals that Barry never completed his community service requirement. Erica plans for her and Geoff to follow The Grateful Dead all summer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 13:00:00" d="2020-11-03 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% 99: While the squad attend a funeral in Los Angeles, Holt hears he is in the running for his dream job: NYPD Commissioner. Boyle pries into Diaz's personal life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 13:30:00" d="2020-11-03 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Game Night: Diaz begs Peralta to help her break some big news to her parents, but her plan's thrown off track when Mr and Mrs Diaz jump to the wrong conclusion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 14:00:00" d="2020-11-03 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Troll Manifestation: Leonard and Sheldon co-publish a physics paper but are forced to defend themselves against negative comments from an online critic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 14:30:00" d="2020-11-03 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (15)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Comic Book Store Regeneration: The gang prepare for the reopening of Stuart's comic book shop. Penny teaches Sheldon to 'let it go' when he is irritated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 15:00:00" d="2020-11-03 15:30:00"><n u="Scrubs">Scrubs II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>My Lucky Day: As if having to move out of her flat after being cut off by her father wasn't bad enough, Elliot faces a malpractice suit from a patient</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 15:30:00" d="2020-11-03 16:00:00"><n u="Scrubs">Scrubs II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>My Monster: Carla is concerned that Turk isn't as romantic as he used to be, Dr Cox lets his pregnant ex-wife stay with him, and Elliot agrees to move in with JD and Turk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 16:00:00" d="2020-11-03 16:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>S-i--Silent N-i--Night: After putting JJ under pressure to get a new dog, Dylan takes a vow of silence to better understand what it's like to be her brother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 16:30:00" d="2020-11-03 17:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>N-e--New Y--Year's E--Eve: Jimmy convinces Maya to go on a night out together on New Year's Eve, but they struggle with Maya's urge to rush home to the kids</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 17:00:00" d="2020-11-03 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (19)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Bachelor/ette Party: Boyle organises an elaborate scavenger hunt for Peralta's bachelor party, but the guys take short cuts that throw the event into disarray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 17:30:00" d="2020-11-03 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (20)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Show Me Going: The squad worry about Diaz when she responds to an active shooter alert, but they are told to remain at the precinct building and can't help her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 18:00:00" d="2020-11-03 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Beverly Goldberg Cookbook: Part 2: When a publisher shows interest in her recipes, Beverly prepares to finally realise her dream of writing a cookbook. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 18:30:00" d="2020-11-03 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>It's a Wonderful Life: When Beverly signs everyone up for a holiday family photo, Geoff is excited to join in - despite Erica's reservations. Ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 19:00:00" d="2020-11-03 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (24)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Commitment Determination: Sheldon pressures Leonard and Penny to choose a date for their wedding while dealing with changes in his own relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 19:30:00" d="2020-11-03 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Matrimonial Momentum: Penny struggles with Leonard's confession that he kissed another woman. Sheldon doesn't know how to act when Amy breaks up with him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 20:00:00" d="2020-11-03 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n>    <k>Theresa and John Paul team up to beat the McQueens' blackmailer, and John Paul is shocked when he thinks that he's uncovered their identity. The Maaliks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 20:30:00" d="2020-11-03 21:00:00"><n u="Schooled">Schooled II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>48% I'll Be There For You: Lainey has high hopes for Coach Mellor's love life, and Principal Glascott isn't sure how to handle difficult librarian Dr Ness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 21:00:00" d="2020-11-03 22:00:00"><n u="Taskmaster">Taskmaster III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Comedy game show. Greg Davies and Alex Horne host as Al Murray, Dave Gorman, Paul Chowdhry, Rob Beckett and Sara Pascoe encounter out-of-season snowmen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-03 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 00:00:00"><n>Keeping Up with the Joneses</n>    <k>Action comedy with Zach Galifianakis, Isla Fisher, Jon Hamm and Gal Gadot. A couple discover that their new neighbours are spies. Violent scenes/no</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 00:00:00" d="2020-11-04 01:00:00"><n u="Buffy the Vampire Slayer">Buffy the Vampire Slayer II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>When She Was Bad: Buffy returns from summer vacation sporting a 'major attitude' and suffers recurring nightmares involving the Master</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 01:00:00" d="2020-11-04 02:00:00"><n u="Angel">Angel II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Reunion: The newly reunited and deadly duo of Darla and Drusilla embark on a murderous rampage across the city. A frantic Angel attempts to stop them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 02:00:00" d="2020-11-04 02:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory III (18)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Pants Alternative: Sheldon has been awarded a prestigious prize but is scared of collecting the award at a ceremony because he knows he'll have to make a speech</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 02:30:00" d="2020-11-04 03:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory III (19)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Wheaton Recurrence: Leonard tells Penny that he loves her. The gang go bowling and find that Sheldon's enemy, Wil Wheaton, is playing in the opposing team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 03:00:00" d="2020-11-04 03:30:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty III (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>92% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
The Rickshank Rickdemption: Still in galactic prison, Rick puts an intricate escape plan into action. Back on Earth, Morty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 03:30:00" d="2020-11-04 04:25:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XIII</n><e>R</e>    <k>Britain's sharpest armchair critics react to Sex Tape, Britain's Got Talent, Line of Duty, This Morning, The All New Monty: Who Bares Wins, The Yorkshire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 04:25:00" d="2020-11-04 05:20:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates IX</n><e>R</e>    <k>Bina, who runs a bridal business, hopes to find a man who's husband material. And will adventurer Stephen run a mile when he finds out</k>  </p>
</a>
