<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="46" t="2020-10-29 03:45:52"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 05:15:00" d="2020-11-05 05:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Alien Parasite Hypothesis: Amy finds that she has romantic feelings for Zack, while Raj and Howard compete to prove who would make the better superhero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 05:40:00" d="2020-11-05 06:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (11)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Justice League Recombination: The guys slowly warm to Zack and find an enjoyable way to bond with him when they enter a New Year's Eve fancy dress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 06:05:00" d="2020-11-05 06:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% Girls vs Suits: Ted meets attractive PhD student Cindy, who is tired of men falling in love with her roommate. Will Ted fall for her instead?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 06:30:00" d="2020-11-05 07:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% Jenkins: Marshall tells Ted a series of anecdotes about his colleague, who is called Jenkins. Later on, Ted is surprised to discover that Jenkins is a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 07:00:00" d="2020-11-05 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>R</e>    <k>Theresa fears that it's her turn to be exposed by the McQueens' blackmailer. Edward tries to buy Verity's silence. James and Sami do some digging on Kurt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 07:30:00" d="2020-11-05 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>R</e>    <k>Theresa and John Paul team up to beat the McQueens' blackmailer, and John Paul is shocked when he thinks that he's uncovered their identity. The Maaliks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 08:00:00" d="2020-11-05 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dummy for Love: Sabrina argues with vice principal Kraft when she writes a piece for the school paper stressing the importance of education over sports</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 08:30:00" d="2020-11-05 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dante's Inferno: To Sabrina's dismay, Harvey's dad decides that his son should date other people - and Hilda and Zelda agree that she should do the same</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 09:00:00" d="2020-11-05 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% The Perfect Week: Barney reaches a milestone, Lily and Marshall realise they've been using the same toothbrush, Robin waits to hear from a date, and Ted insults a student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 09:30:00" d="2020-11-05 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (15)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% Rabbit or Duck: Barney holds his phone number up during the Super Bowl broadcast and is inundated with phone calls from women. Lily and Marshall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 10:00:00" d="2020-11-05 10:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>T-r--Training D-a--Day: Jimmy takes JJ camping to give him 'the talk'. Maya attempts to train a ragtag group of aides for some new students at the school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 10:30:00" d="2020-11-05 11:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (18)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new - N-i--Nightmares on D-i--DiMeo S-Street: The DiMeo kids mistakenly eat some very old Halloween sweets that give them feverish dreams of horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 11:00:00" d="2020-11-05 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Bus Pants Utilization: Leonard's idea for a smartphone application derails his friendship with Sheldon as they fight for control of the project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 11:30:00" d="2020-11-05 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Love Car Displacement: Tensions are high when Bernadette runs into her hulk of an ex-boyfriend at a science conference, leaving Howard feeling threatened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 12:00:00" d="2020-11-05 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Food in a Geoffy: Murray and Geoff have to run around Jenkintown looking for an important cheese steak after a food delivery job goes sideways</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 12:30:00" d="2020-11-05 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Animal House: While Barry's love of Animal House fails to impress an elite fraternity, Beverly tries to convince Murray to take up new hobbies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 13:00:00" d="2020-11-05 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Negotiation: Peralta negotiates a hostage situation with a jewel thief whose face is familiar. Santiago and Gina aid Boyle with his new food truck business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 13:30:00" d="2020-11-05 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Box: Captain Holt sacrifices an evening at the opera to help Peralta carry out an interrogation in the hope of getting a confession from a stubborn suspect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 14:00:00" d="2020-11-05 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (18)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Leftover Thermalization: A power cut at Mrs Wolowitz's house defrosts the last meal she prepared before her death, so the gang consume it in her honour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 14:30:00" d="2020-11-05 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (19)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Skywalker Incursion: When Leonard and Sheldon are invited to speak at Berkeley, they take a detour during the journey to try to meet one of their idols</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 15:00:00" d="2020-11-05 15:30:00"><n u="Scrubs">Scrubs II (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>My Philosophy: JD philosophises about death with a patient who's awaiting a heart transplant, and Elliot campaigns for Dr Kelso to allow the female staff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 15:30:00" d="2020-11-05 16:00:00"><n u="Scrubs">Scrubs II (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>My Brother, My Keeper: JD is assigned to work with Dr Kelso's friend Dr Townshend (guest star Dick Van Dyke), whose old-school methods soon cause problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 16:00:00" d="2020-11-05 16:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>E-i--Eighteen: JJ struggles with not being treated like an adult on his 18th birthday. Ray tries to make Taylor jealous with some of his father's old moves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 16:30:00" d="2020-11-05 17:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>U-n--Unforgettable P-a--Pain: Ray is miserable after breaking up with Taylor. JJ is nervous about socialising with Aaron. Kenneth tells Jimmy to take charge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 17:00:00" d="2020-11-05 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Honeymoon: Peralta and Santiago see a familiar face on their honeymoon. Gina and Boyle get into a family squabble. Jeffords must live up to his new nickname</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 17:30:00" d="2020-11-05 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Hitchcock &amp; Scully: Peralta and Boyle revisit an old case of Hitchcock and Scully's from the 1980s. Limited resources at the precinct building cause tension</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 18:00:00" d="2020-11-05 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Geoff the Pleaser: Geoff struggles to balance demands from the Jenkintown Posse and Erica. Adam faces a crisis of confidence over his career path. Ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 18:30:00" d="2020-11-05 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Preventa Mode: As Valentine's Day approaches, Barry is shocked when an attractive teaching assistant agrees to go out with him. Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 19:00:00" d="2020-11-05 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The 2003 Approximation: Sheldon sulks when Penny and Leonard announce that they're moving in together. Howard and Raj form a band to play at the comic book shop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 19:30:00" d="2020-11-05 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Perspiration Implementation: The guys take fencing lessons from Barry Kripke. Stuart struggles to attract female customers to the comic book shop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 20:00:00" d="2020-11-05 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n>    <k>John Paul reaches new lows to come up with the cash for the McQueens' blackmailer. Can Juliet throw Jordan off the scent of who grassed him up?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 20:30:00" d="2020-11-05 21:00:00"><n u="Schooled">Schooled II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>48% Kick Like a Girl: Hoping to improve the football team's prospects, Mellor and Glascott recruit star soccer player Felicia to kick field goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 21:00:00" d="2020-11-05 22:00:00"><n u="Taskmaster">Taskmaster III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Comedy game show. Al Murray goes to extreme lengths to maximise his point potential with an egg cup. Sara Pascoe swiftly becomes one of the greatest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 22:00:00" d="2020-11-05 22:35:00"><n u="The Inbetweeners">The Inbetweeners II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Duke of Edinburgh Awards: Will is asked to co-ordinate the school's Duke of Edinburgh Award scheme and immediately turns the situation to his own advantage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 22:35:00" d="2020-11-05 23:05:00"><n u="The Inbetweeners">The Inbetweeners II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>End of Term: Will is stressed about exams, Jay has other things on his mind, Simon finally seems to be making headway with Carli, and Neil forgets his kit for his PE exam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 23:05:00" d="2020-11-06 00:05:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction V (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Trans-woman Amira finally feels happy in her skin and seeks a man who's proud to show her off. Rugby player Andy has a soft centre to share with a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 00:05:00" d="2020-11-06 01:05:00"><n u="Buffy the Vampire Slayer">Buffy the Vampire Slayer II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>School Hard: Buffy's mother and friends become trapped inside Sunnydale High School when a vampire named Spike launches an attack against the Slayer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 01:05:00" d="2020-11-06 02:00:00"><n u="Angel">Angel II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Blood Money: Angel investigates Wolfram &amp; Hart's suspicious involvement in a fundraiser for a local teen shelter. Wes, Gunn and Cordelia establish their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 02:00:00" d="2020-11-06 02:30:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty IV</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Promortyus: Rick and Morty find themselves in a fight against face-hugging aliens who just happen to have an M&amp;Ms store. Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 02:30:00" d="2020-11-06 03:00:00"><n u="Primal">Primal [adult swim]</n>    <k>Spear and Fang: Award-winning animation set in a savage prehistoric world. Brought together by tragedy, caveman Spear and dinosaur Fang form an unlikely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 03:00:00" d="2020-11-06 03:15:00"><n u="The Jellies!">The Jellies! II</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Jellies! [adult swim]
Walla Walla Civil War: A small dispute leads to a big-ass war in Walla Walla Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 03:15:00" d="2020-11-06 03:30:00"><n u="The Jellies!">The Jellies! II</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Jellies! [adult swim]
My Friend Sheldon Jr.: The gang realise that there's something strange about Cornell's friend. Ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 03:30:00" d="2020-11-06 03:55:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty III (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>92% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Pickle Rick: Rick turns himself into a pickle in one of his crazy experiments, while Beth, Summer and Morty attend family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 03:55:00" d="2020-11-06 04:20:00"><n u="The Inbetweeners">The Inbetweeners II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Duke of Edinburgh Awards: Will is asked to co-ordinate the school's Duke of Edinburgh Award scheme and immediately turns the situation to his own advantage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 04:20:00" d="2020-11-06 04:50:00"><n u="Friday Night Dinner">Friday Night Dinner II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>80% Adam isn't happy when Jonny claims to have dislocated his shoulder to get out of cleaning the loft. Mum and Dad aren't on speaking terms and Aunty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-06 04:50:00" d="2020-11-06 05:15:00"><n u="Friday Night Dinner">Friday Night Dinner II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>80% Jim makes a cake to celebrate his dog Wilson's birthday, and the family return from a spin in Jonny's new but uncool company car to find something</k>  </p>
</a>
