<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="42" t="2020-10-28 03:44:29"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 05:20:00" d="2020-11-04 05:45:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The 21-Second Excitation: The gang's plans to attend a film screening are scuppered by Sheldon's nemesis Wil Wheaton. Penny and Bernadette invite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 05:45:00" d="2020-11-04 06:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Boyfriend Complexity: When Penny's father comes to visit, Leonard discovers her parents still think that he and Penny are a couple, so he takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 06:10:00" d="2020-11-04 06:35:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% Slapsgiving 2: Revenge of the Slap: When Lily's dad shows up unannounced at Thanksgiving, she reveals the real reason she stopped speaking to him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 06:35:00" d="2020-11-04 07:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% The Window: Ted's friends try to help him woo the perfect woman from his college days, but Barney and Robin spoil his big chance. Will he still get his girl?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 07:00:00" d="2020-11-04 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>R</e>    <k>Verity is lost for words when she sees Diane's new look and knows that Edward is behind the drastic change. Tom and Yazz have very different ideas about their wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 07:30:00" d="2020-11-04 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>R</e>    <k>Theresa fears that it's her turn to be exposed by the McQueens' blackmailer. Edward tries to buy Verity's silence. James and Sami do some digging on Kurt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 08:00:00" d="2020-11-04 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sabrina Gets Her License (Part One): Things are looking good for Sabrina. At 17, she and Harvey are still going strong and she's managing her powers better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 08:30:00" d="2020-11-04 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sabrina Gets Her License (Part Two): After failing at her first attempt to gain her witch's licence, Sabrina is sent to a witch camp for some military-style training</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 09:00:00" d="2020-11-04 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% Girls vs Suits: Ted meets attractive PhD student Cindy, who is tired of men falling in love with her roommate. Will Ted fall for her instead?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 09:30:00" d="2020-11-04 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother V (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% Jenkins: Marshall tells Ted a series of anecdotes about his colleague, who is called Jenkins. Later on, Ted is surprised to discover that Jenkins is a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 10:00:00" d="2020-11-04 10:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>F-i--First S-e--Second F--First Day: When new students with disabilities start at the school, Maya urges their parents to demand full-time aides like Kenneth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 10:30:00" d="2020-11-04 11:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>J-J's D-r--Dream: Ray gets in over his head when he makes up a fake charity to impress his girlfriend. Maya gives newly promoted Jimmy tips on being the boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 11:00:00" d="2020-11-04 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Alien Parasite Hypothesis: Amy finds that she has romantic feelings for Zack, while Raj and Howard compete to prove who would make the better superhero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 11:30:00" d="2020-11-04 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (11)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Justice League Recombination: The guys slowly warm to Zack and find an enjoyable way to bond with him when they enter a New Year's Eve fancy dress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 12:00:00" d="2020-11-04 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Vacation: Beverly marshals everyone for one last family vacation to Disneyland. Erica worries that Geoff wants to break up. Guest starring Christie Brinkley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 12:30:00" d="2020-11-04 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Dana's Back: Adam gets a blast from the past in the shape of Dana - his first love. Meanwhile, Erica and Barry are heading to college with nowhere to live</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 13:00:00" d="2020-11-04 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (11)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Favor: Mobster Seamus Murphy returns to redeem the favour Holt owes him for helping to get Diaz and Peralta out of jail, so the team search for a loophole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 13:30:00" d="2020-11-04 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Safe House: After mobster Seamus Murphy threatens Kevin, Captain Holt devises an elaborate plan to hide his husband in a safe house, with Peralta as his guard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 14:00:00" d="2020-11-04 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (16)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Intimacy Acceleration: When the gang hear about an experiment designed to make participants fall in love, Sheldon and Penny put it to the test as a joke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 14:30:00" d="2020-11-04 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (17)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Colonization Application: Amy learns that Sheldon has applied to take part in a one-way mission to colonise Mars. Leonard surprises Penny with a gift</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 15:00:00" d="2020-11-04 15:30:00"><n u="Scrubs">Scrubs II (11)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>My Sex Buddy: The young doctors' relationships get complicated when JD and Elliot become 'sex buddies'. Turk tries to lighten Elliot's workload but ends up annoying her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 15:30:00" d="2020-11-04 16:00:00"><n u="Scrubs">Scrubs II (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>My New Old Friend: JD can't handle just being friends with Elliot, and Dr Cox and Carla fail to read each other's signals while treating a hypochondriac patient</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 16:00:00" d="2020-11-04 16:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (11)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The H-u-s--Hustle: Maya and Jimmy get dragged into a school fundraiser at which Maya makes a new friend. Ray explores his reckless side with JJ and Dylan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 16:30:00" d="2020-11-04 17:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>D-i--DiMeo A-c--Academy: After a dust-up about JJ's graduation with his teachers, Maya comes to her son's rescue and launches her own school from their home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 17:00:00" d="2020-11-04 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (21)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% White Whale: Diaz and Santiago team up to take down a ruthless killer who has managed to elude them for seven years. Jeffords helps Peralta with wedding chores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 17:30:00" d="2020-11-04 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (22)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Jake &amp; Amy: The precinct squad rush to save Peralta and Santiago's wedding day from a major threat. Captain Holt receives an email containing important news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 18:00:00" d="2020-11-04 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III</n><e>R</e>    <k>Pickleball: Under pressure to beef up his CV, Adam tries out for William Penn's pickleball team. Beverly's determined to give Murray an epic birthday bash. Ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 18:30:00" d="2020-11-04 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Game Night: When he connects with the most popular girl in school, Adam turns to the cool new guidance counsellor for advice. Ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 19:00:00" d="2020-11-04 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Separation Oscillation: Sheldon films a special post-break-up episode of Fun with Flags. Bernadette feels guilty about withholding a secret from Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 19:30:00" d="2020-11-04 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Bachelor Party Corrosion: The guys' science skills are tested when they get a flat tyre during Leonard's surprise bachelor party weekend in Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 20:00:00" d="2020-11-04 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n>    <k>Juliet's new-found confidence impresses Peri, but will Jordan ruin Juliet's chances? The McQueens' torment continues. Nancy's thoughts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 20:30:00" d="2020-11-04 21:00:00"><n u="Schooled">Schooled II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>48% The Rudy-ing of Toby Murphy: After watching the classic film Rudy in C.B.'s class, a student wants to play football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 21:00:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00"><n u="Taskmaster">Taskmaster III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Comedy game show. Greg Davies sets our five comics more tenuous tasks. Who can give Alex Horne the biggest surprise when he emerges from his shed after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 23:00:00"><n u="Celebrity Gogglebox">Celebrity Gogglebox II</n><e>R</e>    <k>What do Britain's best-loved famous faces think of Bake Off: The Professionals, Ramsay's 24 Hours to Hell and Back, Celebrity MasterChef, The Supervet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-04 23:00:00" d="2020-11-05 00:00:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XV</n><e>R</e>    <k>Up for review are Netflix's The Stranger and Love Is Blind; BBC's EastEnders and Spy in the Wild; C4's Crazy Delicious and Hunted; ITV News on Harry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 00:00:00" d="2020-11-05 01:00:00"><n u="Buffy the Vampire Slayer">Buffy the Vampire Slayer II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Some Assembly Required: Two science club nerds use body parts to create the 'perfect girlfriend' for a teenager who has been brought back from the dead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 01:00:00" d="2020-11-05 02:00:00"><n u="Angel">Angel II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Redefinition: After firing Wesley, Cordelia and Gunn, Angel trains for a showdown with Darla and Drusilla. Meanwhile, the fired trio try to figure out what to do next</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 02:00:00" d="2020-11-05 02:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory III (20)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Spaghetti Catalyst: Sheldon hides his friendship with Penny from Leonard, but it isn't long before his double life is exposed. Can he remain friends with both of them?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 02:30:00" d="2020-11-05 03:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory III (21)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Plimpton Stimulation: When Sheldon meets a famous physicist online, he invites her over to the apartment, where she spends her time flirting with Leonard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 03:00:00" d="2020-11-05 03:25:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty III (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>92% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Rickmancing the Stone: Rick takes Morty and Summer on a jaunt to a Mad Max-style universe where he tries to steal a green</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 03:25:00" d="2020-11-05 04:20:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XIII</n><e>R</e>    <k>What do the Goggleboxers think of Ninja Warrior UK, BGT, Hostile Planet, Game of Thrones, Years and Years, Bear's Mission with David Walliams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-11-05 04:20:00" d="2020-11-05 05:15:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates XII</n>    <k>The dating hopefuls include a builder who's finally ready for a concrete relationship, a naked bike rider, a pair of gamers, and a man who's been married</k>  </p>
</a>
