<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2020-10-28 03:47:35"><p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-04 05:00:00" d="2020-11-04 06:30:00"><n>Arena presented by Tractor Supply, The</n>    <k>Thought-provoking conversations, interviews, and stories on the NBA, social justice, and other impactful off-court topics. Featuring Cari Champion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-04 06:30:00" d="2020-11-04 08:00:00"><n>Arena presented by Tractor Supply, The</n>    <k>Thought-provoking conversations, interviews, and stories on the NBA, social justice, and other impactful off-court topics. Featuring Cari Champion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-04 08:00:00" d="2020-11-04 10:00:00"><n>Mr. Russell's House</n>    <k>NBA legend Bill Russell chats with Bill Simmons about growing up and playing for the Celtics during the Civil Rights era. Also covered are Russell's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-04 10:00:00" d="2020-11-04 12:00:00"><n>Game 1: Paul Pierce's dramatic return to court highlights Celtics' win</n>    <k>Celtics F Paul Pierce injured his knee in the middle of the Game 1, but made a dramatic return to lead the Celtics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-04 12:00:00" d="2020-11-04 14:00:00"><n>Game 3: Kobe Bryant pours in 36 to help Lakers secure needed win</n>    <k>Kobe Bryant scored 36 points with an MVP-worthy performance, Sasha Vujacic added 20 points and the Lakers, teetering on the brink of falling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-04 14:00:00" d="2020-11-04 16:00:00"><n>Game 4: Celtics' historic comeback leaves Lakers stunned</n>    <k>The Lakers sprinted out to a 35-14 lead at the end of the 1st Quarter, but the Celtics made an equally impressive run to tie the game as it went down to the wire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-04 16:00:00" d="2020-11-04 18:00:00"><n>Game 6: Celtics finish off Lakers for 17th NBA championship</n>    <k>The Celtics dominated in Game 6 of the Finals, giving Kevin Garnett, Ray Allen, and Paul Pierce their first NBA Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-04 18:00:00" d="2020-11-04 20:00:00"><n>Clippers/Warriors, 11/4</n>    <k>Stephen Curry scored 31 points, including the go-ahead 3-pointer with just over a minute to go that led the defending champion Warriors to their fifth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-04 20:00:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00"><n>Game 1: Kevin Durant dominates in Finals debut as the Thunder go up 1-0</n>    <k>Down by 7 points at halftime, Kevin Durant scores 17 points in the fourth quarter and the Thunder beat the Heat in Game 1</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-05 00:00:00"><n>2012: Mvp Kevin Durant Staves off East Rally With 36 Points</n>    <k>Thunder F Kevin Durant led the West with 36 points and was named MVP in Orlando</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-05 00:00:00" d="2020-11-05 02:00:00"><n>Warriors/Thunder, 1/17/2014</n>    <k>Kevin Durant scored a career-high 54 points to lead the Thunder past the Warriors. Steph Curry and Klay Thompson combined for 12 three-pointers but could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-05 02:00:00" d="2020-11-05 04:00:00"><n>Warriors/Thunder, 2/11</n>    <k>After a roller-coaster of emotions surrounding his return to Oklahoma City, Kevin Durant was glad to come out with a win and move on. Durant scored</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-05 04:00:00" d="2020-11-05 06:00:00"><n>Game 5: Kevin Durant's 39 points caps MVP performance as Warriors claim title</n>    <k>Kevin Durant capped his spectacular first season with the Warriors by bringing home a NBA championship, scoring 39 points in a fast-and-furious</k>  </p>
</a>
