<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2020-10-30 03:40:36"><p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 05:00:00" d="2020-11-06 07:00:00"><n u="Rockets/Celtics, 1986 NBA Finals - Game">Rockets/Celtics, 1986 NBA Finals - Game 6</n>    <k>Larry Bird and the Celtics close out the Houston Rockets for Boston's 16th NBA Championship. Kevin McHale pours in 29 points and grabs 10 rebounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 07:00:00" d="2020-11-06 07:30:00"><n u="NB80's: Volume">NB80's: Volume 1</n>    <k>The intense rivalry between Magic Johnson and Larry Bird takes center stage, while the NBA introduces the 3-point shot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 07:30:00" d="2020-11-06 08:00:00"><n u="NB80's: Volume">NB80's: Volume 2</n>    <k>The Los Angeles Lakers become known as &quot;Showtime&quot; and Moses Malone reaches the Promised Land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 08:00:00" d="2020-11-06 08:30:00"><n u="NB80's: Volume">NB80's: Volume 3</n>    <k>The 1984 NBA Draft introduces some NBA Legends, the Celtics and Lakers battle for supremacy, and All-Star Weekend welcomes the Slam Dunk Contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 08:30:00" d="2020-11-06 09:00:00"><n u="NB80's: Volume">NB80's: Volume 4</n>    <k>While Larry Bird and Magic Johnson continue to battle for league and MVP titles, Spud Webb secures a spot in All-Star history, and Dr. J says goodbye</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 09:00:00" d="2020-11-06 09:30:00"><n u="NB80's: Volume">NB80's: Volume 5</n>    <k>As the Lakers complete back-to-back title victories, the Pistons are on the verge of dominance, and Michael &quot;Air&quot; Jordan delivers a &quot;Shot&quot; to remember</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 09:30:00" d="2020-11-06 10:00:00"><n>Audio Toon: The TV Show</n>    <k>Highlights from Inside the NBA with Shaq, Charles Barkley, Kenny Smith and Ernie Johnson animated by Cartoon Network!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 10:00:00" d="2020-11-06 12:00:00"><n>Film Room: Celtics/Pistons, 1987 Eastern Conference Finals - Game 7 with Mahorn, McHale and Isiah</n>    <k>Kevin McHale and Isiah Thomas relive and discuss Game 7 of the 1987 Eastern Conference Finals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 12:00:00" d="2020-11-06 14:00:00"><n>Game 3: Dwyane Wade scores 42 to inspire Heat's impressive comeback</n>    <k>Dwyane Wade scored a playoff career-high 42 points and singlehandedly fueled a series-saving comeback as the Heat rallied for a 98-96 victory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 14:00:00" d="2020-11-06 16:00:00"><n>Game 6: Dwyane Wade pilots the Heat past the Mavericks for their first NBA title</n>    <k>Dwyane Wade scores 36 points to lead the Miami Heat to their first NBA Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 16:00:00" d="2020-11-06 18:00:00"><n>Heat/Pacers, 11/6</n>    <k>Paul George had 36 points and 12 rebounds to lead the Indiana Pacers to a 90-87 victory. He got going early and performed down the stretch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 18:00:00" d="2020-11-06 20:00:00"><n>Celtics/Hawks, 11/6</n>    <k>Kyrie Irving scored 35 points, Jayson Tatum added 21 and the Boston Celtics held off the Atlanta Hawks 110-107 for their ninth straight victory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 20:00:00" d="2020-11-06 22:00:00"><n>Mavericks/Spurs, 2006 Western Conference Semifinals - Game 7 - Popcast</n>    <k>Added pop up facts throughout the game in which Tim Duncan led all scorers with 41 points but it wasn't enough to overcome Dirk Nowitzki, 37 points</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-06 22:00:00" d="2020-11-07 00:00:00"><n>Thunder/Mavericks, 2011 NBA Western Conference Finals - Game 1 - Popcast</n>    <k>Added pop up facts throughout the game in which Dirk Nowitzki hit 10 of his first 11 shots from the field and an NBA playoff-record 24 straight free throws</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-07 00:00:00" d="2020-11-07 01:00:00"><n>Basketball Stories: A Decade to Remember</n>    <k>Hosted by Matt Winer, Basketball Stories: A Decade to Remember lets you relive some of the greatest NBA Moments spanning across the 2010's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-07 01:00:00" d="2020-11-07 03:00:00"><n>Game 2: Dirk Nowitzki inspires improbable fourth-quarter comeback</n>    <k>Mavericks F Dirk Nowitzki led Dallas back from 15 points down in the 4th quarter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2020-11-07 03:00:00" d="2020-11-07 05:00:00"><n>Game 6: Dirk Nowitzki carries Mavericks to first-ever NBA title</n>    <k>Mavericks G Jason Terry stepped up with 27 points to lead Dallas to their first Championship</k>  </p>
</a>
