<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-10-24 04:43:22"><p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-31 06:40:00" d="2020-10-31 08:15:00" c="1"><n u="Mulan">Mulan II</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% The wedding of Chinese warrior-maiden Mulan is put on hold when the Emperor sends her on a secret mission. Epic family animation featuring the voice of Lucy Liu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-31 08:15:00" d="2020-10-31 10:05:00" c="1"><n>The Pacifier</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% When disgraced Navy SEAL Vin Diesel is assigned to guard five kids in quiet suburbia, family life could prove his hardest mission yet. Family comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-31 10:05:00" d="2020-10-31 11:45:00" c="1"><n>Atlantis: The Lost Empire</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% A young enthusiast joins a deep sea mission to uncover the secrets of the legendary sunken city of Atlantis. Animation with the voice of Michael J Fox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-31 11:45:00" d="2020-10-31 13:45:00" c="1"><n>Maleficent: Mistress Of Evil</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Loyalties are tested as Maleficent embarks on an epic battle against Aurora's future mother-in-law. Fantasy sequel starring Angelina Jolie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-31 13:45:00" d="2020-10-31 15:35:00" c="1"><n u="Frozen">Frozen 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Anna, Elsa and the gang leave Arendelle to travel to an ancient forest of an enchanted land. Animated sequel with Kristen Bell and Idina Menzel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-31 15:35:00" d="2020-10-31 17:05:00" c="1"><n>Brother Bear</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% A troubled youngster is transformed into a bear to teach him a priceless lesson about brotherhood. Disney animation with the voice of Joaquin Phoenix</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-31 17:05:00" d="2020-10-31 18:35:00" c="1"><n>Fantasia</n><t>F</t>    <k>A modern update of the iconic Disney animation featuring visual interpretations of the great works of classical music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-31 18:35:00" d="2020-10-31 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Dinosaur</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% When a meteor hits earth, an orphaned dinosaur and the pack of lemurs who raised him embark upon an epic trek to safety. Animated adventure from Disney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-31 20:00:00" d="2020-10-31 22:00:00" c="1"><n u="Frozen">Frozen 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Anna, Elsa and the gang leave Arendelle to travel to an ancient forest of an enchanted land. Animated sequel with Kristen Bell and Idina Menzel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-31 22:00:00" d="2020-11-01 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Maleficent: Mistress Of Evil</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Loyalties are tested as Maleficent embarks on an epic battle against Aurora's future mother-in-law. Fantasy sequel starring Angelina Jolie</k>  </p>
</a>
