<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-10-27 04:08:22"><p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-03 05:30:00" d="2020-11-03 07:15:00" c="1"><n>Meet The Robinsons</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% An orphaned boy genius learns a priceless lesson about family when he is whisked into the future by a time-travelling teen. Thrilling animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-03 07:15:00" d="2020-11-03 09:00:00" c="1"><n>The Haunted Mansion</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Eddie Murphy and his family try to escape a ghostly house in this spooky family comedy. Co-starring Terence Stamp and Jennifer Tilly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-03 09:00:00" d="2020-11-03 10:50:00" c="1"><n>Finding Nemo</n><t>F</t>    <k>82% A clownfish scours the ocean for his son, who has been caught and put in a dentist's aquarium. Pixar adventure with the voice of Ellen DeGeneres</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-03 10:50:00" d="2020-11-03 12:20:00" c="1"><n>Pocahontas II: Journey To A New World</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% In this sequel to the Disney animation, Pocahontas finds romance as she travels to London to stop the English waging war on her people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-03 12:20:00" d="2020-11-03 14:20:00" c="1"><n u="Frozen">Frozen 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Anna, Elsa and the gang leave Arendelle to travel to an ancient forest of an enchanted land. Animated sequel with Kristen Bell and Idina Menzel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-03 14:20:00" d="2020-11-03 16:10:00" c="1"><n>Atlantis: The Lost Empire</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% A young enthusiast joins a deep sea mission to uncover the secrets of the legendary sunken city of Atlantis. Animation with the voice of Michael J Fox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-03 16:10:00" d="2020-11-03 18:10:00" c="1"><n>The Lion King</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Donald Glover, Seth Rogen and Beyoncé voice the Oscar-nominated remake of the Disney classic about a young lion prince hoping to follow in his father's footsteps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-03 18:10:00" d="2020-11-03 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Finding Nemo</n><t>F</t>    <k>82% A clownfish scours the ocean for his son, who has been caught and put in a dentist's aquarium. Pixar adventure with the voice of Ellen DeGeneres</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-03 20:00:00" d="2020-11-03 21:50:00" c="1"><n u="Frozen">Frozen 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Anna, Elsa and the gang leave Arendelle to travel to an ancient forest of an enchanted land. Animated sequel with Kristen Bell and Idina Menzel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-03 21:50:00" d="2020-11-04 00:50:00" c="1"><n>Underdog</n><t>F</t>    <k>50% Sniffer dog Shoeshine turns superhero after a lab accident, but the mad scientist behind it will stop at nothing to steal back the puppy's powers. Family</k>  </p>
</a>
