<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-10-23 04:46:56"><p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-30 06:00:00" d="2020-10-30 07:40:00" c="1"><n>Homeward Bound: The Incredible Journey</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Three pets left behind by their holidaying owners go on an epic trek to find their masters. Animal adventure with the voices of Sally Field and Michael J Fox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-30 07:40:00" d="2020-10-30 09:15:00" c="1"><n u="Mulan">Mulan II</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% The wedding of Chinese warrior-maiden Mulan is put on hold when the Emperor sends her on a secret mission. Epic family animation featuring the voice of Lucy Liu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-30 09:15:00" d="2020-10-30 11:10:00" c="1"><n u="Toy Story">Toy Story 4</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Woody and the gang are back for a fourth film in the iconic franchise. When a new toy joins the room, a wild road trip begins with friends old and new</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-30 11:10:00" d="2020-10-30 13:20:00" c="1"><n>Aladdin</n><t>F</t>    <k>Live-action re-imagining of the Disney classic about a street urchin who unleashes the power of a genie (Will Smith), sparking a magical adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-30 13:20:00" d="2020-10-30 15:10:00" c="1"><n>Muppet Treasure Island</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Kermit and pals give this classic pirate yarn a Muppet-style makeover. Swashbuckling family adventure starring Tim Curry, Billy Connolly and Jennifer Saunders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-30 15:10:00" d="2020-10-30 17:15:00" c="1"><n>Eight Below</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A team of huskies fight to survive in the Arctic when a storm separates them from their owners. Family drama inspired by a true story, with Paul Walker and Jason Biggs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-30 17:15:00" d="2020-10-30 19:00:00" c="1"><n u="Toy Story">Toy Story 4</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Woody and the gang are back for a fourth film in the iconic franchise. When a new toy joins the room, a wild road trip begins with friends old and new</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-30 19:00:00" d="2020-10-30 21:10:00" c="1"><n>Aladdin</n><t>F</t>    <k>Live-action re-imagining of the Disney classic about a street urchin who unleashes the power of a genie (Will Smith), sparking a magical adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-30 21:10:00" d="2020-10-30 23:10:00" c="1"><n>The Sorcerer's Apprentice</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Sorcerer Nicolas Cage recruits a reluctant Jay Baruchel to be his apprentice, as he battles to defeat evil wizard Alfred Molina. Fantasy adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-10-30 23:10:00" d="2020-10-31 02:10:00" c="1"><n>The Pacifier</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% When disgraced Navy SEAL Vin Diesel is assigned to guard five kids in quiet suburbia, family life could prove his hardest mission yet. Family comedy</k>  </p>
</a>
