<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-10-30 03:42:32"><p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-06 06:15:00" d="2020-11-06 07:45:00" c="1"><n>The Little Mermaid: Ariel's Beginning</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Ariel's father bans music in their underwater kingdom, so the young mermaid tries to find a way to secretly express her love of song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-06 07:45:00" d="2020-11-06 09:45:00" c="1"><n>Dumbo</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Dumbo the elephant takes to the skies again in Tim Burton's live action remake of the 1941 Disney classic. Colin Farrell, Eva Green, Danny DeVito and Michael Keaton star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-06 09:45:00" d="2020-11-06 11:20:00" c="1"><n>The Haunted Mansion</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Eddie Murphy and his family try to escape a ghostly house in this spooky family comedy. Co-starring Terence Stamp and Jennifer Tilly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-06 11:20:00" d="2020-11-06 13:10:00" c="1"><n u="Toy Story">Toy Story 4</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Woody and the gang are back for a fourth film in the iconic franchise. When a new toy joins the room, a wild road trip begins with friends old and new</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-06 13:10:00" d="2020-11-06 15:10:00" c="1"><n>The Lion King</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Donald Glover, Seth Rogen and Beyoncé voice the Oscar-nominated remake of the Disney classic about a young lion prince hoping to follow in his father's footsteps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-06 15:10:00" d="2020-11-06 16:40:00" c="1"><n>Tarzan</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Disney animation about the jungle-dwelling man torn between the ape family that raised him and the human adventurers who could take him home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-06 16:40:00" d="2020-11-06 18:00:00" c="1"><n u="Tarzan">Tarzan II</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Animated adventure following a young Tarzan as he ventures into the jungle on a voyage of self-discovery. With the voices of Glenn Close and George Carlin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-06 18:00:00" d="2020-11-06 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Dumbo</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Dumbo the elephant takes to the skies again in Tim Burton's live action remake of the 1941 Disney classic. Colin Farrell, Eva Green, Danny DeVito and Michael Keaton star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-06 20:00:00" d="2020-11-06 21:45:00" c="1"><n u="Toy Story">Toy Story 4</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Woody and the gang are back for a fourth film in the iconic franchise. When a new toy joins the room, a wild road trip begins with friends old and new</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-11-06 21:45:00" d="2020-11-07 00:45:00" c="1"><n>Homeward Bound II: Lost In San Francisco</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Family adventure about three pets who embark on a series of hair-raising escapades in San Francisco. With the voices of Michael J Fox and Sally Field</k>  </p>
</a>
