<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-10-23 04:34:35"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 05:10:00" d="2020-10-30 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Reality star and retired model Adrianne Curry and her boyfriend, Todd, are living with Adrianne’s menacing Siamese cat, Billy Shears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 06:00:00" d="2020-10-30 07:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet: Coast To Coast</n><t>D</t>    <k>73% Dr. Alex needs to find out what is wrong with a dog struggling from the heatwave. A pregnant guinea pig is being watched closely and Dr. Kate helps a baby wombat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 07:00:00" d="2020-10-30 07:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts try to answer some of nature’s strangest mysteries like, can fish really predict when an earthquake is coming? And, why are eggs shaped like that?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 07:30:00" d="2020-10-30 08:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why do dogs bury bones? Can elephants detect bombs? Why do birds sing in the morning? Plus, what makes seahorses almost indestructible?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 08:00:00" d="2020-10-30 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lizzy and Elise struggle to rescue a stray dog found on the train tracks. Plus, a woman falls in love with a Labrador, but her current dog isn’t so welcoming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 09:00:00" d="2020-10-30 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When a dog with three legs isn’t adopted, Amanda Giese comes to New Orleans to help. Plus, parolee Troy shares some life-changing news with Tia and the team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 10:00:00" d="2020-10-30 11:00:00"><n>The Bronx Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>A look at daily life in the Bronx Zoo, documenting the day-to-day operations that provide quality care for animals whilst educating the public on wildlife and conservation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 11:00:00" d="2020-10-30 12:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>73% Dr Chris treats Tigger the dog - who was hit by a car, Tim makes a surprise discovery in one family’s walls, and young boxer dog is struggling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 12:00:00" d="2020-10-30 13:00:00"><n>Great White Appetite</n><t>D</t>    <k>Remarkably, scientists have no accurate data on the great white's population, mating or even feeding behaviour. Can new information shed light on these</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 13:00:00" d="2020-10-30 14:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Mike and Patricia love their cats, but unfortunately their cats do not love each other. Patricia, a ghost hunter, thinks there is a supernatural reason why</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 14:00:00" d="2020-10-30 14:30:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animals can do extraordinary things – but how do they do it? Experts spill the secrets of the animal kingdom with amazing footage and surprising facts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 14:30:00" d="2020-10-30 15:00:00"><n>Meet The Orangutans</n><t>D</t>    <k>There’s a baby boom at the sanctuary as new arrivals mix with news of more on the way. The dominant male known as C.I.D is thought to be father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 15:00:00" d="2020-10-30 16:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>After 25 years in a tiny clinic, the team is moving to a new clinic with twice the space. When Dr. Jeff repairs a dog's knee, he makes a special connection with her owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 16:00:00" d="2020-10-30 17:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff heads out to a wild animal sanctuary to help an injured tiger. Meanwhile, Dr. Amy tackles exploratory surgery on a cat with a strange appetite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 17:00:00" d="2020-10-30 18:00:00"><n>The Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>Zoo staff face unexpected setbacks weaning a bright sea lion pup off her mother's milk. And, the bird team steps in to support a rejected curassow chick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 18:00:00" d="2020-10-30 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>73% Dr Chris treats a tiny dog with a big growth on her leg. Plus, Tim attempts to get a world-famous crocodile out of the water to look at his injured foot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 19:00:00" d="2020-10-30 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal Cop investigators always hope for a full recovery with all their rescues. The team re-visit dramatic cases to see how the animals are progressing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 20:00:00" d="2020-10-30 21:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mariah looks for a homeless woman needing to give up her beloved pit bull. Lizzy prepares her favourite rescue for a home after dealing with his medical issues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 21:00:00" d="2020-10-30 22:00:00"><n>Isle Of Jaws: Blood Brothers</n><t>D</t>    <k>A team of shark explorers ventures to the Isle of Jaws off the West Australian coast to find out if two great white sharks recognise, and prefer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 22:00:00" d="2020-10-30 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigator Barbara Christensen leads the team as they pursue a horse cruelty case with a difference. But will she catch the culprit?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-30 23:00:00" d="2020-10-31 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia and M2 are preparing a pit bull for her forever home, but the adoption takes an unexpected turn. Plus, a new parolee comes to Villalobos from Boston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 00:00:00" d="2020-10-31 01:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia comes to the rescue of five injured dogs who have been used for fighting. Plus, parolee Spencer is released from jail and returns to Villalobos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 01:00:00" d="2020-10-31 02:00:00"><n>After The Attack</n><t>D</t>    <k>A paraglider who was attacked by a wedge-tailed eagle and a man who was nearly drowned by a saltwater crocodile recount their experiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 02:00:00" d="2020-10-31 03:00:00"><n>Isle Of Jaws: Blood Brothers</n><t>D</t>    <k>A team of shark explorers ventures to the Isle of Jaws off the West Australian coast to find out if two great white sharks recognise, and prefer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 03:00:00" d="2020-10-31 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigator Barbara Christensen leads the team as they pursue a horse cruelty case with a difference. But will she catch the culprit?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 03:50:00" d="2020-10-31 04:40:00"><n>Miami Animal Police</n><t>D</t>    <k>An officer deals with two rampant pit bulls head on. A stray mum and her pups won't come out from under a shed and a case of horse neglect warrants a jail term</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 04:40:00" d="2020-10-31 06:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why do domestic cats find it so hard to get down from trees, and how have two jungle cats evolved? Plus, why do kiwi birds lay monster-sized eggs compared to their size?</k>  </p>
</a>
