<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-10-28 03:39:46"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 05:10:00" d="2020-11-04 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Maryam is a pet psychic, but she can't communicate with her vicious cat Lily. Plus, Khloe discovers an entire feral colony behind her parent's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 06:00:00" d="2020-11-04 07:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>A micro-pig with an injured leg requires surgery, but anaesthesia could be deadly. Later, a French bulldog’s routine dental exam becomes a complex operation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 07:00:00" d="2020-11-04 07:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts explain footage of a humpback whale holding a diver hostage. Plus, how could a colony of 1.5 million animals hide from the world in plain sight?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 07:30:00" d="2020-11-04 08:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animals can do extraordinary things – but how do they do it? Experts spill the secrets of the animal kingdom with amazing footage and surprising facts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 08:00:00" d="2020-11-04 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tania struggles to rescue a puppy hiding under a shed. A potential adopter seeks a companion for her dog, and a beloved employee learns he's finally off parole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 09:00:00" d="2020-11-04 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mariah and Spencer rescue a dog with severe injuries. Plus, a parolee gets arrested and a couple hope to find a friend for their bulldog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 10:00:00" d="2020-11-04 11:00:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>The staff use laser-equipped cameras to determine just how long Trixie the whale shark is. Plus, a shy box turtle makes friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 11:00:00" d="2020-11-04 12:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet: Coast To Coast</n><t>D</t>    <k>73% Dr. Kate discovers dachshund Gary has a life-threatening condition. Dr. Alex is under pressure to deliver 12 puppies, and Dr. Peter performs surgery on a lion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 12:00:00" d="2020-11-04 13:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A woman travels from San Diego to offer one of Villalobos' senior dogs a home. Meanwhile, Lizzy and Marcel search for a mama dog's lost puppies out in the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 13:00:00" d="2020-11-04 14:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jackson works with a cat, Skylar, who's literally afraid of her own tail. Plus, Jackson meets up with a pair of guardians whose cat is constantly knocking things over</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 14:00:00" d="2020-11-04 15:00:00"><n u="Dogs">Dogs 101</n><t>D</t>    <k>A dog encyclopaedia, with the Australian Cattle Dog, Saluki, Norwich Terrier, Boykin Spaniel, Wonder Dog, Bull Terrier, and Cardigan Welsh Corgi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 15:00:00" d="2020-11-04 16:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Jeff and the team are on a time limit to treat an English bulldog who swallowed a rock. Plus, Hector gets a workout from some puppies in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 16:00:00" d="2020-11-04 17:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Jeff fights to fix a German shepherd's broken elbow for his war veteran owner, and a cat with a swollen bladder needs difficult surgery to save its life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 17:00:00" d="2020-11-04 18:00:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>After devouring all his tankmate’s food, a hungry sea turtle finds a space to eat in peace. Plus, two beluga whales are welcomed to their new home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 18:00:00" d="2020-11-04 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet: Coast To Coast</n><t>D</t>    <k>73% Dr. Danni helps her friend’s cat that keeps fighting with its neighbour. Meanwhile, Dr. Peter struggles to get close to Lottie the ferocious and frightened Chihuahua</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 19:00:00" d="2020-11-04 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>It’s a busy day for investigator Trischa Price as she seizes three starving horses, before saving some trapped kittens and helping three abandoned puppies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 20:00:00" d="2020-11-04 21:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Raneys try to restore a failed homestead in Ohio. Marty's only hope is an old gas well, which if he can get working, can breathe life back into the property</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 21:00:00" d="2020-11-04 21:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts examine footage of crows leaving gifts in Seattle. Plus, could a shark really be older than America? And, what is making crop circles in the sea?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 21:30:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why would goats risk their lives to climb an almost vertical wall? Plus, what happens when a zebra has no stripes? Experts explain this and more!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators move in to seize over 200 dogs from an overcrowded puppy mill and an abandoned dog wins the heart of Investigator Scott Wernick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-04 23:00:00" d="2020-11-05 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia takes in a pit bull that was rescued from awful conditions in Kuwait. Meanwhile, when a stray dog arrives at Villalobos, Earl is determined to find the owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 00:00:00" d="2020-11-05 01:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When an aggressive dog is in danger of being put down, Tia heads to South Carolina to save him. Plus, parolee Toney Converse takes on more responsibility</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 01:00:00" d="2020-11-05 02:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Raneys try to restore a failed homestead in Ohio. Marty's only hope is an old gas well, which if he can get working, can breathe life back into the property</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 02:00:00" d="2020-11-05 03:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Sandy and Phil were happily married until they adopted their cat Woody. The couple is convinced that Woody is evil enough to kill their other cat, Pirate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 03:00:00" d="2020-11-05 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators move in to seize over 200 dogs from an overcrowded puppy mill and an abandoned dog wins the heart of Investigator Scott Wernick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 03:50:00" d="2020-11-05 04:40:00"><n>Miami Animal Police</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cruelty Investigator Dierdra 'Buffy' Jorgensen helps out on a case of animal breeding gone bad and ends up saving the lives of many animals, including a Dachshund puppy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 04:40:00" d="2020-11-05 05:10:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>How do koalas keep cool in the Australian sun? How do elephants communicate when they are miles apart? Experts answer these questions!</k>  </p>
</a>
