<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2020-10-25 03:36:24"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 05:10:00" d="2020-11-01 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Peggy is a ‘Real Housewife of Orange County’. Being a housewife, she's used to catfights, except she's now dealing with one involving her real cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 06:00:00" d="2020-11-01 07:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% The minute Dexter entered the house he was out to kill Daisy. Meanwhile, Corey got Giver for Sarah’s birthday, but this is one gift he’d like to give back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 07:00:00" d="2020-11-01 08:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Parents Greg and Dina have three loving children and one vicious cat named Mia. Plus, the only thing keeping Chris and Tenille from moving in together is her hostile cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 08:00:00" d="2020-11-01 09:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Andy loves girlfriend Alyssa, but hates her ‘demon cat’, Tosh, who turned after he moved in with her. Eric and Kaotar's problem cat, Vincent, tries anything to escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 09:00:00" d="2020-11-01 10:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jackson heads on the road to solve more feline issues. A cat called Godzilla is not as fearsome as she appears, and is terrified of the other cat in the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 10:00:00" d="2020-11-01 11:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>George and Beth are prisoners in their own home due to their vicious kitty Reese. Reese is a cat version of Jack the Ripper and Beth is one of his choice targets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 11:00:00" d="2020-11-01 12:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Alan and Shannon wanted a cat to cuddle, but instead they got Barnabas - a hissing, flesh ripping cat. The only thing that calms him down is opera music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 12:00:00" d="2020-11-01 13:00:00"><n>Modern Dinosaurs</n><t>D</t>    <k>A dive beneath the waves in search of the mysterious creatures of New Zealand’s oceans, from the southern fjords to the Kaikoura coast and the Milford Sound</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 13:00:00" d="2020-11-01 14:00:00"><n>Cold Blooded Peruvian Predator: Expedition Mungo</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mungo heads to Peru in a bid to capture on camera the legendary yacumama – a super-snake so feared by local villagers that they have tried to blow it up with dynamite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 14:00:00" d="2020-11-01 15:00:00"><n>Swimming With Monsters: Steve Backshall</n><t>D</t>    <k>Steve travels to the Pantanal in Brazil to swim with and study the monstrous anacondas that inhabit this region. But could his presence in the water trigger an attack?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 15:00:00" d="2020-11-01 16:00:00"><n>Jeremy Wade's Dark Waters</n><t>D</t>    <k>Fisherman and adventurer, Jeremy Wade, travels to Lake Garda in northern Italy to investigate a 16th century monster fish. What secrets is the lake hiding?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 16:00:00" d="2020-11-01 17:00:00"><n>SERIES Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>The dedicated team continue their work through the chaos of the COVID-19 pandemic. A dog has been hit by a car and a puppy is suspected of eating DVDs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 17:00:00" d="2020-11-01 18:00:00"><n>Saved By The Barn</n><t>D</t>    <k>A cow called Buttercup comes to the barn, but the team is concerned about her feisty behaviour. And, Ginger the lamb battles a life-threatening infection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 18:00:00" d="2020-11-01 18:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>73% Foster Mum Melissa takes puppy Tyson to Chris for a routine check-up and is confronted with terrible news. Tyson needs major heart surgery or he will die</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 18:30:00" d="2020-11-01 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>73% When two Tasmanian devil babies are close to death after getting a mystery illness, Chris rushes to help. And will a miniature schnauzer survive a deadly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 19:00:00" d="2020-11-01 20:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Raneys attempt to save a single mother and her daughter from a rampant moose, Marty builds a bridge across a creek and Matt teaches predator deterrent techniques</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 20:00:00" d="2020-11-01 21:00:00"><n>Guardians Of The Glades</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dusty and the team must capture a giant calf-eating snake and venture into an abandoned factory to save upper Florida from invasive pythons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 21:00:00" d="2020-11-01 22:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia races to rescue four dogs from a rural shelter in Louisiana from euthanasia. Plus, Mariah and Toney give a scared, shy dog a shot at a forever home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 22:00:00" d="2020-11-01 23:00:00"><n>Cold Blooded Peruvian Predator: Expedition Mungo</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mungo heads to Peru in a bid to capture on camera the legendary yacumama – a super-snake so feared by local villagers that they have tried to blow it up with dynamite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 23:00:00" d="2020-11-02 00:00:00"><n>Jeremy Wade's Dark Waters</n><t>D</t>    <k>Fisherman and adventurer, Jeremy Wade, travels to Lake Garda in northern Italy to investigate a 16th century monster fish. What secrets is the lake hiding?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-02 00:00:00" d="2020-11-02 01:00:00"><n>Swimming With Monsters: Steve Backshall</n><t>D</t>    <k>Steve travels to the Pantanal in Brazil to swim with and study the monstrous anacondas that inhabit this region. But could his presence in the water trigger an attack?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-02 01:00:00" d="2020-11-02 02:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>The dedicated team continue their work through the chaos of the COVID-19 pandemic. A dog has been hit by a car and a puppy is suspected of eating DVDs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-02 02:00:00" d="2020-11-02 03:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Raneys attempt to save a single mother and her daughter from a rampant moose, Marty builds a bridge across a creek and Matt teaches predator deterrent techniques</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-02 03:00:00" d="2020-11-02 04:40:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>The crew helps Lizzy find and injured dog and a long-time employee gets exciting news about his future. Meanwhile, Mariah helps a dog facing tumour surgery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-02 04:40:00" d="2020-11-02 05:10:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why are some cats cross-eyed? How do meerkats eat poisonous scorpions and how can hippos sleep whilst holding their breath? Experts answer these questions and more!</k>  </p>
</a>
