<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-10-29 03:39:10"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 05:10:00" d="2020-11-05 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Debbie is torn between her boyfriend and her peeing cat Blinkie. Krisi and Jason want to get married, but standing in their way is her crazy cat, Frankie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 06:00:00" d="2020-11-05 07:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>A golden retriever is rushed into surgery after swallowing a pacifier. Then, when a stray dog is hit by a car in Oklahoma, Dr Jeff and his team step up to save him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 07:00:00" d="2020-11-05 07:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts analyse and explain how spiders covered a whole town in webs overnight. Plus, do crows have funerals and why is a lake in Venezuela so electrifying?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 07:30:00" d="2020-11-05 08:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animals can do extraordinary things – but how do they do it? Experts spill the secrets of the animal kingdom with amazing footage and surprising facts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 08:00:00" d="2020-11-05 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia takes in a pit bull that was rescued from awful conditions in Kuwait. Meanwhile, when a stray dog arrives at Villalobos, Earl is determined to find the owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 09:00:00" d="2020-11-05 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When an aggressive dog is in danger of being put down, Tia heads to South Carolina to save him. Plus, parolee Toney Converse takes on more responsibility</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 10:00:00" d="2020-11-05 11:00:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>After devouring all his tankmate’s food, a hungry sea turtle finds a space to eat in peace. Plus, two beluga whales are welcomed to their new home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 11:00:00" d="2020-11-05 12:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet: Coast To Coast</n><t>D</t>    <k>73% Dr. Danni helps her friend’s cat that keeps fighting with its neighbour. Meanwhile, Dr. Peter struggles to get close to Lottie the ferocious and frightened Chihuahua</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 12:00:00" d="2020-11-05 13:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Tia receives an adoption email unlike any other, she makes a cross-country trip to find a dog a home before Christmas. Plus, the family get an unforgettable gift</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 13:00:00" d="2020-11-05 14:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jackson meets up with a soft-spoken musician who feels abused by her adopted cat and is ashamed that she can't figure out how to prevent her cat’s behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 14:00:00" d="2020-11-05 15:00:00"><n u="Dogs">Dogs 101</n><t>D</t>    <k>Learn which pets are best for urban living and which ones are family friendly through a mix of experts, live-action footage and photography</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 15:00:00" d="2020-11-05 16:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Jeff works to save a dog kicked in the head by a horse, and tackles a neighbourhood overrun with feral cats. And a pet ferret shows some worrying symptoms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 16:00:00" d="2020-11-05 17:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Jeff returns to Mexico to help desperate pets - and some reluctant patients at a monkey sanctuary. Plus, the team must catch and treat a pack of street dogs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 17:00:00" d="2020-11-05 18:00:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>A rescued sea otter must build his independence after becoming too attached to his best friend. And, over 50 African penguins are moved for spring cleaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 18:00:00" d="2020-11-05 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet: Coast To Coast</n><t>D</t>    <k>73% Dr. Alex desperately tries to fix a Labrador-staffy cross that has been attacked by another dog. Plus, an American Bulldog has eaten a whole packet of macadamia nuts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 19:00:00" d="2020-11-05 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Kristie Franks has a difficult job trying to herd up 20 cats in the overrun house of a hoarder, while Debbie Michielson rescues a horse with an injury to its leg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 20:00:00" d="2020-11-05 21:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Raneys arrive in Missouri to see a family that has just survived a tornado. Living in a crumbling cabin, they also have no clean water source</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 21:00:00" d="2020-11-05 21:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why have a pair of giraffes turned white in Kenya? Plus, why are the world’s fastest land animal not always successful when hunting? Experts examine this and more!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 21:30:00" d="2020-11-05 22:00:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>How do bats avoid bumping into each other in the middle of the night? Why did a bottlenose dolphin seek out a diver’s help? Experts examine this and more!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 22:00:00" d="2020-11-05 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>A shocking discovery leads to a life and death battle for a litter of pups and an emaciated mare struggles to give birth to her foal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-05 23:00:00" d="2020-11-06 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Villalobos prepares for Hurricane Barry with Tia and the crew urgently ensuring the animals’ safety. Later, a cancer survivor hopes to rescue an unwanted dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-06 00:00:00" d="2020-11-06 01:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Kenani is in a serious motorcycle accident, Tia and the Villalobos crew must band together to ensure him a speedy recovery. Plus, an ex-marine looks for a dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-06 01:00:00" d="2020-11-06 02:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Raneys arrive in Missouri to see a family that has just survived a tornado. Living in a crumbling cabin, they also have no clean water source</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-06 02:00:00" d="2020-11-06 03:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Mike and Patricia love their cats, but unfortunately their cats do not love each other. Patricia, a ghost hunter, thinks there is a supernatural reason why</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-06 03:00:00" d="2020-11-06 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>A shocking discovery leads to a life and death battle for a litter of pups and an emaciated mare struggles to give birth to her foal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-06 03:50:00" d="2020-11-06 04:40:00"><n>Miami Animal Police</n><t>D</t>    <k>Wildlife trapper Todd Hardwick gets a call from a family hearing noises and scratches coming from the roof of their house. What he finds is quite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-06 04:40:00" d="2020-11-06 05:10:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>What are cats trying to communicate to humans? Why have some of the world’s cleverest monkeys turned to a life of crime? Experts answer these questions and more!</k>  </p>
</a>
