<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-10-24 04:33:14"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 06:00:00" d="2020-10-31 07:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A couple is torn between two dogs and can’t decide who to bring home with them. And, a local stray is in dire need of medical attention, but afraid of humans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 07:00:00" d="2020-10-31 08:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A phone call in the middle of the night leads Tia racing to deal with a family emergency. And, a homeless man reaches out for help when his dog has trouble breathing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 08:00:00" d="2020-10-31 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Moe and Lizzy rescue a sick stray, but a diagnosis proves tricky. Meanwhile, new mom Tania struggles to find a balance between life and work at Villalobos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 09:00:00" d="2020-10-31 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>The rescue team begin Operation Rhino, hoping to place a long-term shelter resident in a fantastic home. Plus, two dogs need rescuing in the French Quarter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 10:00:00" d="2020-10-31 11:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>The crew rescues a sick and injured dog that is facing a whole host of difficult health problems. Plus, former parolee worker Matt returns to the shelter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 11:00:00" d="2020-10-31 12:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Overwhelmed by work, Tia hires three new parolees to help out – but soon things take a turn for the worse. And the shelter is swamped by a group of new dogs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 12:00:00" d="2020-10-31 13:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet: Coast To Coast</n><t>D</t>    <k>73% Dr. Kate investigates why a rabbit has stopped eating. Plus, a sausage dog receives experimental treatment and Dr. Peter helps a monkey with suspected tuberculosis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 13:00:00" d="2020-10-31 14:00:00"><n>The Vet Life</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Ross takes care of a pair of roosters involved in a barnyard brawl and joins Dr Lavigne for a hyena consultation. And, Dr Blue treats a paralysed Yorkie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 14:00:00" d="2020-10-31 15:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>With thousands of animals in need, and vet care unaffordable to most, Dr Jeff heads to Mexico to run a mobile clinic and help as many people and pets as they can</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 15:00:00" d="2020-10-31 16:00:00"><n>Shark Island</n><t>D</t>    <k>In a remote corner of the Indian Ocean, Reunion Island has become the most dangerous place on the planet for shark attacks. Is there a way of preventing them?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 16:00:00" d="2020-10-31 17:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Villalobos throws a Halloween party to raise money for the rescue. An old friend returns and Lizzy struggles to rescue a stray dog in the middle of the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 17:00:00" d="2020-10-31 18:00:00"><n>Mermaids: The New Evidence</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jon Frankel meets the marine biologist who is convinced that mermaids exist and examines the social media response to apparent sightings of the mythical creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 18:00:00" d="2020-10-31 20:00:00"><n>Loch Ness Monster: New Evidence</n><t>D</t>    <k>Top scientists reveal how a revolutionary study and advanced DNA technology solved the mystery of the legendary Loch Ness monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 20:00:00" d="2020-10-31 22:00:00"><n>The Lost Kingdom Of The Yeti</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the high-altitude wilderness of Bhutan, new evidence hints that the mysterious yeti may exist. Mark Evans travels into the Himalayas to discover the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 22:00:00" d="2020-10-31 23:00:00"><n>Guardians Of The Glades</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dusty and the team must capture a giant calf-eating snake and venture into an abandoned factory to save upper Florida from invasive pythons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-10-31 23:00:00" d="2020-11-01 01:00:00"><n>The Cannibal In The Jungle</n><t>D</t>    <k>Follows the story of an American scientist who was convicted of killing and cannibalizing two colleagues in the jungles of Flores, Indonesia in 1977</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 01:00:00" d="2020-11-01 02:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Raneys are faced with the daunting task of overhauling a faulty electrical system and building the first hydro-electric wheel on the Little Susitna River</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 02:00:00" d="2020-11-01 03:00:00"><n>Treehouse Masters</n><t>D</t>    <k>A family asks Pete to build a brewery-in-the-sky on their massive property. Pete crafts a barn themed tavern with a brewing system in the trees accessible by a rope</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 03:00:00" d="2020-11-01 03:50:00"><n>Treehouse Masters</n><t>D</t>    <k>An Irish family has the perfect tree to nestle a Celtic-themed cottage. Pete devises a design that includes a rainmaker to mimic the wet Ireland climate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 03:50:00" d="2020-11-01 04:40:00"><n>Treehouse Masters</n><t>D</t>    <k>Pete builds an adventure-themed treehouse for a family of explorers in Pennsylvania’s Pocono Mountains. This two-storey masterpiece is packed with novelties</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-11-01 04:40:00" d="2020-11-01 05:10:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>How do caterpillars transform into magnificent butterflies in their cocoon? Plus, why are cats’ tongues the way they are? Experts answer these questions and more!</k>  </p>
</a>
