<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-10-28 03:49:54"><p id_tv="1119" o="2020-11-04 05:00:00" d="2020-11-04 06:30:00" c="1"><n>Hell Is Where The Home Is</n><t>F</t>    <k>Two troubled couples rent a beautiful house in the desert, hoping to forget their struggles. But chaos ensues when an unexpected visitor with sinister motives shows up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-11-04 06:30:00" d="2020-11-04 07:00:00"><n>Sky Cinema Preview</n>    <k>Check out all the great movies coming to Sky Cinema in November</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-11-04 07:00:00" d="2020-11-04 09:10:00" c="1"><n>The Field Guide To Evil</n><t>F</t>    <k>Anthology horror film bringing together eight nightmarish stories from around the globe, from acclaimed directors including Peter Strickland and Can Evrenol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-11-04 09:10:00" d="2020-11-04 11:00:00" c="1"><n>Alien Parasite</n><t>F</t>    <k>A local cop fights back when, one by one, the residents of a small town become infected by an insidious bug that turns them into violent killing machines</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-11-04 11:00:00" d="2020-11-04 14:00:00" c="1"><n>Interstellar</n><t>F</t>    <k>85% Christopher Nolan's awe-inspiring sci-fi epic stars Matthew McConaughey and Anne Hathaway as explorers tasked with securing humanity's survival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-11-04 14:00:00" d="2020-11-04 16:00:00" c="1"><n>Star Trek V: The Final Frontier</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Captain Kirk and his crew are kidnapped by a renegade Vulcan in this sci-fi sequel, directed by William Shatner. With the late Leonard Nimoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-11-04 16:00:00" d="2020-11-04 18:15:00" c="1"><n>Star Trek VI: The Undiscovered Country</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% The Enterprise crew's imminent peace with the Klingons, is threatened after Kirk and McCoy are framed for the Klingon leader's murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-11-04 18:15:00" d="2020-11-04 20:05:00" c="1"><n>The Final Wish</n><t>F</t>    <k>A man returns home to help his grief-stricken mother following his father's sudden death, and discovers a darkly mysterious object in his possessions. Mystery-horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-11-04 20:05:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Reign Of Fire</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% In a world scorched by dragons, grim Christian Bale and slayer Matthew McConaughey defend their band of survivors against fire-breathing predators. Fantasy adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-05 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Interstellar</n><t>F</t>    <k>85% Christopher Nolan's awe-inspiring sci-fi epic stars Matthew McConaughey and Anne Hathaway as explorers tasked with securing humanity's survival</k>  </p>
</a>
