<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2020-10-24 04:33:14"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 05:00:00" d="2020-10-31 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 07:00:00" d="2020-10-31 07:20:00"><n u="Pimp My Ride">Pimp My Ride V (7)</n><t>M</t>    <k>57% Pimp Master of Ceremonies Xzibit turns tired old hatchbacks into fully loaded cruisin' machines. X and the guys take a worn out Mama's Minivan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 07:20:00" d="2020-10-31 07:45:00"><n u="Pimp My Ride">Pimp My Ride V (8)</n><t>M</t>    <k>57% X and the guys create a fantasy car! Complete with reverse gull wing doors, a cotton candy machine, and even a robotic arm! (S5, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 07:45:00" d="2020-10-31 08:10:00"><n u="Pimp My Ride">Pimp My Ride V (9)</n><t>M</t>    <k>57% X and the G.A.S. crew surprise the owner of a Ford Festiva with a big pimpin' a nitrous system, a racing body kit, a 'tower of power' and a telescoping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 08:10:00" d="2020-10-31 08:35:00"><n u="Pimp My Ride">Pimp My Ride V (10)</n><t>M</t>    <k>57% Chamillionaire fills in for X and finds a comic book lover who's obsessed by the Fantastic Four, so the guys at G.A.S. turn this fan's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 08:35:00" d="2020-10-31 08:55:00"><n u="Pimp My Ride">Pimp My Ride V (11)</n><t>M</t>    <k>57% X finds a mobile doggie grooming company owner with one mangy mutt of a car. G.A.S. pimp out the car with a top-of-the-line doggie washing station, plasma</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 08:55:00" d="2020-10-31 09:00:00"><n u="New: Fresh Out Live">New: Fresh Out Live I (135)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Fresh Out Live delivers the most important music and pop culture news of the week and beyond with artist interviews, in-studio performances, album drops</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 09:00:00" d="2020-10-31 10:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VIII (818)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ryan thought he'd found his quarantine bae. But when Kamie and Nev start to dig, it's not long before they uncover that Micah may be more interested</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 10:00:00" d="2020-10-31 11:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VIII (819)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dianela fled her home in Venezuela to start a new life with José, a man she's been in a relationship with but has never met! Nev and Kamie tackle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 11:00:00" d="2020-10-31 12:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VIII (820)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Brooklyn needs answers about her elusive online ex Jason so she can move on. But Nev and Kamie dig up drama in Brooklyn's dating past that may connect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 12:00:00" d="2020-10-31 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 X (1005)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Briana confronts Luis about her STI test results. Jade is forced to support her family after they all lose their jobs. Aubree reconsiders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 13:00:00" d="2020-10-31 14:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 X (1006)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% An explosive family brawl leaves Jade caught between Sean and her parents. DeVoin's family reappears in Briana and Nova's lives after being absent for years. (S10, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 14:00:00" d="2020-10-31 15:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 X (1007)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Jade is caught between her mum and Sean, but a drug test could reveal the truth. Leah is forced to balance her growing concerns for Ali and supporting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 15:00:00" d="2020-10-31 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Trick Or Treat">Catfish: Trick Or Treat VII (737)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Justin Combs joins Nev to help CJ find Shana, a woman who CJ's been having a steamy relationship with for eight years but has never met! (S7, ep37)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 16:00:00" d="2020-10-31 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Trick Or Treat">Catfish: Trick Or Treat VIII (809)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaliyah is saving herself for model Jaquan, a guy she's dating exclusively but has never met. As Nev and Kamie dig into his story, they become alarmed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 17:00:00" d="2020-10-31 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Trick Or Treat">Catfish: Trick Or Treat VI (619)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jasmine writes to Nev and Max asking for help for a &quot;friend&quot;. But they're perplexed when Jasmine drops a bombshell revelation: they've helped her friend before! (S6, ep19)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 18:00:00" d="2020-10-31 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Trick Or Treat">Catfish: Trick Or Treat II (215)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Superfan Keyonnah can hardly believe her luck, she's almost certain that she's been having an online relationship with her childhood crush, the rapper Bow Wow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 19:00:00" d="2020-10-31 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Trick Or Treat">Catfish: Trick Or Treat II (204)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Lauren met Derek online years ago. Derek is caring, supporting Lauren after she had a baby with a former boyfriend. Lauren thinks Derek could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 20:00:00" d="2020-10-31 21:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Trick Or Treat">Catfish: Trick Or Treat III (306)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>John is ready to leave Detroit but one thing holds him back: Kelsey. The two have never spoken outside of online chats but John is sure she's the one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 21:00:00" d="2020-10-31 22:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Trick Or Treat">Catfish: Trick Or Treat V (503)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Since Leuh saw surfer Justin it's been insta-love. But after two failed attempts to meet up, she wants to know if he's the man of her dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 22:00:00" d="2020-10-31 23:00:00"><n u="New: TV Talent Shows At War">New: TV Talent Shows At War I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nicki Chapman explores the cut-throat world of talent shows. TV execs describe the tactics they employ to beat the competition. (S1, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 23:00:00" d="2020-11-01 00:00:00"><n u="Ex On The Beach: Exiest Moments">Ex On The Beach: Exiest Moments (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>46% We take a look back at the best bits from the first four series. Find out the real story behind the craziest beach arrivals, the biggest betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 00:00:00" d="2020-11-01 01:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us III (304)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ashley and Jordan take the ultimate friend test, mates Nicole and Dayna dish the dirt on each other and Crystal plots revenge on her bad boyfriend Jack. (S3, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 01:00:00" d="2020-11-01 02:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us III (305)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Buddies Ant and Joe take their banter to the next level, and Tian and Natalie get inked with tattoos neither will ever forget. (S3, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 02:00:00" d="2020-11-01 03:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us III (306)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's a double tat initiation for tattooists Hue and Charl and emotions run high, and Chloe marks her ground with a tattoo her cheating boyfriend will never forget. (S3, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 03:00:00" d="2020-11-01 03:25:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass II (211)</n><t>M</t>    <k>69% Bam Margera and Brandon Dicamillo get double-crossed by the Jackass producers during a prank and &quot;arrested&quot; by a fake police officer. Also features beard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 03:25:00" d="2020-11-01 03:50:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass II (212)</n><t>M</t>    <k>69% Johnny Knoxville, Chris Pontius, Mike Kassak and Rick Kossick go to the Sunset ranch for an old-style western shoot out. Also features snow surfing and spermathon! (S2, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 03:50:00" d="2020-11-01 04:15:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (915)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Hip hop star Vic Mensa joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to check out some close calls in &quot;Still Alive&quot;, learn creative ways to save more money and get extra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 04:15:00" d="2020-11-01 04:40:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (916)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo choke down some street meat, party with a few &quot;sliter sisters&quot; and hit the stairs with some extreme slinkies. (S9, ep16)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 04:40:00" d="2020-11-01 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (917)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Singer-songwriter Jessie J joins Rob, Steelo and Chanel to learn how to &quot;do it like a dude&quot;, hear some harsh truths in &quot;mum-splaining&quot; and watch the bodies</k>  </p>
</a>
