<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-10-28 03:48:16"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 05:00:00" d="2020-11-04 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 07:00:00" d="2020-11-04 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (411)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% Quinn becomes a believer in guardian angels after watching a television special about them, and although Daria remains skeptical, she's unable to convince Quinn otherwise. (S4, ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 07:20:00" d="2020-11-04 07:45:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills II (212)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% In this season finale, Heidi makes her final decision about moving in with Spencer. Lauren looks to Audrina to fill the void left by her best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 07:45:00" d="2020-11-04 08:10:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills III (2)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% After last season's heartache, it looks as if Lauren's ready for a fresh start. After being betrayed by friends and losing Heidi to Spencer, are things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 08:10:00" d="2020-11-04 09:00:00"><n u="16 And Pregnant">16 And Pregnant I (106)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Catelynn and Tyler both have very dramatic home lives, and it gets even more complicated when Catelynn falls pregnant. They have some important choices</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 09:00:00" d="2020-11-04 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (519)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Kailyn's estranged mum returns. Chelsea faces Adam at Aubree's practice. Corey's dad helps Leah with Ali's temporary wheelchair. Jenelle starts the process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 10:00:00" d="2020-11-04 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (520)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Adam is arrested again. Chelsea tries to cope. Leah tries to manage the growing jealousy between the twins. Nathan and Barbara clash. Kailyn struggles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 11:00:00" d="2020-11-04 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (521)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Jenelle and Barbara clash over Jace's behavioural issues. Kailyn struggles with the kids for Javi's return home. Leah decides to take Corey to court. (S5, ep21)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 12:00:00" d="2020-11-04 13:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Homeless">Rich Kids Go Homeless I (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Former ballet dancer Calum finds it difficult to cope on the streets, even when paired with Gert, a Belgian man left homeless after losing his benefits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 13:00:00" d="2020-11-04 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers VII (728)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and NFL star Rashad Jennings help Deven find his mysterious online love James. James won't videochat yet he invites Deven to fly across the country to meet him! Deven needs answers. (S7, ep28)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 14:00:00" d="2020-11-04 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers VI (602)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alante has been planning a life with his online love. She’s perfect but her disappearances have Alante worried. Nev and Max help uncover a truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 15:00:00" d="2020-11-04 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers VII (717)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A mystery leads Nev and Laura to help Derek track down his online love. They uncover a Snapchat scandal, betrayal, and a conclusion that hits closer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 16:00:00" d="2020-11-04 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers VII (715)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max agree to help Chelsea finally meet Charles in person. While Chelsea has only spoken to Charles once on the phone, the guys soon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 17:00:00" d="2020-11-04 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers VIII (813)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Kamie receive a request to help Dre finally meet elusive Casey. But the request is unconventional and the situation becomes so intense, the hosts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 18:00:00" d="2020-11-04 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers VII (719)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Jane Carrey help aspiring sugarbaby Mike choose between his LA life of leisure and his affection for the mysterious Joey, a broke mechanic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 19:00:00" d="2020-11-04 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers V (506)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chanelle is the light Michael needed in his life, but out of the blue she's disappeared, leaving only Nev and Max to help him find his missing love. (S5, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 20:00:00" d="2020-11-04 21:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Homeless">Rich Kids Go Homeless I (106)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Isabella leaves her high life and celebrity boyfriend to live homeless in Stratford. She also meets Cathy, a homeless mother who won't go anywhere without</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 21:00:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00"><n u="New: Teen Mom">New: Teen Mom 2 X (1008)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Tensions erupt when Jade asks her parents to move out. After an x-ray, Leah grapples with the possibility that Ali's condition is progressing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 23:00:00"><n u="New: Geordie OGs">New: Geordie OGs III (302)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Holly installs a pre-wedding sex ban and Marnie has no idea Casey is engagement ring shopping. Aaron turns to a sport psychologist which makes him reassess his future. (S3, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 23:00:00" d="2020-11-05 00:00:00"><n u="New: Catfish: The TV Show">New: Catfish: The TV Show VIII (821)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Jay met Vegas girl Anna, he thought he had hit the jackpot! Before he can cash in his chips, Nev and Kamie find that Anna may hold secrets that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 00:00:00" d="2020-11-05 01:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Trolls">Catfish: Trolls I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ciera's life changed when a troll named Eskimo Jay stole her selfies and created an offensive meme that went viral. Ciera teams up with Charlamagne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 01:00:00" d="2020-11-05 02:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime">True Life Crime I (106)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Lesandro &quot;Junior&quot; Guzman-Feliz was killed by gang members brandishing machetes. The murder was recorded by security cameras. The violent nature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 02:00:00" d="2020-11-05 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Nathan's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Nathan's Best Bits XVII (1703)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Sam and Chloe's relationship comes under scrutiny from Nathan, causing friction in the house. Will this divide help Nathan and Chloe's bond and allow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 03:00:00" d="2020-11-05 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Nathan's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Nathan's Best Bits XIX (1901)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Geordies are back, but this time Anna &amp; Scotty are shaking things up by throwing four newbies in the mix. They do their best but the oldies are always</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 03:50:00" d="2020-11-05 04:15:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (927)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo swap places as Chanel teaches that &quot;cute&quot; kills, Steelo warns about &quot;death carts&quot; and Rob shows how people get down with PPP. (S9, ep27)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 04:15:00" d="2020-11-05 04:40:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (928)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rapper Big Baby D.R.A.M. joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to get into some 'Bad Broccoli', learn how to speak 'Unclish' and fend off a few urban predators. (S9, ep28)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 04:40:00" d="2020-11-05 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (929)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rapper Post Malone joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to play some ball, get messy with the category &quot;saucin' on you&quot;, and show off some knuckle tats. (S9, ep29)</k>  </p>
</a>
