<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2020-10-29 03:49:44"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 05:00:00" d="2020-11-05 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 07:00:00" d="2020-11-05 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (412)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% When Jake suffers a slight kitchen mishap of the inferno variety, the Morgendorffers must move to a hotel. (S4, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 07:20:00" d="2020-11-05 07:45:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills III (2)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Lauren heads to Laguna Beach to get advice from her mother over her recent situation. Audrina meets up with her former fling, Justin. Spencer proposes to Heidi. (S3, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 07:45:00" d="2020-11-05 08:10:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills III (3)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Now she's decided to give Justin a second chance, Audrina wants Lauren to get to know her boy better. She invites Lauren to drinks, and Lauren agrees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 08:10:00" d="2020-11-05 09:00:00"><n u="16 And Pregnant">16 And Pregnant II (201)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jenelle, a North Carolina beach bunny who loves partying, realizes her long-distance boyfriend isn't coming back, and that she's too immature to raise a baby herself. (S2, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 09:00:00" d="2020-11-05 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (522)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Kailyn and Jo disagree over Isaac's upcoming visitation schedule. Chelsea comes face to face with Adam's new girlfriend. Arguments with Nathan and Barbara</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 10:00:00" d="2020-11-05 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (523)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Jenelle's second son, Kaiser, is born. Leah discovers that Corey wants full custody. Kailyn gets emotional when Isaac leaves for summer visitation with Jo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 11:00:00" d="2020-11-05 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (524)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Leah and Corey face each other in court. Kailyn and Javi adjust to life without Isaac. Chelsea deals with another of Adam's arrests. Jenelle tries to build</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 12:00:00" d="2020-11-05 13:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Homeless">Rich Kids Go Homeless I (106)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Isabella leaves her high life and celebrity boyfriend to live homeless in Stratford. She also meets Cathy, a homeless mother who won't go anywhere without</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 13:00:00" d="2020-11-05 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models VIII (816)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Kamie are shocked to hear that Stephanie has been talking to Danny for ten years but has never video chatted! Stephanie is ready for love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 14:00:00" d="2020-11-05 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models VII (727)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Co-host popstar, Elle King joins Nev to help Nique find her Tumblr love, Alice. Digging deep leads to more questions than answers as</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 15:00:00" d="2020-11-05 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models VII (710)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dylan's fallen for a beautiful model with an elusive secret. With all the standard red flags, Nev and Max assume it's an open and shut case, but the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 16:00:00" d="2020-11-05 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models II (205)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dorion is about to give up everything for online love Jeszica, including his relationship with girlfriend Raffinee. But first he wants to know, is Jeszica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 17:00:00" d="2020-11-05 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Sunny is in love with the man of her dreams. Jamison is a model, a TV writer, and also studying to be an anaesthesiologist. However, the pair have never met</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 18:00:00" d="2020-11-05 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models VII (707)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Traves asks for help with his online girlfriend Candy, it looks like classic catfishing. But when the guys dig deeper, they realise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 19:00:00" d="2020-11-05 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models IV (406)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Single father Felipe is ready to settle down with Jasmine. However, the two have been talking online for eight months and have never met. Max returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 20:00:00" d="2020-11-05 21:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VIII (821)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Jay met Vegas girl Anna, he thought he had hit the jackpot! Before he can cash in his chips, Nev and Kamie find that Anna may hold secrets that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 21:00:00" d="2020-11-05 21:30:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Get ready to snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! This week features Selling Sunset's notorious Christine Quinn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 21:30:00" d="2020-11-05 22:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Get ready to snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! The cult show is back, this week featuring US reality TV royalty Caitlyn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 22:00:00" d="2020-11-05 23:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Nathan's Story">Geordie Shore: Nathan's Story I (107)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nathan lets us in to his boudoir to tell all about his life from playing with dollhouses in school to changing the face of reality TV. Hear the inside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-05 23:00:00" d="2020-11-06 00:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs III (302)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Holly installs a pre-wedding sex ban and Marnie has no idea Casey is engagement ring shopping. Aaron turns to a sport psychologist which makes him reassess his future. (S3, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 00:00:00" d="2020-11-06 00:30:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd IX (901)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>59% Justin Bieber takes the reins from Ashton Kutcher. Taylor Swift, Rob Dyrdek and Sean Kingston are all victims of Bieber's mischievous mind. (S9, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 00:30:00" d="2020-11-06 01:00:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd IX (902)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>59% Bam Margera punks Tyler, The Creator, Ronnie and Tyler Posey. (S9, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 01:00:00" d="2020-11-06 02:00:00"><n u="New: Double Shot At Love With...">New: Double Shot At Love With... II (250)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Pauly D, Vinny, and the rest of the Vegas crew reunite virtually to break down all the hookups and blow ups from this season. Plus Mike &quot;The Situation&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 02:00:00" d="2020-11-06 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Nathan's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Nathan's Best Bits XIX (1909)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Geordie's throw a house party! Beau chooses Bethan over Abbie, which leads to Chloe and Nathan falling out - Again! Scott decides team bonding's needed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 03:00:00" d="2020-11-06 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Nathan's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Nathan's Best Bits XX (2003)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chloe confronts the girls about not supporting her. Sam's behaviour on a lads night out leads to them splitting up, again! Abbie tells James she saw Chloe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 03:50:00" d="2020-11-06 04:15:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (930)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% On a special episode of Major Key-diculousness, DJ Khaled teaches Rob, Chanel and Sterling how to be grateful, how to avoid &quot;They&quot; and how to get &quot;Lost at Ski&quot;. (S9, ep30)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 04:15:00" d="2020-11-06 04:40:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness VIII (801)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% With a whole new stage, the guys &quot;Do It For The Vine&quot;, bust out their 3D glasses for the category &quot;3Diculousness&quot; and watch some old folks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 04:40:00" d="2020-11-06 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness VIII (802)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Comedian Eric Andre returns to check out some &quot;Power Dicks&quot;, watch people go tongue to tongue in the category &quot;Unexpected Mouth Mates&quot; and get sticky</k>  </p>
</a>
