<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2020-10-25 03:44:17"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 05:00:00" d="2020-11-01 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 07:00:00" d="2020-11-01 07:20:00"><n u="Pimp My Ride">Pimp My Ride V (12)</n><t>M</t>    <k>57% X pimps a Jeep owned by a contractor who's always on the go. The guys at G.A.S. give it a 'lowrider' style paint job and airbags, and add the ultimate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 07:20:00" d="2020-11-01 07:45:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills I (108)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Jason wants to make Lauren's 20th birthday special, but when she lies to him about working with male models for a Teen Vogue assignment, their relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 07:45:00" d="2020-11-01 08:10:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills I (109)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Heidi decides she's had enough drama with Jordan. When she turns to the girls for advice, she realises what she has to do. And are Lauren and Jason's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 08:10:00" d="2020-11-01 08:35:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills I (110)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Lauren's work at LA Fashion Week brings a career opportunity of a lifetime, but she's torn between her job and Jason. Whitney leaves LA; Heidi and Audrina</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 08:35:00" d="2020-11-01 09:00:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills II (201)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% After a rocky summer with her boyfriend Jason, Lauren decides to break it off and returns to work to face her boss. Heidi finds herself in trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 09:00:00" d="2020-11-01 09:30:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills II (202)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Lauren goes on her first date since Jason and is tested at work when she's asked to work a fashion show. Heidi has a life changing secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 09:30:00" d="2020-11-01 10:00:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills II (203)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Uninvited Audrina goes to Heidi's birthday, she learns Heidi's not ready to forgive and forget. Lauren, determined to focus on work, falls for the charms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 10:00:00" d="2020-11-01 10:30:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills II (204)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Audrina tells Heidi about Spencer's cheating ways, but Heidi is doubtful - until she sees it for herself. Lauren continues to wonder whether she is ready</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 10:30:00" d="2020-11-01 11:00:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills II (205)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Heidi calls Spencer out on his flirting behaviour after warnings from girlfriends, Heidi gives him another chance. Lauren and Whitney are threatened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 11:00:00" d="2020-11-01 11:30:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills II (206)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Heidi and Lauren get into a major argument about Spencer as Lauren feels like she is losing Heidi as a friend. (S2, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 11:30:00" d="2020-11-01 12:00:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills II (207)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Lauren realises she can't trust her best friends after Heidi hooks Jen up with Brody. (S2, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 12:00:00" d="2020-11-01 13:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Scammed">Catfish: Scammed VIII (811)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In the first ever virtual catfish episode, Nev and Kamie won't let quarantine stop them from helping love struck Jason find the dirt on his Insta-model Keith. (S8, ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 13:00:00" d="2020-11-01 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Scammed">Catfish: Scammed II (211)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaliyah has been able to share her life struggles with Alicia. However, despite living only 70 blocks away, Alicia refuses to meet her as she hasn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 14:00:00" d="2020-11-01 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Scammed">Catfish: Scammed VII (711)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kiaira and Cortney had a baby despite Kiaira never meeting Cortney or the baby! Nev and Max try to bring the family together, but is this the greatest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 15:00:00" d="2020-11-01 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Scammed">Catfish: Scammed III (304)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Lucille led a simple life until she was asked to work for music producer Kidd Cole. Companies were never paid and one day Kidd couldn't be found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 16:00:00" d="2020-11-01 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Scammed">Catfish: Scammed IV (404)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Daisy met Marcus on Instagram and he instantly stole her heart. But Marcus won't speak to Daisy on the phone, let alone meet her in person</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 17:00:00" d="2020-11-01 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Scammed">Catfish: Scammed VI (617)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Robin is desperate to meet her hunky, long-distance love in person. Nev and Max agree to help her hunt him down, but what they uncover turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 18:00:00" d="2020-11-01 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Scammed">Catfish: Scammed V (519)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Luis has fallen for a single mum, and now he's ready to take their online relationship to the next level. But first Nev and Max must</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 19:00:00" d="2020-11-01 20:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 X (1006)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% An explosive family brawl leaves Jade caught between Sean and her parents. DeVoin's family reappears in Briana and Nova's lives after being absent for years. (S10, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 20:00:00" d="2020-11-01 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 X (1007)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Jade is caught between her mum and Sean, but a drug test could reveal the truth. Leah is forced to balance her growing concerns for Ali and supporting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 21:00:00" d="2020-11-01 22:00:00"><n u="Ghosted: Love Gone Missing">Ghosted: Love Gone Missing II (204)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>38% Michael quickly fell in love after the charming Francisco slid into his Twitter DMs. Their relationship blossomed fast, but there were some serious snags</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 22:00:00" d="2020-11-01 23:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Abbie And James'...">Geordie Shore: Abbie And James'... I (106)</n><t>M</t>    <k>. tory. Abbie reflects on her long journey to finding her perfect place: Geordie Shore. Whilst James opens up about the events that made him the man he is. (S1, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-01 23:00:00" d="2020-11-02 00:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs III (301)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaron welcomes his son into the world, but there's some bad news for his relationship. Holly takes a trip to secure a wedding venue and Marnie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-02 00:00:00" d="2020-11-02 01:00:00"><n u="One Night With My Ex">One Night With My Ex II (206)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Reality series. Holly ended things with Tom after his past came back to haunt them. Estranged Mark and Pippa have three kids, but have not spoken for six years. (S2, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-02 01:00:00" d="2020-11-02 02:00:00"><n u="Lindsay Lohan's Beach Club">Lindsay Lohan's Beach Club I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Lindsay comes to a decision regarding Jonitta and Gabi's altercation, and then decides to bring in two new VIP Hosts. New arrival Kailah plants seeds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-02 02:00:00" d="2020-11-02 03:00:00"><n>OMG! Gold Digger And Proud</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet the women who know the secret to getting cash out of men. They feel no shame in taking what they can get, and the gents are perfectly happy to give it to them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-02 03:00:00" d="2020-11-02 03:50:00"><n u="Double Shot At Love With...">Double Shot At Love With... II (216)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>. J Pauly D and Vinny. On their last day in Vegas, Pauly and Nikki must make a difficult decision about their relationship. Vinny and Maria consider their future together. (S2, ep16)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-02 03:50:00" d="2020-11-02 04:15:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (918)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo take a vacation to Lake Painatonka, catch the quick hands in 'Grabbies' and watch some unsuspecting people get pranked. (S9, ep18)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-02 04:15:00" d="2020-11-02 04:40:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (919)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Hip hop legend DJ Paul joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to get a little 'Zap Happy', live the 'Jugg Life', and get energized by some 'Beatspiration'. (S9, ep19)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-02 04:40:00" d="2020-11-02 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (920)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo get jammed up in 'Stuck My Life', take their chances in 'Gator Gamblin'' and enlist in the 'Gravy Seals'. (S9, ep20)</k>  </p>
</a>
