<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2020-10-30 03:41:17"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 05:00:00" d="2020-11-06 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 07:00:00" d="2020-11-06 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (413)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% Daria helps Jane dye her hair with less than stellar results. (S4, ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 07:20:00" d="2020-11-06 07:45:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills III (4)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Now that Heidi and Spencer have had her engagement rock resized at the jewellers, Heidi suggests that her husband-to-be come home with her to Colorado</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 07:45:00" d="2020-11-06 08:10:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills III (5)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% After Justin's disappearing act at Brody's barbeque on the last episode, Lauren thought Audrina's days with the bad boy were over. (S3, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 08:10:00" d="2020-11-06 09:00:00"><n u="16 And Pregnant">16 And Pregnant II (202)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nikki is a prankster princess whose posse of friends love her, but hate her boyfriend. Can she convince her friends and family that Josh is worthy of being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 09:00:00" d="2020-11-06 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (525)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Jenelle approaches Barbara about gaining custody of Jace. Kailyn is reunited with Isaac. Chelsea tries to move on romantically as Adam goes to jail. (S5, ep25)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 10:00:00" d="2020-11-06 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning VI (601)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Javi blows up over something he finds on Kailyn's phone. Chelsea is shocked when Adam requests 50/50 custody of Aubree. Leah has to face Corey in court</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 11:00:00" d="2020-11-06 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning VI (602)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Leah has to take a court-ordered drug test. Chelsea joins forces with Adam's ex to fight his custody request. Kailyn &amp; Javi's issues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 12:00:00" d="2020-11-06 13:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VIII (821)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Jay met Vegas girl Anna, he thought he had hit the jackpot! Before he can cash in his chips, Nev and Kamie find that Anna may hold secrets that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 13:00:00" d="2020-11-06 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Greats">Catfish: Greats V (515)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catfish is going international with a trip to the UK! Nev and Max meet Spencer who's been holding on to a secret for six years: he's in a relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 14:00:00" d="2020-11-06 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Greats">Catfish: Greats VI (603)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Danny is intent on building a life with his online love, despite her violent past. But when he enlists Nev and Max to help him meet her, they discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 15:00:00" d="2020-11-06 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Greats">Catfish: Greats VII (721)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Nick Young, aka Swaggy P, help Sheila figure out if she's being romanced by Love &amp; Hip Hop's Rich Dollaz. Is it a fan girl crush or is Sheila</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 16:00:00" d="2020-11-06 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Greats">Catfish: Greats VII (718)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max try to help Nick determine if the person he kissed during a mysterious blindfolded rendezvous is actually his online love, Jasmine, or someone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 17:00:00" d="2020-11-06 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Greats">Catfish: Greats III (305)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Tracie Thoms had a connection with a fan named &quot;Sammie&quot; after hearing about the passing of Sammie's friend. Sammie suddenly disappeared and now Tracie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 18:00:00" d="2020-11-06 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Greats">Catfish: Greats II (201)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Cassie was on a downward spiral until she got a friend request from a rapper named Steve. Two and a half years later, Cassie and Steve are engaged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 19:00:00" d="2020-11-06 19:55:00"><n u="Catfish: Greats">Catfish: Greats IV (403)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Harold found his match with a beautiful fellow jock named Armani. Although they live in the same area, they've never met. Nev is joined by Angel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 19:55:00" d="2020-11-06 20:00:00"><n>The Official UK Number One</n><t>M</t>    <k>Check out this week's ultimate chart champion as we present The Official UK Number 1!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 20:00:00" d="2020-11-06 21:00:00"><n u="World's Most Luxurious Hotels">World's Most Luxurious Hotels I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Docuseries offering a privileged peek at the luxuries enjoyed by the super-rich. A look at the Kempinski Adlon in Berlin, which has hosted the Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 21:00:00" d="2020-11-06 22:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 X (1008)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Tensions erupt when Jade asks her parents to move out. After an x-ray, Leah grapples with the possibility that Ali's condition is progressing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 22:00:00" d="2020-11-06 23:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs III (302)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Holly installs a pre-wedding sex ban and Marnie has no idea Casey is engagement ring shopping. Aaron turns to a sport psychologist which makes him reassess his future. (S3, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 23:00:00" d="2020-11-06 23:30:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Get ready to snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! This week features Selling Sunset's notorious Christine Quinn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-06 23:30:00" d="2020-11-07 00:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Get ready to snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! The cult show is back, this week featuring US reality TV royalty Caitlyn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-07 00:00:00" d="2020-11-07 01:00:00"><n u="TV Talent Shows At War">TV Talent Shows At War I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nicki Chapman explores the cut-throat world of talent shows. TV execs describe the tactics they employ to beat the competition. (S1, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-07 01:00:00" d="2020-11-07 01:30:00"><n u="Lip Sync Battle: Superstore">Lip Sync Battle: Superstore V (505)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's a &quot;Superstore&quot; super battle when Ben Feldman battles co-star Lauren Ash for the LSB Championship belt. Taking on tracks by Celine Dion and Madonna! (S5, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-07 01:30:00" d="2020-11-07 02:00:00"><n u="Lip Sync Battle: Black-ish">Lip Sync Battle: Black-ish V (506)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Comedy actor Brandon Micheal Hall takes on Marcus Scribner (Andre in &quot;Black-ish&quot;) as they battle it out for the LSB championship belt. Features tracks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-07 02:00:00" d="2020-11-07 02:30:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XVII (1727)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo find out what happens when you suffer from &quot;blindsight&quot;, save some coin by performing &quot;DIY plastic surgery&quot; and celebrate family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-07 02:30:00" d="2020-11-07 03:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XVII (1731)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel, and Steelo try not to say the wrong thing in &quot;temper triggers&quot;, celebrate all the fathers out there with &quot;dad's weekend&quot;, and prove that older</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-07 03:00:00" d="2020-11-07 03:25:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass II (213)</n><t>M</t>    <k>69% Johnny Knoxville gets looks of disbelief as he frantically tries to get his blood-soaked car washed. Also features krazy glue test, extreme unicycle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-07 03:25:00" d="2020-11-07 03:50:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass II (214)</n><t>M</t>    <k>69% Rake Yohn and Johnny Knoxville suit up in haz-mat gear to transfer an unknown chemical through the streets of Portland. Also features the human pinata</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-07 03:50:00" d="2020-11-07 04:15:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness VIII (803)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob welcomes NFL superstar Rob Gronkowski to learn what it's like to be &quot;Unwakeable&quot;, the dangers of being &quot;Bus Blind&quot; and experience the strange</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-07 04:15:00" d="2020-11-07 04:40:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness VIII (804)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Sterling discuss a condition called &quot;Temporary Fansanity&quot;, people who are &quot;Quick To Cry&quot; and our favourite summer sporting event, the &quot;Bro Games&quot;. (S8, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-07 04:40:00" d="2020-11-07 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness VIII (805)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Multi-platinum singer/songwriter Leona Lewis joins to watch some of her fellow &quot;Aisle Trolls&quot;, be misunderstood while &quot;Speaking Leonese&quot; and learn about</k>  </p>
</a>
