<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2020-10-23 04:45:48"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 05:00:00" d="2020-10-30 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 07:00:00" d="2020-10-30 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (408)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% The Morgendorffers attend a weekend retreat at the Quiet Ivy mental-health spa to be evaluated, as Helen is being considered for promotion. (S4, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 07:20:00" d="2020-10-30 07:45:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills II (206)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Heidi and Lauren get into a major argument about Spencer as Lauren feels like she is losing Heidi as a friend. (S2, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 07:45:00" d="2020-10-30 08:10:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills II (207)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Lauren realises she can't trust her best friends after Heidi hooks Jen up with Brody. (S2, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 08:10:00" d="2020-10-30 09:00:00"><n u="16 And Pregnant">16 And Pregnant I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this episode, we follow Amber, who's expecting a baby with her boyfriend Gary. They decide to move in together but it's not always easy for these teen parents. (S1, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 09:00:00" d="2020-10-30 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (510)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Kailyn and Javi finally celebrate their wedding. Chelsea graduates and lands a job. Jenelle accepts a plea that puts her on supervised probation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 10:00:00" d="2020-10-30 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (511)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Javi takes Isaac to Jo's for the first time. Adam responds to Chelsea's visitation objection. Ali tests out her wheelchair while Leah continues to struggle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 11:00:00" d="2020-10-30 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (512)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Kailyn's baby is born. Chelsea struggles with the new visitation agreement. Leah and Jeremy work on their relationship. Jenelle is pregnant but things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 12:00:00" d="2020-10-30 13:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Homeless">Rich Kids Go Homeless I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Far from her designer brands and world trips, Rukaya soon feels vulnerable on the streets when a group of men intimidate her and a fellow homeless woman. (S1, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 13:00:00" d="2020-10-30 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Filtered Fakers">Catfish: Filtered Fakers VI (610)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dylan receives an anonymous text warning him that his online love, Ally, is not who she says she is. After the mystery texter is revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 14:00:00" d="2020-10-30 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Filtered Fakers">Catfish: Filtered Fakers VIII (804)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Kamie receive an anonymous email from a whistleblower reporting a catfishing! But when our hosts arrive to help the named victim, they uncover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 15:00:00" d="2020-10-30 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Filtered Fakers">Catfish: Filtered Fakers VII (737)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Justin Combs joins Nev to help CJ find Shana, a woman who CJ's been having a steamy relationship with for eight years but has never met! (S7, ep37)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 16:00:00" d="2020-10-30 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Filtered Fakers">Catfish: Filtered Fakers VII (724)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After chatting for years with Chris, Shakinah needs to move forward with her life. But when Nev and co-host Kamie Crawford find out that Chris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 17:00:00" d="2020-10-30 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Filtered Fakers">Catfish: Filtered Fakers VII (710)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dylan's fallen for a beautiful model with an elusive secret. With all the standard red flags, Nev and Max assume it's an open and shut case, but the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 18:00:00" d="2020-10-30 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Filtered Fakers">Catfish: Filtered Fakers VI (608)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max receive emails from opposite sides of the same online romance, each concerned that the other may be a catfish! What happens next leaves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 19:00:00" d="2020-10-30 19:55:00"><n u="Catfish: Filtered Fakers">Catfish: Filtered Fakers III (302)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max are contacted by Carmen who is sounding the alarm on behalf of her cousin, Antwane. He's been in a three-year romance with a man named</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 19:55:00" d="2020-10-30 20:00:00"><n>The Official UK Number One</n><t>M</t>    <k>Check out this week's ultimate chart champion as we present The Official UK Number 1!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 20:00:00" d="2020-10-30 21:00:00"><n u="World's Most Luxurious Yachts">World's Most Luxurious Yachts I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Docuseries offering a privileged peek at the luxuries enjoyed by the super-rich. Helipads, pools and gold-embossed interiors are standard on GBP35m super yachts. (S1, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 21:00:00" d="2020-10-30 22:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 X (1007)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Jade is caught between her mum and Sean, but a drug test could reveal the truth. Leah is forced to balance her growing concerns for Ali and supporting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 22:00:00" d="2020-10-30 23:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs III (301)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaron welcomes his son into the world, but there's some bad news for his relationship. Holly takes a trip to secure a wedding venue and Marnie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 23:00:00" d="2020-10-30 23:30:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Get ready to snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! The cult show is back, this week featuring US reality TV royalty Caitlyn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-30 23:30:00" d="2020-10-31 00:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs UK">MTV Cribs UK I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring the homes of reality king Joey Essex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 00:00:00" d="2020-10-31 01:00:00"><n u="TV Talent Shows At War">TV Talent Shows At War I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nicki Chapman explores the cut-throat world of talent shows. Before they climb on that nerve-wracking stage, the contestants face many trials. (S1, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 01:00:00" d="2020-10-31 01:30:00"><n u="Lip Sync Battle: Tennis Special">Lip Sync Battle: Tennis Special V (503)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Serena Williams guest stars in the ultimate husband vs wife battle as tennis legend Andy Roddick takes on actress/supermodel Brooklyn Decker; features</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 01:30:00" d="2020-10-31 02:00:00"><n u="Lip Sync Battle: Riverdale">Lip Sync Battle: Riverdale V (504)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Special guest John Legend joins the LSB crew as singer/songwriter Andy Grammer takes on Riverdale's Vanessa Morgan as they battle it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 02:00:00" d="2020-10-31 02:30:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XVII (1725)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel, and Steelo pick up speed in &quot;fear feet&quot;, get international with &quot;British injuries&quot;, and dish out some &quot;parental payback&quot;. (S17, ep25)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 02:30:00" d="2020-10-31 03:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XVII (1726)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo check out the reasons we hate working from home, hurt some feelings with &quot;second-favourite parents&quot; and hand out promotions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 03:00:00" d="2020-10-31 03:25:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass II (211)</n><t>M</t>    <k>69% Bam Margera and Brandon Dicamillo get double-crossed by the Jackass producers during a prank and &quot;arrested&quot; by a fake police officer. Also features beard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 03:25:00" d="2020-10-31 03:50:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass II (212)</n><t>M</t>    <k>69% Johnny Knoxville, Chris Pontius, Mike Kassak and Rick Kossick go to the Sunset ranch for an old-style western shoot out. Also features snow surfing and spermathon! (S2, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 03:50:00" d="2020-10-31 04:15:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (912)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo dive head-first into some &quot;Dead Pools&quot;, go into &quot;Carrot Shock&quot; and learn a valuable life lesson that &quot;everything farts&quot;. (S9, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 04:15:00" d="2020-10-31 04:40:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (913)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Grammy Award-winning duo The Chainsmokers join Rob, Chanel and Steelo to cringe at some &quot;biters&quot;, ride &quot;stolen mattresses&quot; and marvel at the magic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-10-31 04:40:00" d="2020-10-31 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (914)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo check out the fierce &quot;Lawn Warriors&quot;, learn some wisdom in &quot;Speak Your Mind&quot; and witness some &quot;furry fury&quot;. (S9, ep14)</k>  </p>
</a>
