<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2020-10-27 04:06:28"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 05:00:00" d="2020-11-03 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 07:00:00" d="2020-11-03 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (410)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% The Fashion Club tells (sub)urban legends to pass the time while they're stranded in a bad part of town; driving around Lawndale, Daria hears one of them. (S4, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 07:20:00" d="2020-11-03 07:45:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills II (210)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% Lauren's turning 21 and Heidi has big plans for the birthday bash. But, before the party, Heidi decides it's time to tell Lauren about Spencer's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 07:45:00" d="2020-11-03 08:10:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills II (211)</n><t>M</t>    <k>35% With a new job on the line, Whitney stumbles in her biggest opportunity with Teen Vogue. Spencer goes too far when he pressures Heidi to leave Lauren</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 08:10:00" d="2020-11-03 09:00:00"><n u="16 And Pregnant">16 And Pregnant I (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Not only is 16 year old Whitney pregnant, but so is her mother! Watch her prepare to become both a big sister and a mother. (S1, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 09:00:00" d="2020-11-03 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (516)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Leah starts medication for her anxiety. Kailyn and Javi visit Joe and Vee's apartment. Nathan prepares for jail and Jenelle worries about being alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 10:00:00" d="2020-11-03 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (517)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Jenelle struggles alone with Jace while Nathan is away. Leah and Jeremy clash over finances. Chelsea investigates Adam's legal charges from his accident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 11:00:00" d="2020-11-03 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning">Teen Mom 2: From The Beginning V (518)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Leah and Jeremy visit Ali's specialist. Jenelle and Nathan are reunited. Javi leaves for a work trip and Kailyn struggles with loneliness. Chelsea receives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 12:00:00" d="2020-11-03 13:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Homeless">Rich Kids Go Homeless I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Billionaire's son Bobby has a Ferrari and a private jet, and loves to party. But will his monied charms get results when he is sleeping rough? (S1, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 13:00:00" d="2020-11-03 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs III (302)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max are contacted by Carmen who is sounding the alarm on behalf of her cousin, Antwane. He's been in a three-year romance with a man named</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 14:00:00" d="2020-11-03 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs II (209)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Five months ago Artis met Jess online. Artis and Jess each were in relationships, but believed they'd found true love. But is Jess everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 15:00:00" d="2020-11-03 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs VII (739)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Justin Combs and Nev set out to help Cherie uncover Avion's identity, a mysterious stranger who contacted the 26-year-old sales rep after he bought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 16:00:00" d="2020-11-03 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs VII (713)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Tinder match ignited a fire for Jordan that caused Angel to end a real relationship to pursue him. Nev and his wife Laura uncover dark truths that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 17:00:00" d="2020-11-03 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs IV (405)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chitara took a big leap and came out to her family when she met Priscilla online, but Priscilla ended their relationship unexpectedly. Now Chitara</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 18:00:00" d="2020-11-03 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs V (508)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Joanna was about to meet her online love in the flesh, but a crazy night in Vegas caused the whole relationship to go sour. Now she's enlisted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 19:00:00" d="2020-11-03 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs IV (415)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>David is the only love Andria has ever known. Love letters and voice messages make Andria stay. But having never met after 10 years, she needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 20:00:00" d="2020-11-03 21:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Homeless">Rich Kids Go Homeless I (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Former ballet dancer Calum finds it difficult to cope on the streets, even when paired with Gert, a Belgian man left homeless after losing his benefits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 21:00:00" d="2020-11-03 22:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 X (1007)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Jade is caught between her mum and Sean, but a drug test could reveal the truth. Leah is forced to balance her growing concerns for Ali and supporting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 22:00:00" d="2020-11-03 22:30:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Get ready to snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! This week features Selling Sunset's notorious Christine Quinn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 22:30:00" d="2020-11-03 23:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Get ready to snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! The cult show is back, this week featuring US reality TV royalty Caitlyn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-03 23:00:00" d="2020-11-04 00:00:00"><n u="New: Geordie Shore: Nathan's Story">New: Geordie Shore: Nathan's Story I (107)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nathan lets us in to his boudoir to tell all about his life from playing with dollhouses in school to changing the face of reality TV. Hear the inside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 00:00:00" d="2020-11-04 01:00:00"><n u="Young, Dumb &amp; Banged Up In The Sun">Young, Dumb &amp; Banged Up In The Sun II (201)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Mat fell foul of the Indonesia's immigration and ended up in the country's notorious prison system. (S2, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 01:00:00" d="2020-11-04 01:30:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd V (501)</n><t>M</t>    <k>59% Ashton Kutcher plays practical jokes on unsuspecting celebrities. Today features Simon Cowell and Raven Simone. (S5, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 01:30:00" d="2020-11-04 02:00:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd V (505)</n><t>M</t>    <k>59% Ashton Kutcher plays practical jokes on unsuspecting celebrities. Today features Benjamin Mckenzie, Jason Bateman and Akon. (S5, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 02:00:00" d="2020-11-04 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Nathan's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Nathan's Best Bits XIII (1310)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In the series finale Chloe and Marty get flirty again, but can they really stay just good friends? Kyle gets some big news from Boss Anna, but the fallout</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 03:00:00" d="2020-11-04 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Nathan's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Nathan's Best Bits XV (1501)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The lads and lasses are back and there is an old friend joining the family. It's not long before the gang hit the toon and cracks start to show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 03:50:00" d="2020-11-04 04:15:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (924)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Sterling are joined by none other than Rob's dad, Gene Drydek, who teaches the gang about the power of magnets, that it's &quot;never too late&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 04:15:00" d="2020-11-04 04:40:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (925)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo celebrate summer vacation by getting 'Sand Blasted', take a trip to 'Painland' and party with 'The Bang Gang. (S9, ep25)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-11-04 04:40:00" d="2020-11-04 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (926)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Radio and TV star Charlemagne Tha God joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to &quot;put some respeck on my name&quot;, call out the &quot;donkeys of the day&quot; and realise</k>  </p>
</a>
