<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-10-23 04:48:37"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 05:23:00" d="2020-10-30 05:54:00"><n>Hermia, Darrifourcq, Ceccaldi - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Manuel Hermia, Sylvain Darrifourcq, and Valentin Ceccaldi perform as an unconventional trio consisting of saxophone, cello, and drums. Incorporating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 05:54:00" d="2020-10-30 07:00:00"><n>Smooth Series at NSJ: George Benson &amp; Kenny G</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast from the North Sea Jazz Archives presents a compilation with music of George Benson &amp; Kenny G</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 07:00:00" d="2020-10-30 08:05:00"><n>Louis Armstrong: Live in Australia</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1964 Louis Armstrong recorded his biggest-selling record, Hello, Dolly! He made assorted television appearances, especially in the 1950s and 1960s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 08:05:00" d="2020-10-30 09:21:00"><n>November Music: R. Frerichs/H. Alizadeh/Cello8ctet</n><t>M</t>    <k>The November Music festival in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands is the ultimate event for experiencing a broad range of music. It features a wonderful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 09:21:00" d="2020-10-30 10:14:00"><n>Marcus Miller: Thoughts on Miles</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this 2009 portrait of Marcus Miller, Miller looks back on his relationship with Miles Davis. He shares countless stories of the recording process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 10:14:00" d="2020-10-30 11:15:00"><n>Crossroads: From Highlife to Musette</n><t>M</t>    <k>A two-part documentary, narrated by Dee Dee Bridgwater. &quot;Part 2: From Highlife to Musette on the road where European and African music converge,&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 11:15:00" d="2020-10-30 12:21:00"><n>Tamara Murphy - Spirograph Studies</n><t>M</t>    <k>Spirograph Studies have leapt onto the Australian music scene with their detailed, textural approach to playing improvised music. Post-rock, post-jazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 12:21:00" d="2020-10-30 14:03:00"><n u="Duke Ellington: Jazz from Newport, Brussels">Duke Ellington: Jazz from Newport, Brussels, 1973</n><t>M</t>    <k>The foremost jazz composer and bandleader of the twentieth century, Duke Ellington, returns with his orchestra to the festival where he revived his career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 14:03:00" d="2020-10-30 14:47:00"><n>Colin Stetson Solo at Pitchfork</n><t>M</t>    <k>This impressive solo concert by Colin Stetso, an American saxophonist known for his unique musical style influenced by a wide range of jazz genres</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 14:47:00" d="2020-10-30 15:42:00"><n>McCoy Tyner Trio &amp; Ravi Coltrane - Jazz a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>The legendary pianist McCoy Tyner has become one of the most influential pianists in jazz history. As a member of the John Coltrane Quartet in the 1960s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 15:42:00" d="2020-10-30 17:21:00"><n>J.E. &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley live in Switzerland</n><t>M</t>    <k>Cannonball Adderley: Live in '63 boasts two beautifully filmed concerts from one of the most celebrated sextets in jazz history, captured at the top of their game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 17:21:00" d="2020-10-30 19:05:00"><n>Live at The Metro Theatre</n><t>M</t>    <k>Angus &amp; Julia Stone are an Australian brother-sister folk-blues group which formed in 2006. Their parents played as a folk duo before Julia and Angus were born</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 19:05:00" d="2020-10-30 20:04:00"><n>BIRDtv: Cecile McLorin Salvant</n><t>M</t>    <k>This BIRD.tv episode features a rising star on the jazz scene: within the last few years, vocalist Cécile McLorin Salvant (.1989) has risen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 20:04:00" d="2020-10-30 21:00:00"><n>Une Soirée de Poche: St. Paul &amp; The Broken Bones</n><t>M</t>    <k>Discover a thrilling performance by St. Paul and The Broken Bones, a soulful sextet from Birmingham, Alabama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 21:00:00" d="2020-10-30 22:34:00"><n>Incognito - Sing Jazz 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>Incognito is an acid jazz project formed by Jean-Paul &quot;Bluey&quot; Maunick and Paul &quot;Tubbs&quot; Williams, original members of the disco-funk Light of the World</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-30 22:34:00" d="2020-10-31 00:00:00"><n>Africa Live! The Concerts</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 00:00:00" d="2020-10-31 01:44:00"><n>The Story of Papa Wemba</n><t>M</t>    <k>Documentary film 'History of Papa Wemba' traces the story of the father of Congolese rumba: iconic, trailblazing and intergenerational music artist Papa Wemba</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 01:44:00" d="2020-10-31 02:31:00"><n>Matthew Whitaker - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>The American jazz pianist Matthew Whitaker is a major new voice on jazz piano, organ, and a wide range of keyboard instruments. He appears at jazzahead! 2019 with guitarist Marcos Robinson, bassist Karim Hutton, and drummer Isaiah Johnson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 02:31:00" d="2020-10-31 03:06:00"><n>Pauli Lyytinen Magnetia Orkesteri - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pauli Lyytinen Magnetia Orkesteri is a classic jazz quartet that doesn't sound classic - the fresh sound is instilled in the quartet's DNA. Mixing steady</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 03:06:00" d="2020-10-31 04:04:00"><n>The MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Hoera</n><t>M</t>    <k>This MotorMusic Jazz Sessions episode features the Belgian musicians of Hoera who love to create, produce, and present original work and concepts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 04:04:00" d="2020-10-31 05:05:00"><n>Terry Callier: Live in Berlin</n><t>M</t>    <k>Terry Callier, the man who has written music history in the 1960s and 1970s, returns to the stage after a 15 year break</k>  </p>
</a>
