<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-10-30 03:44:25"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 05:04:00" d="2020-11-06 05:32:00"><n>Fearless Trio - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Fearless Trio consists of pianist Simon Nabatov, drummer Fabian Arends, and saxophonist Johannes Ludwig, who also writes the music. Led by Ludwig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 05:32:00" d="2020-11-06 06:04:00"><n>Horse Orchestra - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Horse Orchestra experiments with different genres in jazz, hip-hop, and noise. Bringing virtuosity and eclecticism to the forefront, the septet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 06:04:00" d="2020-11-06 07:00:00"><n>Stift Festival: Suite del Ángel</n><t>M</t>    <k>Marcelo Nisinman, Alberto Mesirca, Daniel Rowland, Zoran Markovic, Natacha Kudritskaya</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 07:00:00" d="2020-11-06 08:06:00"><n>Les McCann: Live in New Orleans</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 08:06:00" d="2020-11-06 09:08:00"><n>Istanbul Sessions: Kerem Gorsev</n><t>M</t>    <k>Recognized as a composer of great talent, Kerem Görsev is one of the most gifted Turkish pianists of his generation. His trio, completed by Kagan Yildiz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 09:08:00" d="2020-11-06 10:14:00"><n>The Sound of New York - Luis Perdomo &amp; Mimi Jones</n><t>M</t>    <k>Born in 1971 in Caracas, Luis Perdomo began appearing on television and radio in Venezuela at the age of 12. Bassist and singer Mimi Jones, born Miriam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 10:14:00" d="2020-11-06 11:14:00"><n>Non Stop Travels: The Story of Michel Petrucciani</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 11:14:00" d="2020-11-06 11:55:00"><n>Lorren at the North Sea Jazz Club: Shades of Blue</n><t>M</t>    <k>With her relaxed, bright voice, vocalist Lorren has made her name on the Dutch jazz scene. In this 'Shades of Blue' concert, which was recorded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 11:55:00" d="2020-11-06 14:07:00"><n>Buddy Rich Big Band - The North Sea Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>Buddy Rich, one of the most influential jazz drummers of all time, performed at the North Sea Jazz Festival of 1978 with his orchestra. Rich's drumming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 14:07:00" d="2020-11-06 15:10:00"><n>Christian Scott - Jazz a Vienne 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Christian Scott aTunde Adjuah blends jazz fusion, hip-hop and alternative rock, developing a unique and distinct sound. Scott's performance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 15:10:00" d="2020-11-06 15:52:00"><n>Misc: Jérôme Beaulieu live in Montreal</n><t>M</t>    <k>Modern jazz with a twist, based on a group effort rather than on personal virtuosity: 'Misc'! The 'Trio Jérôme Beaulieu' quickly made a name for itself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 15:52:00" d="2020-11-06 17:03:00"><n>Episode 4: Stan Getz - Jazz Greats</n><t>M</t>    <k>American tenor saxophonist Stan Getz performed in bebop and cool jazz groups and helped popularize bossa nova in the USA. In 1983 he played in California's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 17:03:00" d="2020-11-06 18:49:00"><n>Live at The Hordern Pavilion</n><t>M</t>    <k>Big hits, booty dancing, stage dives, fan freestyles, A$AP Rocky's debut Down Under tour had it all! At his sold-out Sydney show, hip hop's hottest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 18:49:00" d="2020-11-06 20:06:00"><n>BIRDtv: Boogieball with The NPG and Questlove</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 20:06:00" d="2020-11-06 21:00:00"><n>Jacques Kuba Séguin: L'étude des Lueurs</n><t>M</t>    <k>Trumpeter Jacques Kuba Séguin's ensemble unites some of Montreal's most expressive musicians: double bassist Frédéric Alarie, pianist Jonathan Cayer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 21:00:00" d="2020-11-06 22:02:00"><n>Maceo Parker: Jazz a Juan</n><t>M</t>    <k>At 25, saxophonist Maceo Parker played in James Brown's band, but today he is also known for his collaborations with George Clinton's Parliament-Funkadelic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-06 22:02:00" d="2020-11-07 00:00:00"><n>STUFF. live at BIRD Rotterdam</n><t>M</t>    <k>Discover an irresistible live act! STUFF is full of unflagging energy. The band could be considered an avant-garde jazz band who play a mix of funk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-07 00:00:00" d="2020-11-07 01:17:00"><n>A Different Way: Rodolfo Mederos</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rodolfo Mederos is a bandoneonist, a composer with an enormous oeuvre, one of the authorities on the tango – and an inspiration to new generations of musicians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-07 01:17:00" d="2020-11-07 01:53:00"><n>The Kutimangoes - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>The KutiMangoes come from Denmark. Their musical style, however, is everything but Danish. Performing exotic Afrobeats inspired by Western African culture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-07 01:53:00" d="2020-11-07 02:42:00"><n>Linda May Han Oh - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Linda May Han Oh brings her quartet to jazzahead! 2019. This highly sought-after double bassist from Australia is also a productive composer, composing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-07 02:42:00" d="2020-11-07 03:47:00"><n>MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Nardozza - Bisceglia</n><t>M</t>    <k>Trumpeter Carlo Nardozza and pianist Michel Bisceglia combine their talents to create wonderful music with haunting melodies and beautiful themes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-07 03:47:00" d="2020-11-07 04:50:00"><n>Tonya Baker: Live at Jazz a Vienne Festival</n><t>M</t>    <k>Psalmist, gifted songwriter, author, instructor, workshop instructor, and gospel singer Tonya Baker travels the world to share her gift of singing and her great wisdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-07 04:50:00" d="2020-11-07 05:50:00"><n>Pomrad: Live at Jazz en Baie Festival</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pomrad, alias Adriaan van de Velde, an electronic producer from Antwerp, creates harmonious and colourful music blended with by '80s funk</k>  </p>
</a>
