<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2020-10-24 04:44:46"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 05:05:00" d="2020-10-31 05:38:00"><n u="Duets: Carla Bley and Steve Swallow in">Duets: Carla Bley and Steve Swallow in 1988</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1988 Steve Swallow and Carla Bley began performing duet concerts in Europe, the United States, South America and Japan. Duets, an album of their songs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 05:38:00" d="2020-10-31 07:00:00"><n u="Freddie Hubbard &amp; The Satchmo Legacy Live in">Freddie Hubbard &amp; The Satchmo Legacy Live in 1987</n><t>M</t>    <k>Estival offers a thrilling and particularly surprising line-up that explores the rich world of contemporary music. Freddie Hubbard is an American</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 07:00:00" d="2020-10-31 07:58:00"><n>Sam Moore &amp; The London Community Gospel Choir</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sam Moore is best known for his work with the historic soul duo Sam &amp; Dave. The rapid-fire style, built on the call and response of gospel, was fashioned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 07:58:00" d="2020-10-31 08:59:00"><n>Georgie Fame &amp; the Blue Flames</n><t>M</t>    <k>Georgie Fame, known for &quot;Yeh, Yeh&quot; and &quot;The Ballad of Bonnie and Clyde&quot; makes a triumphant comeback with The Blue Flames. This performance is brimming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 08:59:00" d="2020-10-31 10:10:00"><n>Dave Brubeck and Paul Desmond live in Belgium</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dave Brubeck: Live in '64 boasts a beautifully filmed concert from one of the most beloved quartets in jazz history. Paul Desmond (alto sax), Joe Morello</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 10:10:00" d="2020-10-31 10:50:00"><n>Odelion Orchestra - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>Odelion Orchestra is vocalist-composer Margriet Sjoerdsma's project with pianist Jeroen van Vliet, the electric string trio Westside Trio, and three horn players</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 10:50:00" d="2020-10-31 11:19:00"><n>Naissam Jalal Quest of the Invisible - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>In her trio, flutist Naissam Jalal brings together pianist Leonardo Montana and double bassist Claude Tchamitchian. The band's repertoire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 11:19:00" d="2020-10-31 11:49:00"><n>Kuba Wiecek Trio - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Polish saxophonist Kuba Wiecek is only 23 years old, but his trio has already made its mark on the Polish jazz scene by placing a heavy focus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 11:49:00" d="2020-10-31 14:05:00"><n>Fred Hersch Trio - Jazz a Ramatuelle</n><t>M</t>    <k>At the age of 63, Fred Hersch is unquestionably one of today's key figures in jazz piano. Supported by John Hebert (double bass) and Eric McPherson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 14:05:00" d="2020-10-31 15:24:00"><n>Terrasson &amp; Belmondo: A Nous Garo</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 15:24:00" d="2020-10-31 15:45:00"><n>Live at the Office: BIGYUKI &amp; Now vs Now</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into Rotterdam's BIRD club, named after New Yorker saxophonist Charlie Parker. Discover a fantastic live concert deeply rooted in jazz, funk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 15:45:00" d="2020-10-31 16:24:00"><n>Seine Sessions: Funk &amp; Afro</n><t>M</t>    <k>Entitled &quot;Funk &amp; Afro&quot;, this episode of the Seine Sessions (2016) hosted by Eddy King presents unique performances, and interviews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 16:24:00" d="2020-10-31 17:41:00"><n>Tinariwen: Concert Bouffes du Nord</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Malian-Berber band Tinariwen performed a one-off acoustic concert at the Théâtre des Bouffes du Nord in Paris during their European tour in the spring of 2011</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 17:41:00" d="2020-10-31 18:34:00"><n>Final Step Live @ Il Magazzino: Three Sails</n><t>M</t>    <k>From the polyglot border region of Ticino in Switzerland – well-known for its beautiful Lake Maggiore and the International Film Festival in Locarno</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 18:34:00" d="2020-10-31 19:16:00"><n>Conservatory Concert Big Band</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 19:16:00" d="2020-10-31 20:10:00"><n u="Rahsaan Roland Kirk Live in">Rahsaan Roland Kirk Live in 1964</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rahsaan Roland Kirk: Live in '64 presents an astounding concert by this musical superhero playing his entire instrumental arsenal of saxophone, flute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 20:10:00" d="2020-10-31 21:00:00"><n u="Sarah Vaughan &quot;The Divine One&quot; in">Sarah Vaughan &quot;The Divine One&quot; in 1958</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sarah Vaughan: Live in '58 &amp; 64 features the Divine One in her prime, wrapping her sultry voice around jazz standards such as &quot;Lover Man&quot;, &quot;Misty&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 21:00:00" d="2020-10-31 21:54:00"><n u="Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas - Music Meeting">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas - Music Meeting 2020</n><t>M</t>    <k>Music Meeting 2020 presents this exclusive concert by pianist Ramón Valle and guitarist Reinier Baas, filmed at Concertgebouw De Vereeniging in Nijmegen, The Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-10-31 21:54:00" d="2020-11-01 00:00:00"><n>Ricardo Herz Trio - Da Pá Virada Sessions</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Ricardo Herz Trio consists of Ricardo Herz on violin, Michi Ruzitschka on nylon string guitar, and Pedro Ito on percussion. Band leader Ricardo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 00:00:00" d="2020-11-01 01:06:00"><n>Edina Mokus - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Edina Szirtes Mokus, expresses her talents with her own projects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 01:06:00" d="2020-11-01 01:44:00"><n>Freedoms Trio - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Freedoms Trio is an international project consisting of Norwegian Steinar Aadnekvam, Brazilian Rubem Farias, and Deodato Siquir from Mozambique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 01:44:00" d="2020-11-01 02:21:00"><n>Max Andrzejewski's Hutte - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Max Andrzejewski's HUTTE is a Berlin-based band that has already released two very successful albums. Always highly energetic, adventurous, and expressive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 02:21:00" d="2020-11-01 03:55:00"><n>Jazzed Out Swiss</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazzed Out proves that a jazz session can take place anywhere. In this episode, Zurich serves as a backdrop to sets by pianist Stefan Rusconi and Grand Pianoramax</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 03:55:00" d="2020-11-01 04:40:00"><n>Jazz Legends: Show Time at the Blue Note</n><t>M</t>    <k>This show at the Blue Note takes us back to 1967 for an amazing night of jazz at the Blue Note Jazz Club in Brussels. Featuring Ted Curson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 04:40:00" d="2020-11-01 05:33:00"><n u="Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas - Music Meeting">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas - Music Meeting 2020</n><t>M</t>    <k>Music Meeting 2020 presents this exclusive concert by pianist Ramón Valle and guitarist Reinier Baas, filmed at Concertgebouw De Vereeniging in Nijmegen, The Netherlands</k>  </p>
</a>
