<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-10-25 03:45:41"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 05:33:00" d="2020-11-01 06:12:00"><n>LoLanders - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>The band LoLanders consists of six musical friends and individuals who play inspired new music that combines the passion and traditions of Scotland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 06:12:00" d="2020-11-01 07:00:00"><n>Rita Reys &amp; The Pim Jacobs Trio at North Sea Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast from the North Sea Jazz Archives presents &quot;Europe's First Lady of Song&quot;, popular Dutch jazz vocalist Rita Reys, accompanied by husband</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 07:00:00" d="2020-11-01 08:14:00"><n>Artvark Saxophone Quartet &amp; Ntjam Rosie: Homelands</n><t>M</t>    <k>Homelands is a collaboration between Artvark Saxophone Quartet and Cameroonian-Dutch singer Ntjam Rosie. The music is inspired by both traditional</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 08:14:00" d="2020-11-01 09:18:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Avi Lebovich Orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>The legendary Yellow Submarine Jazz Club in Jerusalem presents trombonist Avi Lebovich and his Orchestra. The Orchestra is a contemporary incarnation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 09:18:00" d="2020-11-01 10:04:00"><n>Agnes Gosling Quartet - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>Agnes Gosling has matured as a writer and arranger. With her quartet, Gosling honors the tradition of great acoustic jazz while exploring new sounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 10:04:00" d="2020-11-01 11:21:00"><n>Live at The Metro Theatre</n><t>M</t>    <k>The unconventional Sia Kate Isobelle Furler, simply known as Sia, has gained worldwide attention over the last few years. Her unique stage presence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 11:21:00" d="2020-11-01 12:29:00"><n>Sarah Vaughan Live in '58 &amp; 64: The Divine One</n><t>M</t>    <k>This concert features the Divine One in her prime, wrapping her sultry voice around jazz standards such as Lover Man. Performances like these demonstrate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 12:29:00" d="2020-11-01 12:44:00"><n>BIRDtv: Hypnotic Brass Ensemble</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rotterdam's BIRD is a club, café, and restaurant with a live music program that's deeply rooted in jazz. This episode is dedicated to seven brothers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 12:44:00" d="2020-11-01 14:14:00"><n>Ray Charles live at North Sea Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast from the North Sea Jazz Archives presents a compilation with music of Ray Charles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 14:14:00" d="2020-11-01 14:53:00"><n>Paradox Live: Bertus Borgers &amp; The Young Retro's</n><t>M</t>    <k>PARADOX Tilburg is the most intimate jazz club in the Netherlands, with a devoted audience from all across Europe. This episode of PARADOX LIVE presents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 14:53:00" d="2020-11-01 16:09:00"><n>Memoirs of a Hip 'Ole Black Man</n><t>M</t>    <k>His hands move with the speed of light, and his warm voice caresses his listeners' hearts and minds. Vinx De'Jon Parrette i's a true artist, passionate for his art. (2015)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 16:09:00" d="2020-11-01 16:41:00"><n>SWART. - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>SWART. is a modern jazz group founded by the Dutch saxophonist and composer Celia Swart. SWART.'s live performances balance intellectual creative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 16:41:00" d="2020-11-01 17:20:00"><n u="Miriam Makeba Live at Estival Lugano">Miriam Makeba Live at Estival Lugano 1985</n><t>M</t>    <k>Miriam Makeba, also named Mama Africa, was a South African singer, actress, United Nations goodwill ambassador, and civil-rights activist. She brought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 17:20:00" d="2020-11-01 19:20:00"><n>Florian Favre Trio - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianist Florian Favre has already earned a firm place on the Swiss jazz scene. His trio, with Manu Hagmann on bass and Arthur Hnatek on drums, performs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 19:20:00" d="2020-11-01 21:00:00"><n>Elliot Galvin Trio - November Music</n><t>M</t>    <k>The pianist Elliot Galvin is a member of the young UK jazz group Dinosaur. Performing with his own trio, the gifted musician has been compared to Django</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 21:00:00" d="2020-11-01 22:05:00"><n>Dave Brubeck Quartet - The North Sea Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Dave Brubeck Quartet played an unforgettable concert at the North Sea Jazz Festival of 1982. The American jazz pianist was one of the first to weave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 22:05:00" d="2020-11-01 22:45:00"><n>John Coltrane: Live in Comblain-la-Tour</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast of John Coltrane's 1965 performance at the short-lived Belgian jazz festival in Comblain-la-Tour features Trane's classic quartet with Elvin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 22:45:00" d="2020-11-01 23:24:00"><n>Angel Forrest Show 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>There is no question that Angel is one of the most powerful singers on the contemporary blues scene today. The strength of her performances has allowed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-01 23:24:00" d="2020-11-02 00:00:00"><n>Visions of Music: The Arabian Connection</n><t>M</t>    <k>The fascinating documentary Visions of Music - The Arabian Connection is mainly narrated by Rabih Abou-Khalil, who puts in context the history of music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 00:00:00" d="2020-11-02 01:34:00"><n>Lucky Chops - Live at BIRD</n><t>M</t>    <k>Formed in 2006, the NYC-based band Lucky Chops first caught the attention of the masses when a video of their performance at a subway station went viral</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 01:34:00" d="2020-11-02 02:07:00"><n>The Sound of New York - Mark Turner</n><t>M</t>    <k>Mark Turner has developed a distinctive and highly personal style. His demanding compositional approach, his sharp improvisational skills and his great</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 02:07:00" d="2020-11-02 03:24:00"><n>Klischee - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Klischee is one of Switzerland's most in-demand live acts. Although it started out as a studio project, this band soon transformed into a stage favorite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 03:24:00" d="2020-11-02 04:10:00"><n>The MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Jasper Somsen Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>This MotorMusic Jazz Sessions episode features the Dutch Jasper Somsen with his trio. Their dig into free form improvisations results in short suites</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 04:10:00" d="2020-11-02 05:12:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Yaron Herman and Avishai Cohen</n><t>M</t>    <k>For this session in Jerusalem's Yellow Submarine, pianist Yaron Herman invited trumpeter Avishai Cohen. Both musicians are considered among the very finest</k>  </p>
</a>
