<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-10-26 03:44:50"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 05:12:00" d="2020-11-02 07:00:00"><n>New Cool Collective: Live in Luxor</n><t>M</t>    <k>Since 1993, the Dutch band New Cool Collective has been a unique mix of jazz, dance, latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo. This concert features special</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 07:00:00" d="2020-11-02 07:33:00"><n>Dionne Warwick live at the 27 Club</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dionne Warwick's vocal artistry ranges from voluminous deep register to soft, fragile high notes. She masters the entire range with almost unnerving ease</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 07:33:00" d="2020-11-02 09:15:00"><n>Dee Dee Bridgewater: Red Earth</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this film, Grammy-winning American jazz singer Dee Dee Bridgewater explores her Malian roots. Aided by producer Cheick Tidiane Seck, she works</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 09:15:00" d="2020-11-02 10:11:00"><n>Tim Kliphuis and the NCO: The Changing Seasons</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Netherlands Chamber Orchestra commissioned violinist Tim Kliphuis, internationally known for his genre-crossing approach to music, to write</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 10:11:00" d="2020-11-02 11:45:00"><n>Scott DuBois Quartet Live In Munich</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rising star of the jazz guitar Scott DuBois leads his quartet, consisting of Gebhard Ullmann (reeds), Thomas Morgan (bass), and Kresten Osgood (drums)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 11:45:00" d="2020-11-02 12:19:00"><n u="Jazz a Antibes Juan-les-Pins: John McLaughlin">Jazz a Antibes Juan-les-Pins: John McLaughlin 1</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 12:19:00" d="2020-11-02 14:08:00"><n>Tinariwen: Concert Bouffes du Nord</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Malian-Berber band Tinariwen performed a one-off acoustic concert at the Théâtre des Bouffes du Nord in Paris during their European tour in the spring of 2011</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 14:08:00" d="2020-11-02 15:23:00"><n>Kim Hoorweg at BIRD, Rotterdam</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kim Hoorweg landed her first record deal at the young age of 14. Since then, the Dutch singer has been involved in various music projects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 15:23:00" d="2020-11-02 15:59:00"><n>Toko Telo - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Malagasy power trio Toko Telo, combines dazzling musicianship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 15:59:00" d="2020-11-02 18:02:00"><n>Yves Theiler Trio - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Yves Theiler Trio plays contemporary jazz full of intricate rhythms. Never losing their wide appeal, the three musicians play contrasting polyrhythms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 18:02:00" d="2020-11-02 18:31:00"><n>The Hammond© Sessions: Dede Priest</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this series, Rob Mostert and the Hammond B3 organ take center stage, accompanied by the world's finest jazz musicians for a musical collaboration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 18:31:00" d="2020-11-02 19:14:00"><n u="29th Street Saxophone Quartet: Estival">29th Street Saxophone Quartet: Estival 1987</n><t>M</t>    <k>The 29th Street Saxophone Quartet is an American quartet founded in 1982 by alto saxophonists Bobby Watson and Ed Jackson, tenor saxophonist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 19:14:00" d="2020-11-02 20:08:00"><n>Emilia Martensson - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>London based Emilia Martensson won the 'Vocalist of the Year-2016' award at The Parliamentary Jazz Awards. Heavily inspired by her native southern Swedish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 20:08:00" d="2020-11-02 21:00:00"><n>TorTube: Tingvall Trio - Vägen</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of TorTube entitled Vägen (2016), features iconic Swedish jazz pianist Martin Tingvall and his trio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 21:00:00" d="2020-11-02 22:06:00"><n>Etienne Mbappe - Jazzwoche Burghausen</n><t>M</t>    <k>The talented Cameroonian bassist and singer songwriter Etienne Mbappé surrounds himself with upcoming jazz talent from Paris in his band The Prophets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 22:06:00" d="2020-11-02 22:38:00"><n>Charles Lloyd Quartet live in Brussels</n><t>M</t>    <k>This 1966 recording features Charles Lloyd's quartet, accompanied by Keith Jarrett (piano), Cecil McBee (double bass) and Jack DeJohnette (drums), playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-02 22:38:00" d="2020-11-03 00:00:00"><n>Dee Dee Bridgewater: Motherland</n><t>M</t>    <k>With 'Red Earth', American singer Dee Dee Bridgewater goes on a Malian journey that merges and melds all borders. She brings her own experiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 00:00:00" d="2020-11-03 01:00:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: Blossom</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Morgenland Chamber Orchestra has been an integral part of the Morgenland Festival since 2009. This ensemble of musicians from Germany and various guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 01:00:00" d="2020-11-03 02:46:00"><n>David Murray Quartet feat. Saul Williams - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>David Murray researched the relationship between avant-garde and tradition in a way that makes him stand out among his saxophonist peers. For his latest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 02:46:00" d="2020-11-03 03:51:00"><n>The Art Farmer Quartet live In England</n><t>M</t>    <k>Art Farmer: Live in '64 highlights an amazing one-hour concert featuring the great flugelhornist in his prime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 03:51:00" d="2020-11-03 06:43:00"><n>Sao Paulo Samba</n><t>M</t>    <k>Orquestra Sinfônica do Estado de Sao Paulo, John Neschling</k>  </p>
</a>
