<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-10-28 03:51:17"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 05:27:00" d="2020-11-04 05:59:00"><n>Seine Sessions: World Music</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of Seine Sessions 'World Music', presented by Eddy King, shows unique performances and interviews of among Teófilo Chantre, Tiwitine and Kinsy Ray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 05:59:00" d="2020-11-04 07:00:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: A Trace of Grace</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode entitled &quot;A Trace Of Grace&quot; features the rich and complex music of Michel Godard and Kayhan Kalhor, two musicians interested in instruments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 07:00:00" d="2020-11-04 08:01:00"><n>Rhoda Scott &amp; La Velle: Hammond, Soul and Blues</n><t>M</t>    <k>Although American soul and jazz organist Rhoda Scott spent most of her career in France, this performance at the antique theatre of Vienne is special</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 08:01:00" d="2020-11-04 09:02:00"><n>Michel Petrucciani Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>Recorded in Stuttgart in 1998, this performance features pianist Michel Petrucciani, drummer Steve Gadd and bassist Anthony Jackson. The musicians achieve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 09:02:00" d="2020-11-04 10:05:00"><n>Comblain-la-Tour Jazz Festival: Jimmy McGriff Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>Of the major soul-jazz pioneers, Hammond B3 organ player Jimmy McGriff (1936-2008) was the bluesiest and often insisted that he was more of a blues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 10:05:00" d="2020-11-04 10:58:00"><n u="Tania Maria: Live at Estival Lugano">Tania Maria: Live at Estival Lugano 1987</n><t>M</t>    <k>This performance of Brazilian Tania Maria promises to make you want to dance. The singer, composer and pianist sets fire to the Estival scene with her pop and jazzy song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 10:58:00" d="2020-11-04 12:02:00"><n u="The Crusaders: Estival Lugano">The Crusaders: Estival Lugano 1987</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Crusaders, an American jazz fusion group that was popular in the '70s. Their performance at Estival is beyond soulful and an amazing show to watch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 12:02:00" d="2020-11-04 13:02:00"><n>Erik Truffaz Quartet - WorldStock Festival</n><t>M</t>    <k>Known for his fusion of rock, hip-hop, electronic music and jazz, trumpeter Erik Truffaz is joined on stage by Marcello Giuliani on bass, Benoit Carboz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 13:02:00" d="2020-11-04 14:05:00"><n>The Sound of New York - Stefon Harris</n><t>M</t>    <k>The passionate play, the energetic stage presence and the amazing virtuosity of vibraphonist Stefon Harris have propelled him to the forefront of the current jazz scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 14:05:00" d="2020-11-04 15:30:00"><n>Play Your Own Thing: A Story Of Jazz In Europe</n><t>M</t>    <k>„Play Your Own Thing&quot; portrays the development of jazz in Europe with its emancipation and expertise, its freedom and individualism, the development</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 15:30:00" d="2020-11-04 16:11:00"><n>Ornithology - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Guitarist Silvan Jeger expanded his solo project Ornithology into a trio with bassist Jan Roder and drummer Dieter Ulrich. At Moods, Ornithology explores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 16:11:00" d="2020-11-04 17:48:00"><n>A. Shepp &quot;Swinging The Blues&quot; - Jazz a La Villette</n><t>M</t>    <k>Archie Shepp's name has made it into the majority of jazz history books. Known for his explosive and free improvisations, the saxophonist pays tribute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 17:48:00" d="2020-11-04 18:29:00"><n>Nelida Karr - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Nelida Karr, sings, plays various instruments. Her music reflects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 18:29:00" d="2020-11-04 19:22:00"><n>Mister Joe Williams and the Basie Alumni Band</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Count Basie Alumni Band is joined by Joe Williams for a bluesy performance at the Brussels Jazz Club in 1980</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 19:22:00" d="2020-11-04 20:26:00"><n>MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Linus</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of the DJAZZ series &quot;Belgium Sessions,&quot; presents 'Linus', a duo of two composers and improvisers: baritone guitar player Ruben Machtelinckx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 20:26:00" d="2020-11-04 21:00:00"><n>The Sound of New York - Bilal</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bilal Sayeed Oliver, better known as Bilal, is an American singer-songwriter and producer currently residing in New York. Hailed by the public and critics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 21:00:00" d="2020-11-04 21:34:00"><n>Cecile McLorin Salvant Quartet - Jazz a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>Singer Cecile McLorin Salvant performs vaudeville, country, blues, broadway songs, rarities, and her own compositions. An audience member once described</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 21:34:00" d="2020-11-05 00:00:00"><n>Remember Häns'che Weiss - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>French guitar virtuoso Biréli Lagrene pays tribute to one of the most prominent exponents of gipsy jazz: German guitarist Häns'che Weiss (1951-2016)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-05 00:00:00" d="2020-11-05 01:11:00"><n>November Music 2017: Daniel Herskedal</n><t>M</t>    <k>Norwegian tuba player and composer Daniel Herskedal trained at the Trondheim and Copenhagen Music Conservatories. He is at the head of a formidable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-05 01:11:00" d="2020-11-05 02:40:00"><n>Casper the Funky Ghost: Bootsy Collins a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bootsy Collins' syncopated, hard and relentlessly rhythmic music strongly influenced funk music's development. Now in his 60s, Bootsy maintains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-05 02:40:00" d="2020-11-05 04:07:00"><n>Live at The Metro Theatre</n><t>M</t>    <k>Last year Alabama Shakes' debut record 'Boys &amp; Girls' arrived like a lightning bolt, seducing us with its blues-infused rock 'n' roots and Southern soul charms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-05 04:07:00" d="2020-11-05 04:40:00"><n>Marion Williams Sings Spirituals</n><t>M</t>    <k>You can't help but be carried away by the powerful voice Marion Williams, who, with backing from her group and backup singers, sings gospel songs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-05 04:40:00" d="2020-11-05 05:37:00"><n>Istanbul Sessions: Ilhan Ersahin's Wonderland</n><t>M</t>    <k>In the Babylon Jazz Club saxophonist Ilhan Ersahin plays a concert with his project Wonderland. The formation, completed by great gipsy clarinetist Hüsnü</k>  </p>
</a>
