<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-10-27 04:11:20"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 06:43:00" d="2020-11-03 07:00:00"><n>Thelonious Monk Quartet in Belgium</n><t>M</t>    <k>Thelonious Monk: Live in '65 features an intimate concert filmed three days apart in Belgium in the Winter of 1965 with a legendary quartet that includes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 07:00:00" d="2020-11-03 08:28:00"><n>Terrasson &amp; Belmondo: A Nous Garo</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 08:28:00" d="2020-11-03 09:20:00"><n>Lex Jasper Trio: Happy Days Are Here Again</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 09:20:00" d="2020-11-03 10:05:00"><n>Visions of Music: The Latin Tinge</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this episode of the Visions of Music series, Tito Puente explains the origins of Latin jazz, a trend founded in the '30s and' 40s by Dizzy Gillespie and Chano Pozo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 10:05:00" d="2020-11-03 11:18:00"><n>Manu Lanvin &amp; The Devil Blues a La Traverse</n><t>M</t>    <k>Released in 2016, Manu Lanvin's Blues, Booze &amp; Rock 'N' Roll album has been praised by the music community for its ever-growing fan base</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 11:18:00" d="2020-11-03 12:27:00"><n>Trio Chemirani: Dawâr</n><t>M</t>    <k>The veritable tombak virtuosos of Trio Chemirani, consisting of Chemirani Senior and Juniors, enrapture the Festival de Saintes. The Trio Chemirani's music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 12:27:00" d="2020-11-03 13:19:00"><n>Africa Live! The Concerts</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 13:19:00" d="2020-11-03 14:06:00"><n>Frank Paavo Quintet - JazzConnect, Westbroek</n><t>M</t>    <k>The saxophonist Frank Paavo has been active on the Amsterdam and Netherland's jazz scene since the early 1980s. His music is inspired by the hard-bop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 14:06:00" d="2020-11-03 15:05:00"><n>Brussels Jazz Orchestra &amp; Bert Joris - Big Valses</n><t>M</t>    <k>Founded in 1993 by Frank Vaganée, Serge Plume and Marc Godfroid, the Brussels Jazz Orchestra is recognised and has been subsidised by the Flemish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 15:05:00" d="2020-11-03 16:35:00"><n>Al Di Meola: One of These Nights</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 16:35:00" d="2020-11-03 17:02:00"><n>Daniel Erdmann's Velvet Revolution - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Velvet Revolution redefines what music can be in the 21st century: vivid, live, and unafraid to use force and power when the music asks for it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 17:02:00" d="2020-11-03 17:31:00"><n>Kirke Karja Quartet - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kirke Karja is a new face on the Estonian jazz scene. Yet, the pianist has become one of the brightest young musicians within the homeland's jazz circles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 17:31:00" d="2020-11-03 18:40:00"><n>MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: De Beren Gieren</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Dutch-Belgian acoustic-electronic piano threesome 'De Beren Gieren' ('The Bears Shriek', 'Les Ours Vautours') are known for their unique energetic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 18:40:00" d="2020-11-03 20:03:00"><n>Tivoli Utrecht: Sven Hammond Soul</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 20:03:00" d="2020-11-03 21:00:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: The Art of Duo</n><t>M</t>    <k>&quot;The Art of Duo&quot; presents an unprecedented duo featuring pianist Salman Gambarov and sheng player, a Chinese mouth-organ, Wu Wei</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 21:00:00" d="2020-11-03 22:04:00"><n u="Blue Note: A Story of Modern Jazz - Part">Blue Note: A Story of Modern Jazz - Part II</n><t>M</t>    <k>&quot;Blue Note - A Story of Modern Jazz&quot; tells the story of Alfred Lion and Francis Wolff and their record label. It is the story of the rise of Modern Jazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 22:04:00" d="2020-11-03 23:02:00"><n>Keita, Tinariwen Maal &amp; Sangare: Africa Live!</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-03 23:02:00" d="2020-11-04 00:00:00"><n>John Coltrane: Live in Comblain-la-Tour</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast of John Coltrane's 1965 performance at the short-lived Belgian jazz festival in Comblain-la-Tour features Trane's classic quartet with Elvin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 00:00:00" d="2020-11-04 00:30:00"><n>Mario Batkovic - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Mario Batkovic, aims to explore the sonic possibilities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 00:30:00" d="2020-11-04 01:46:00"><n>10th Anniversary: JazzArt Orchestra &amp; Friends</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazz, funk, or soul: the JazzArt Orchestra tackles each genre without batting an eye. One of the orchestra's ambitions is to cooperate with other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 01:46:00" d="2020-11-04 02:28:00"><n>Sammy Price and his All Star Orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>Texan pianist Sammy Price (1908-1992) played everything from blues and boogie-woogie to swing and jump-blues. Starting in Dallas as a singer and dancer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 02:28:00" d="2020-11-04 02:56:00"><n>Paradox Live: Jeroen van Vliet Moon Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>In the TV show PARADOX LIVE (2016) you get a taste of the greatest concerts and interviews with artists from all around the world. This episode of PARADOX</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 02:56:00" d="2020-11-04 03:47:00"><n>The Mel Lewis Orchestra live at Estival Lugano</n><t>M</t>    <k>Estival offers a thrilling and particularly surprising line-up that explores the rich world of contemporary music. The Mel Lewis Orchestra was arguably</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-11-04 03:47:00" d="2020-11-04 05:27:00"><n>Aki Rissanen Trio at Jazzclub Unterfahrt, Munich</n><t>M</t>    <k>Live from 'Jazzclub Unterfahrt' in Munich, Germany, Finnish pianist Aki Rissanen performs his original compositions. Together with Antti Lotjonen</k>  </p>
</a>
