<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2020-10-23 04:49:01"><p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 07:00:00" d="2020-10-30 07:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby/Cardiff 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Derby County take on Cardiff City at Pride Park in the 2017-18 campaign in a match with implications</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 07:15:00" d="2020-10-30 07:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby/Leeds 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Derby County take on Marcelo Bielsa's Leeds United at Pride Park in a Championship match that saw five goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 07:30:00" d="2020-10-30 07:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: West Brom/Leeds 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, West Brom take on Leeds United at The Hawthorns in a high-scoring Championship match that saw one side dominate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 07:45:00" d="2020-10-30 08:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic V Rangers '96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic meet Rangers in November 1996 at Celtic Park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 08:00:00" d="2020-10-30 08:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: David Villa</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series looking at some of football's greats. Here, a look at Spanish striker David Villa, a record goalscorer for his country, and a UEFA European</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 08:30:00" d="2020-10-30 09:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Goals</n><t>O</t>    <k>From spectacular volleys, to the perfect team move, enjoy the greatest goals in football history. With exclusive interviews with the likes of Marco</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 09:00:00" d="2020-10-30 09:30:00"><n>Football Years: 94/95</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some memorable seasons in the world of football. Here, the focus is on the 1994-1995 campaign, which saw surprise league winners in England and France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 09:30:00" d="2020-10-30 09:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: A. Villa/B'ham 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Aston Villa host Birmingham City at Villa Park in a high-scoring Second City derby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 09:45:00" d="2020-10-30 10:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: A. Villa/Forest 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Aston Villa host Nottingham Forest at Villa Park in an enthralling, end-to-end encounter that saw 10 goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 10:00:00" d="2020-10-30 10:15:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers V Celtic '97</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers meet Celtic in the top flight back in a vital clash in the 1996-97 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 10:15:00" d="2020-10-30 10:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '98</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic face Rangers in the top flight back in 1998</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 10:30:00" d="2020-10-30 11:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Cafu</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, remember Brazilian legend Cafu, a two-time World Cup winner, and his country's most capped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 11:00:00" d="2020-10-30 11:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Transfers</n><t>O</t>    <k>A football transfer can cost millions or nothing at all. Some can transform a club. Some can rock it to its core. This show counts downs the most important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 11:30:00" d="2020-10-30 12:00:00"><n>Football Years 95/96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive the 1995-96 season as the Bosman ruling changed football. Plus, England hosted the Euros, Auxerre and Atletico Madrid were surprise league winners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 12:00:00" d="2020-10-30 13:00:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: League 2 19/20</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Sky Bet League Two Play-Off final from Wembley Stadium, as two teams battle it out to reach League One</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 13:00:00" d="2020-10-30 13:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Charlton/S'land '98</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic clash from the English Football League - here, rewind to May 1998 for the First Division play-off final at Wembley, as Charlton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 13:15:00" d="2020-10-30 13:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Gillingham/M.City '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic match from the English Football League. Here, remember the thrilling 1998-99 Second Division play-off final between Gillingham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 13:30:00" d="2020-10-30 13:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Bolton v Watford '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic match from the English Football League. Here, Bolton Wanderers and Watford face off in the First Division play-off final at Wembley back in 1999</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 13:45:00" d="2020-10-30 14:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers take on Celtic in the top flight back in 1999</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 14:00:00" d="2020-10-30 14:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Baresi</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, Italian legend Franco Baresi, who spent his entire club career at Milan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 14:30:00" d="2020-10-30 15:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Entertainers</n><t>O</t>    <k>Celebrate some of the game's greatest entertainers - the players who make football fun. Featuring exclusive interviews with Zlatan Ibrahimovic, Ronaldinho and Gheorghe Hagi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 15:00:00" d="2020-10-30 15:30:00"><n>Football Years 96/97</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1996-1997 football season, as an African nation won a major tournament for the first time, one of the decade's finest goals was scored</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 15:30:00" d="2020-10-30 16:30:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: League 1 19/20</n><t>O</t>    <k>With a place in the Sky Bet Championship on the line, the two League One play-off finalists go head-to-head at Wembley Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 16:30:00" d="2020-10-30 16:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Bolton/Preston '01</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic clash from the Football League. Here, Bolton Wanderers and Preston North End meet in the First Division play-off final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 16:45:00" d="2020-10-30 17:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Sheff Utd/Wolves '03</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic English Football League clash. Here, Sheffield United and Wolves meet in the First Division play-off final at the Millennium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 17:00:00" d="2020-10-30 17:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: N.Forest/Yeovil '07</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic clash from the English Football League. Here, Nottingham Forest face Yeovil in their Sky Bet League One play-off semi-final second</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 17:15:00" d="2020-10-30 17:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers travel to Celtic Park in 1999, knowing a win against rivals Celtic would clinch the Scottish title</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 17:30:00" d="2020-10-30 18:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Del Piero</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, a look at Italian forward Alessandro Del Piero, who holds the record for both goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 18:00:00" d="2020-10-30 18:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns - Captains</n><t>O</t>    <k>Some of the most inspirational players in football, these are the greatest captains of all time. With exclusive interviews with the likes of Carles Puyol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 18:30:00" d="2020-10-30 19:00:00"><n>Football Years: 97/98</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1997-1998 football season, as Ronaldo and Rivaldo made major moves in European football, Arsenal won the double, and France claimed the World Cup on home soil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 19:00:00" d="2020-10-30 20:00:00"><n>New: The Women's Football Show</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at all the latest headlines, news and major talking points from around the world of women's football, with special guests joining to offer their insight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-10-30 20:00:00" d="2020-10-30 23:00:00"><n>Live EFL: Coventry v Reading</n><t>O</t>  </p>
</a>
