<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="36" t="2020-10-30 03:44:50"><p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 05:00:00" d="2020-11-06 06:00:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: League 1 16/17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Bradford City face Millwall at Wembley in the Sky Bet League 1 play-off final, as the teams battle for a spot in next season's Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 06:00:00" d="2020-11-06 07:00:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: League 2 16/17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Exeter City meet Blackpool at Wembley Stadium in the final of the Sky Bet League 2 play-offs. The two meetings in the season ended in a draw and a Blackpool win</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 07:00:00" d="2020-11-06 07:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Leeds v A.Villa '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Leeds United face Aston Villa in the Sky Bet Championship, with the sides meeting in the league</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 07:15:00" d="2020-11-06 07:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: H'field v Leeds 2017</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, a West Yorkshire derby as Huddersfield Town play Leeds United in 2017 in the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 07:30:00" d="2020-11-06 07:45:00"><n u="EFL Greatest:Sheff Wed/N'castle">EFL Greatest:Sheff Wed/N'castle 17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Sheffield Wednesday take on Newcastle United in 2017 in the Sky Bet Championship, with both sides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 07:45:00" d="2020-11-06 08:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic meet Rangers in a tense encounter in the final Old Firm derby of 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 08:00:00" d="2020-11-06 08:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: George Weah</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, Liberian striker George Weah, who was 1995 FIFA World Player of the Year, and a champion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 08:30:00" d="2020-11-06 09:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Entertainers</n><t>O</t>    <k>Celebrate some of the game's greatest entertainers - the players who make football fun. Featuring exclusive interviews with Zlatan Ibrahimovic, Ronaldinho and Gheorghe Hagi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 09:00:00" d="2020-11-06 09:30:00"><n>Football Years 96/97</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1996-1997 football season, as an African nation won a major tournament for the first time, one of the decade's finest goals was scored</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 09:30:00" d="2020-11-06 09:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Fulham v A.Villa '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember some classic matches from English football. In this episode, Fulham looked to maintain their playoff hopes against Aston Villa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 09:45:00" d="2020-11-06 10:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: N.Forest/Ipswich '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Nottingham Forest look to avoid relegation from the Sky Bet Championship as they face Ipswich Town in May 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 10:00:00" d="2020-11-06 10:15:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Hearts v Rangers '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Hearts host Rangers in October 2017 in a four-goal thriller that saw the Ibrox club come from behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 10:15:00" d="2020-11-06 10:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Rang v Aber '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers host rivals Aberdeen at Ibrox in November 2017 in a game that saw the Glasgow club dominate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 10:30:00" d="2020-11-06 11:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Gheorghe Hagi</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. This episode looks at Gheorghe Hagi, widely considered Romania's finest ever player</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 11:00:00" d="2020-11-06 11:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns - Captains</n><t>O</t>    <k>Some of the most inspirational players in football, these are the greatest captains of all time. With exclusive interviews with the likes of Carles Puyol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 11:30:00" d="2020-11-06 12:00:00"><n>Football Years: 97/98</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1997-1998 football season, as Ronaldo and Rivaldo made major moves in European football, Arsenal won the double, and France claimed the World Cup on home soil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 12:00:00" d="2020-11-06 13:00:00"><n>Championship Season Review 17/18</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive all the key moments from the 2017-2018 Sky Bet Championship season, as Wolves charged towards the title and a tight relegation battle ensured at the bottom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 13:00:00" d="2020-11-06 13:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: B'ford v Swindon '13</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember some classic matches from English football. Here, Bradford City face Swindon Town in December 2013 in Sky Bet League 1</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 13:15:00" d="2020-11-06 13:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Bradford/Arsenal '12</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the greatest matches from English football. Here, League 2 side Bradford City take on Premier League giants Arsenal in the Football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 13:30:00" d="2020-11-06 13:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby v Hull 2017</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Derby County and Hull City go head-to-head in a thrilling encounter back in 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 13:45:00" d="2020-11-06 14:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Aber v Rang '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Aberdeen play host to Rangers in December 2017, with the sides meeting for the second time in a week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 14:00:00" d="2020-11-06 14:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Kaka</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, a look at Kaka, the AC Milan midfielder who won titles in Serie A and the Champions League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 14:30:00" d="2020-11-06 15:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Finals</n><t>O</t>    <k>Football has been blessed with epic matches where triumph and heartbreak are entwined. From 'golden goal' winners to penalty shoot-out thrillers, enjoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 15:00:00" d="2020-11-06 15:30:00"><n>Football Years: 98/99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1998-1999 campaign, in which Denilson broke the transfer record, Steven Gerrard and John Terry made their debuts and Manchester United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 15:30:00" d="2020-11-06 16:30:00"><n>EFL Play Off Finals C'Ship 17/18</n><t>O</t>    <k>Fulham and Aston Villa meet in the Sky Bet Championship play-off final at Wembley. Villa are looking to end a two-year exile from the Premier League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 16:30:00" d="2020-11-06 16:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Sheff W/Sheff U 2017</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, relive a thrilling Steel City derby between rivals Sheffield Wednesday and Sheffield United at Hillsborough Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 16:45:00" d="2020-11-06 17:00:00"><n>Efl Greatest: Leeds/Sheff Utd 2017</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at a classic match from the EFL. Here, Leeds and Sheffield United go head-to-head at Elland Road in a thrilling contest back in 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 17:00:00" d="2020-11-06 17:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Ipswich/Sheff W '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at a classic match from the EFL. Here, Ipswich Town and Sheffield Wednesday meet at Portman Road in a four-goal thriller back in 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 17:15:00" d="2020-11-06 17:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Hibs v Rang '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic match from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Hibs host Rangers at Easter Road in a thrilling December 2017 encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 17:30:00" d="2020-11-06 18:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Andrea Pirlo</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, a look at Andrea Pirlo, the AC Milan star whose passing and vision made him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 18:00:00" d="2020-11-06 18:15:00"><n>EFL Highlights</n><t>O</t>    <k>Cardiff City face Barnsley at the Cardiff City Stadium in midweek action from the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 18:15:00" d="2020-11-06 18:30:00"><n>EFL Highlights</n><t>O</t>    <k>Huddersfield Town take on Bristol City at the John Smith's Stadium in midweek action from the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 18:30:00" d="2020-11-06 21:30:00"><n>Live EFL: Cardiff v Bristol City</n><t>O</t>    <k>A big weekend of action from the Sky Bet Championship begins as Cardiff City take on Bristol City at the Cardiff City Stadium in a Friday night clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 21:30:00" d="2020-11-06 22:30:00"><n>The Women's Football Show</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at all the latest news and major talking points from around the world of women's football, with guest and pundits joining to offer their unique insight and opinion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 22:30:00" d="2020-11-06 23:00:00"><n>EFL Goals: League 1&amp;2 MD11</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the goals from the midweek action in Sky Bet Leagues One and Two. Matches include Blackpool v Wigan Athletic and Sunderland v Ipswich Town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-06 23:00:00" d="2020-11-07 02:00:00"><n>Best Moments 1993-2019: C'Ship</n><t>O</t>    <k>All the way from 1993 through to 2019, take a look back over the years and enjoy the very best moments from the Championship Play-Off final as teams battle</k>  </p>
</a>
