<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="36" t="2020-10-28 03:51:42"><p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 05:00:00" d="2020-11-04 06:00:00"><n>EFL Playoff Final League 1 2014/15</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Preston North End face Swindon Town at Wembley in the League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 06:00:00" d="2020-11-04 07:00:00"><n>EFL Playoff Final League 2 2014/15</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Wycombe Wanderers and Southend United meet at Wembley in the League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 07:00:00" d="2020-11-04 07:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Gillingham/M.City '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic match from the English Football League. Here, remember the thrilling 1998-99 Second Division play-off final between Gillingham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 07:15:00" d="2020-11-04 07:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Bolton v Watford '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic match from the English Football League. Here, Bolton Wanderers and Watford face off in the First Division play-off final at Wembley back in 1999</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 07:30:00" d="2020-11-04 07:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Bolton/Preston '01</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic clash from the Football League. Here, Bolton Wanderers and Preston North End meet in the First Division play-off final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 07:45:00" d="2020-11-04 08:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers take on Celtic in the top flight back in 1999</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 08:00:00" d="2020-11-04 08:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Vieira</n><t>O</t>    <k>A profile of former France and Arsenal midfielder Patrick Vieira. One of the game's all-time greats, Vieira's power and precision saw him win the Premier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 08:30:00" d="2020-11-04 09:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Finals</n><t>O</t>    <k>Football has been blessed with epic matches where triumph and heartbreak are entwined. From 'golden goal' winners to penalty shoot-out thrillers, enjoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 09:00:00" d="2020-11-04 09:30:00"><n>Football Years: 98/99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1998-1999 campaign, in which Denilson broke the transfer record, Steven Gerrard and John Terry made their debuts and Manchester United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 09:30:00" d="2020-11-04 09:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Sheff Utd/Wolves '03</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic English Football League clash. Here, Sheffield United and Wolves meet in the First Division play-off final at the Millennium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 09:45:00" d="2020-11-04 10:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: N.Forest/Yeovil '07</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic clash from the English Football League. Here, Nottingham Forest face Yeovil in their Sky Bet League One play-off semi-final second</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 10:00:00" d="2020-11-04 10:15:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers travel to Celtic Park in 1999, knowing a win against rivals Celtic would clinch the Scottish title</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 10:15:00" d="2020-11-04 10:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers face Celtic at Ibrox in a six-goal thriller from the top flight back in the 1999-2000 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 10:30:00" d="2020-11-04 11:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: M Desailly</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, a look at French great Marcel Desailly, a UEFA Champions League, UEFA European</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 11:00:00" d="2020-11-04 11:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Comebacks</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sometimes all appears lost. Hope has disappeared and a team is simply down and out. But fortunes can be reversed. Here, take a look at some of football's greatest comebacks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 11:30:00" d="2020-11-04 12:00:00"><n>Football Years: 99/00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive the 1999-2000 season, as Thierry Henry went to Arsenal, Galatasaray won the first piece of European silverware by a Turkish club, and France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 12:00:00" d="2020-11-04 13:00:00"><n>Championship Season Review 15/16</n><t>O</t>    <k>A review of the 2015-2016 Sky Bet Championship season, with a look at all of the biggest stories and key matches from another eventful year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 13:00:00" d="2020-11-04 13:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Cardiff/Swansea '09</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic clash from the English Football League. Here, Cardiff City meet Swansea City in a thrilling south Wales derby at Ninian Park in 2009</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 13:15:00" d="2020-11-04 13:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: M'wall/S'thorpe '09</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic clash from the English Football League. Here, Millwall face Scunthorpe at Wembley Stadium in the League 1 play-off final in 2009</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 13:30:00" d="2020-11-04 13:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Sheff U/Sheff Wed '09</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic clash from the English Football League. Here, Sheffield United and Sheffield Wednesday meet in a thrilling Steel City derby in September 2009</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 13:45:00" d="2020-11-04 14:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic meet Rangers at Celtic Park in an eight-goal encounter back in the 2000-2001 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 14:00:00" d="2020-11-04 14:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Matthaus</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, a look at German great Lothar Matthaus, capped 150 times, and a UEFA European Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 14:30:00" d="2020-11-04 15:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Controversies</n><t>O</t>    <k>Football is the beautiful game - but it has an ugly side. When law and order breaks down, it can be unrecognisable from the sport loved by millions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 15:00:00" d="2020-11-04 15:30:00"><n>Football Years 90/91</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some memorable seasons in the world of football. Here, the focus is on the 1990-1991 campaign, beginning with the World Cup and featuring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 15:30:00" d="2020-11-04 16:30:00"><n>EFL Play Off Finals C'Ship 15/16</n><t>O</t>    <k>The most lucrative fixture in world football - the Sky Bet Championship play-off final - sees Hull City and Sheffield Wednesday meet at Wembley Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 16:30:00" d="2020-11-04 16:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: P'boro/So'ton 2011</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic clash from the English Football League. Here, Peterborough and Southampton meet in an eight-goal thriller in League 1 in February 2011</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 16:45:00" d="2020-11-04 17:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Watford/Leicester '13</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic clash from the English Football League. Here, Watford meet Leicester City in the famous second leg of their Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 17:00:00" d="2020-11-04 17:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Sheff Wed/Leeds '14</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic match from the Football League. Here, Yorkshire rivals Sheffield Wednesday and Leeds United meet at Hillsborough in January</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 17:15:00" d="2020-11-04 17:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers host Celtic at Ibrox in the 2000-2001 season in a match that produced six goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 17:30:00" d="2020-11-04 18:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Ian Rush</n><t>O</t>    <k>A profile of former Liverpool and Wales great Ian Rush. A prolific striker, Rush won five league titles, three FA Cups and the European Cup across a glittering career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 18:00:00" d="2020-11-04 18:30:00"><n>MLS Round Up Show</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major talking points from the latest round of fixtures in Major League Soccer. Matches include FC Dallas v Houston Dynamo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 18:30:00" d="2020-11-04 19:00:00"><n>Soccer AM - The Best Bits</n><t>O</t>    <k>All the best bits from the week's Soccer AM, as Jimmy Bullard and John Fendley are joined by guests from the world of sports and entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 19:00:00" d="2020-11-04 19:15:00"><n>Scottish Premiership Round-Up</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the action from the latest round of fixtures in the Scottish Premiership. Matches include Livingston v Motherwell and Kilmarnock v Rangers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 19:15:00" d="2020-11-04 19:30:00"><n>SPFL Hlts: Kilmarnock v Rangers</n><t>O</t>    <k>Kilmarnock take on Rangers at Rugby Park in Sunday lunchtime action from the Scottish Premiership</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 19:30:00" d="2020-11-04 20:00:00"><n>EFL Goals: League 1&amp;2 MD11</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the goals from the midweek action in Sky Bet Leagues One and Two. Matches include Blackpool v Wigan Athletic and Sunderland v Ipswich Town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-04 20:00:00" d="2020-11-04 23:00:00"><n>Live EFL: Derby County v QPR</n><t>O</t>    <k>Derby County take on Queens Park Rangers at Pride Park in midweek action from the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
</a>
