<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="36" t="2020-10-27 04:11:42"><p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 05:00:00" d="2020-11-03 06:00:00"><n>EFL Playoff Final League 1 2013/14</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Leyton Orient face Rotherham United at Wembley in the League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 06:00:00" d="2020-11-03 07:00:00"><n>EFL Playoff Final League 2 2013/14</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Burton Albion and Fleetwood Town meet at Wembley in the League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 07:00:00" d="2020-11-03 07:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Sheff U/Bristol '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Sheffield United host Bristol City at Bramall Lane in 2017 in a game with a late dramatic twist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 07:15:00" d="2020-11-03 07:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Reading/Cardiff '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Reading host Cardiff City at the Madejski Stadium in 2017 in a game with a thrilling conclusion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 07:30:00" d="2020-11-03 07:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Bristol C/Man Utd '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL Cup. Here, Bristol City host Premier League Man Utd at Ashton Gate in the 2017-18 competition's quarter-finals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 07:45:00" d="2020-11-03 08:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Rang v Aber '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers host rivals Aberdeen at Ibrox in November 2017 in a game that saw the Glasgow club dominate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 08:00:00" d="2020-11-03 08:15:00"><n>Scottish Premiership Round-Up</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the action from the latest round of fixtures in the Scottish Premiership. Matches include Livingston v Motherwell and Kilmarnock v Rangers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 08:15:00" d="2020-11-03 08:30:00"><n>SPFL Hlts: Kilmarnock v Rangers</n><t>O</t>    <k>Kilmarnock take on Rangers at Rugby Park in Sunday lunchtime action from the Scottish Premiership</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 08:30:00" d="2020-11-03 09:00:00"><n>EFL Goals: League 1&amp;2 MD10</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major talking points from around the week's matches in Sky Bet Leagues One and Two. Matches include Portsmouth v Charlton Athletic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 09:00:00" d="2020-11-03 09:30:00"><n>Soccer AM - The Best Bits</n><t>O</t>    <k>All the best bits from the week's Soccer AM, as Jimmy Bullard and John Fendley are joined by guests from the world of sports and entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 09:30:00" d="2020-11-03 09:45:00"><n>Scottish Premiership Round-Up</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the action from the latest round of fixtures in the Scottish Premiership. Matches include Livingston v Motherwell and Kilmarnock v Rangers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 09:45:00" d="2020-11-03 10:00:00"><n>SPFL Hlts: Kilmarnock v Rangers</n><t>O</t>    <k>Kilmarnock take on Rangers at Rugby Park in Sunday lunchtime action from the Scottish Premiership</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 10:00:00" d="2020-11-03 10:15:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Aber v Rang '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Aberdeen play host to Rangers in December 2017, with the sides meeting for the second time in a week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 10:15:00" d="2020-11-03 10:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Hibs v Rang '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic match from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Hibs host Rangers at Easter Road in a thrilling December 2017 encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 10:30:00" d="2020-11-03 11:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Rivaldo</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, a look at Rivaldo, the Brazilian star who won World Player of the Year in 1999 and the World Cup in 2002</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 11:00:00" d="2020-11-03 11:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Transfers</n><t>O</t>    <k>A football transfer can cost millions or nothing at all. Some can transform a club. Some can rock it to its core. This show counts downs the most important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 11:30:00" d="2020-11-03 12:00:00"><n>Football Years 95/96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive the 1995-96 season as the Bosman ruling changed football. Plus, England hosted the Euros, Auxerre and Atletico Madrid were surprise league winners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 12:00:00" d="2020-11-03 13:00:00"><n>Championship Season Review 14/15</n><t>O</t>    <k>A season review of the 2014-2015 Sky Bet Championship season, with a look at all of the biggest stories and key matches from another eventful year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 13:00:00" d="2020-11-03 13:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: A.Villa/Wolves 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Aston Villa host Wolves at Villa Park in a memorable Midlands derby in the 2017-18 campaign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 13:15:00" d="2020-11-03 13:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Fulham/QPR 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, promotion-chasing Fulham host QPR at Craven Cottage in a west London derby that saw a memorable comeback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 13:30:00" d="2020-11-03 13:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: M'boro/Wolves 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Middlesbrough host Wolves at the Riverside in 2018 in a game that saw the visitors reduced to nine men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 13:45:00" d="2020-11-03 14:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Hibs v Hearts '18</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the Scottish Professional Football League. Here, Edinburgh rivals Hibs and Hearts go head-to-head at Easter Road in March 2018</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 14:00:00" d="2020-11-03 14:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest:Roberto Carlos</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, the focus is on former Real Madrid and Brazil full-back Roberto Carlos - a UEFA Champions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 14:30:00" d="2020-11-03 15:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Entertainers</n><t>O</t>    <k>Celebrate some of the game's greatest entertainers - the players who make football fun. Featuring exclusive interviews with Zlatan Ibrahimovic, Ronaldinho and Gheorghe Hagi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 15:00:00" d="2020-11-03 15:30:00"><n>Football Years 96/97</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1996-1997 football season, as an African nation won a major tournament for the first time, one of the decade's finest goals was scored</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 15:30:00" d="2020-11-03 16:30:00"><n>EFL Playoff Final C'Ship 2014/15</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Middlesbrough take on Norwich City at Wembley in the Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 16:30:00" d="2020-11-03 16:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Cardiff/Wolves 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Cardiff City host Wolves at the Cardiff City Stadium in 2018 in a match that had a dramatic ending</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 16:45:00" d="2020-11-03 17:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby/Cardiff 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Derby County take on Cardiff City at Pride Park in the 2017-18 campaign in a match with implications</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 17:00:00" d="2020-11-03 17:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby/Leeds 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Derby County take on Marcelo Bielsa's Leeds United at Pride Park in a Championship match that saw five goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 17:15:00" d="2020-11-03 17:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic V Rangers '96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic meet Rangers in November 1996 at Celtic Park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 17:30:00" d="2020-11-03 18:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest:Roberto Baggio</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, the focus is on former Juventus, Milan and Italy forward Roberto Baggio, one of the game's great mavericks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 18:00:00" d="2020-11-03 18:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns - Captains</n><t>O</t>    <k>Some of the most inspirational players in football, these are the greatest captains of all time. With exclusive interviews with the likes of Carles Puyol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 18:30:00" d="2020-11-03 19:00:00"><n>EFL Goals: League 1&amp;2 MD10</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major talking points from around the week's matches in Sky Bet Leagues One and Two. Matches include Portsmouth v Charlton Athletic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 19:00:00" d="2020-11-03 19:30:00"><n>MLS Round Up Show</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major talking points from the latest round of fixtures in Major League Soccer. Matches include FC Dallas v Houston Dynamo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 19:30:00" d="2020-11-03 20:00:00"><n>Soccer AM - The Best Bits</n><t>O</t>    <k>All the best bits from the week's Soccer AM, as Jimmy Bullard and John Fendley are joined by guests from the world of sports and entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2020-11-03 20:00:00" d="2020-11-03 23:00:00"><n>Live EFL:Blackburn v Middlesbrough</n><t>O</t>  </p>
</a>
