<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="109" t="2020-10-28 03:52:19"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 05:00:00" d="2020-11-04 05:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (25)</n>    <k>The Grades
Miss Simian discovers a failed test from Gumball's past that brings down his grade point average. This means he has to retake kindergarten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 05:15:00" d="2020-11-04 05:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (26)</n>    <k>The Diet
Gumball and Darwin discover the reason Dad's diet wasn't working was that he was actually on ten diets: and eating a meal for each of them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 05:25:00" d="2020-11-04 05:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (27)</n>    <k>The Ex
Gumball discovers that Rob, his old nemesis, is &quot;neme-seeing&quot; someone else now. Devastated that Rob has fallen out of hate with him, Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 05:35:00" d="2020-11-04 05:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (28)</n>    <k>The Weirdo
When they see the school bullies making fun of Sussie Gumball and Darwin decide to try and help her act less weird. They carefully observe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 05:45:00" d="2020-11-04 06:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (29)</n>    <k>The Menu
The prize jewel on the Secret Joyful Burger menu is a mysterious burger but to order it you need to know its name. When Larry refuses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 06:00:00" d="2020-11-04 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>30% Bad Penny
Ben is at the annual Big Bacon Pig Parade but childhood friend Penny Heaven has met the family to ruin Ben's fun with her safety-obsessed self</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 06:10:00" d="2020-11-04 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (36)</n>    <k>Max to the Max
While Ben, Gwen and Max hike to a waterfall, the Bug Brothers are back with a plan to duplicate Diamondhead. But when their cloning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 06:25:00" d="2020-11-04 06:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (26)</n>    <k>81% The Love
When Bobert finds he's infected with a virus called love.exe he asks Gumball and Darwin to give him a definition for the word 'love'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 06:35:00" d="2020-11-04 06:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (27)</n>    <k>The Scam
At Halloween show-and-tell, the class isn't buying Gumball's story about Gargaroth The Devourer until Carrie fakes a terrifying haunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 06:55:00" d="2020-11-04 07:05:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (51)</n>    <k>52% Flashback: Part 1
A flashback reveals how Robin formed the Teen Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 07:05:00" d="2020-11-04 07:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (52)</n>    <k>52% Flashback: Part 2
A flashback reveals how Robin changed from mild-mannered sidekick to quick-tempered leader</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 07:25:00" d="2020-11-04 07:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! II (12)</n>    <k>Road Trip
A road trip in Cyborg's T-Car is really fun - for a while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 07:35:00" d="2020-11-04 07:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! II (12)</n>    <k>The Best Robin
Robin calls on another team when the others are too lazy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 07:50:00" d="2020-11-04 08:00:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (15)</n>    <k>65% #CrushingIt
Diana Prince is absolutely crushing it in every single aspect of life as a student at Metropolis High until someone shows up who threatens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 08:00:00" d="2020-11-04 08:20:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (17)</n>    <k>65% #IllusionsOfGrandeur
Ready to emerge from her father's shadow Zee Zatara secretly seeks fame and acclaim performing for her own audience at the pier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 08:20:00" d="2020-11-04 08:30:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears I (11)</n>    <k>Everyday Bears
It’s a normal day for the Bears. This means that Ice gets in a fight with a Roomba, Panda’s life gets turned upside down when a mouse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 08:30:00" d="2020-11-04 08:40:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears I (12)</n>    <k>Nom Nom
When Nom Nom shows up on the Bears’ doorstep, dishevelled and deposed from his spot as cutest internet star ever after a recent meltdown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 08:40:00" d="2020-11-04 09:00:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears I (13)</n>    <k>The Road
The Bears flashback to when they were young cubs! The three Bears, on their way through the desert, come upon a giant warehouse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 09:00:00" d="2020-11-04 09:10:00"><n u="Craig of the Creek">Craig of the Creek I (8)</n>    <k>70% Escape from Family Dinner
There's a huge water balloon fight at the creek but Craig is stuck at home for a family dinner unless he can escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 09:10:00" d="2020-11-04 09:25:00"><n u="Craig of the Creek">Craig of the Creek I (9)</n>    <k>70% Monster in the Garden
Craig is determined to catch the monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 09:25:00" d="2020-11-04 09:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan I (9)</n>    <k>48% Babysitting Bedlam
Dan and Wynton meet a strange boy who leads them into an underground maze whe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 09:35:00" d="2020-11-04 09:55:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan I (9)</n>    <k>48% Rubbed the Wrong Way
After a Bakugan field errupts the town kids stampede to get their own Bakugan but when the field is contaminated Lia must save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 09:55:00" d="2020-11-04 10:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (40)</n>    <k>The BFFS
Gumball's old BFF, Fuzzy, turns up on his doorstep. Darwin struggles to accept that there was someone before him and fails to contain his jealousy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 10:05:00" d="2020-11-04 10:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (41)</n>    <k>The Agent
Gumball and Darwin's clothes go missing after a swimming lesson, and Gumball is forced to wear a tuxedo from the lost and found office</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 10:25:00" d="2020-11-04 10:35:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (30)</n>    <k>65% Sleeper Sofa
When the Sky Pirates infiltrate Sheriff HQ they put our heroes in danger!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 10:35:00" d="2020-11-04 10:50:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (11)</n>    <k>Outfoxed
When Rufus and Reg come to swindle the town Sheriff Mao Mao teaches them a lesson in justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 10:50:00" d="2020-11-04 11:00:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (6)</n>    <k>That Slobot is No Bot of Mine
Axel and the team compete against themselves in tests of skill, strength and stamina, but when SloBot gets belittled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 11:00:00" d="2020-11-04 11:20:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (7)</n>    <k>Sarge in Charge
Axel and the team must rescue Sarge Charge from a solo mission in the backyard which Orangutank has turned into his own personal heart of darkness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 11:20:00" d="2020-11-04 11:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! VI (14)</n>    <k>52% The Titans Go Casual
The Superhero Board of Authority institutes a dress code which leads the Titans to introduce Casual Tuesday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 11:30:00" d="2020-11-04 11:45:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (3)</n>    <k>52% Dignity of Teeth
When Beast Boy gets a stack of cash from the Tooth Fairy against Raven's advice the other Titans start knocking out their own teeth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 11:45:00" d="2020-11-04 11:55:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (36)</n>    <k>Teen Titans Roar!
The Titans are outraged when their favorite cartoon is rebooted so they come up with a plan to get this new show off the air</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 11:55:00" d="2020-11-04 12:15:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (37)</n>    <k>52% Teen Titans Vroom: Part 1
In this episode of Turbo Titans Go Force the Titans gain the ability to transform into cars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 12:15:00" d="2020-11-04 12:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (4)</n>    <k>52% Fish Water
Starfire wins a goldfish at the carnival and vows to keep it alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 12:25:00" d="2020-11-04 12:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (5)</n>    <k>52% TV Knight
Batman and Commissioner Gordon check in on various happenings around Jump City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 12:40:00" d="2020-11-04 12:50:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (31)</n>    <k>65% Mao Mao's Nakey
When MM loses his clothes while trying to scale the Ruby Pure Heart he has to get back to Sheriff's HQ by daybreak</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 12:50:00" d="2020-11-04 13:05:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (12)</n>    <k>Thumb War
The gang decide to compete in the annual Thumb War competition but a surprise forces Mao Mao to deal with the unthinkable. losing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 13:05:00" d="2020-11-04 13:15:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (12)</n>    <k>Brain Trust
Dr. Fox accidentally transports the gang inside her brain, where they must control her movements to complete a dangerous experiment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 13:15:00" d="2020-11-04 13:35:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (13)</n>    <k>P.L.O.T. Device 2: Beyond the Bored Dome
Dr. Fox reprograms the P.L.O.T. Device to only generate boring events but the gang can't help but add drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 13:35:00" d="2020-11-04 13:50:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (15)</n>    <k>49% A Ninjustice to Harold
Harold's world is turned upside down when Beth becomes the class ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 13:50:00" d="2020-11-04 14:05:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (16)</n>    <k>49% Having the Timeout of Our Lives
Owen forms a special bond with Duncan after having loads of fun with him during their timeouts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 14:05:00" d="2020-11-04 14:15:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (17)</n>    <k>49% Hic Hic Hooray
Bridgette gets the hiccups and becomes desperate to get rid of them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 14:15:00" d="2020-11-04 14:30:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (18)</n>    <k>49% Bananas and Cheese
Duncan is determined to stop the musical duo Bananas and Cheese from coming to the daycare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 14:30:00" d="2020-11-04 14:40:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (19)</n>    <k>49% Inglorious Toddlers
Owen fears he's about to lose his BFF Noah to a gifted military school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 14:40:00" d="2020-11-04 14:55:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (20)</n>    <k>49% Not Without My Fudgy Lumps
Noah tries to rescue the chocolates Owen forgot outside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 14:55:00" d="2020-11-04 15:05:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (19)</n>    <k>65% #GothamCon
A fun day for Barbara Gordon and her bestie Harleen Quinzel (at Gotham City's annual geekfest, the Annual Convention of Gotham City Enthusiats!) is turned on its head when, out of nowhere, the villainous Harley Quinn shows up to wreak havoc! Lucky for eve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 15:05:00" d="2020-11-04 15:25:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (16)</n>    <k>65% #MisgivingTree
Jessica Cruz and Pam Isley bond over protecting an ancient tree from being cut down. Neither of them realizes who the other's alter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 15:25:00" d="2020-11-04 15:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! VI (15)</n>    <k>We're Off To Get Awards
During an awards ceremony, Robin is swept up by a tornado and arrives in a magical land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 15:35:00" d="2020-11-04 15:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (1)</n>    <k>Pie Bros
Beast Boy has to get a job at a pie shop to earn enough money to buy Cyborg a birthday gift only his job interferes with being able to attend the actual party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 15:50:00" d="2020-11-04 16:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (11)</n>    <k>A Farce
Brother Blood takes the Titans to trial for their recent destruction of Jump City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 16:00:00" d="2020-11-04 16:20:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (12)</n>    <k>52% Animals It's Just a Word!
After the other Titans are injured Beast Boy donates his blood to save them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 16:20:00" d="2020-11-04 16:30:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (26)</n>    <k>Snow Way Out
Owen wants everyone to love his new snowsuit and envy him but it's just not working out that way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 16:30:00" d="2020-11-04 16:40:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (27)</n>    <k>49% All Up in Your Drill
Duncan stages a small coup to oust Courtney as their official class firefighter so that he can wear the shiny firefighter helmet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 16:40:00" d="2020-11-04 16:55:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (28)</n>    <k>Toys Will Be Toys
Courtney becomes a toy tester but forgets that the most important thing is to have fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 16:55:00" d="2020-11-04 17:05:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (29)</n>    <k>49% Stay Goth, Poodle Girl, Stay Goth
Gwen accidentally brings a pink stuffed pony she loves to daycare and spends the day denying it's hers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 17:05:00" d="2020-11-04 17:15:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (30)</n>    <k>49% Gum and Gummer
Beth gets her gum stuck in Leshawna's hair and has to get it out - without Leshawna finding out it's there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 17:15:00" d="2020-11-04 17:25:00"><n u="Mighty Magiswords">Mighty Magiswords III (20)</n>    <k>52% Flashback Farms
Trying to cheer Vambre up Prohyas recalls when they were just kids on their parents broccoli Farm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 17:25:00" d="2020-11-04 17:35:00"><n u="Apple &amp; Onion">Apple &amp; Onion I (35)</n>    <k>60% Dragonhead
Apple and Onion must run a secret parking lot on their roof terrace so they can have a shower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 17:35:00" d="2020-11-04 17:52:00"><n u="Apple &amp; Onion">Apple &amp; Onion I (36)</n>    <k>60% Pulling Your Weight
Apple and Onion join a gym to gain the strength of seven people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 17:52:00" d="2020-11-04 18:02:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (12)</n>    <k>Brain Trust
Dr. Fox accidentally transports the gang inside her brain, where they must control her movements to complete a dangerous experiment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 18:02:00" d="2020-11-04 18:20:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (13)</n>    <k>P.L.O.T. Device 2: Beyond the Bored Dome
Dr. Fox reprograms the P.L.O.T. Device to only generate boring events but the gang can't help but add drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 18:20:00" d="2020-11-04 18:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! VI (15)</n>    <k>We're Off To Get Awards
During an awards ceremony, Robin is swept up by a tornado and arrives in a magical land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 18:30:00" d="2020-11-04 18:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (8)</n>    <k>Genie President
Robin hatches a plan to get rich off pennies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 18:40:00" d="2020-11-04 19:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (9)</n>    <k>Little Elvis
The Titans team up with Shazam to defeat Mr. Mind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 19:00:00" d="2020-11-04 19:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (17)</n>    <k>The Uploads
Gumball and Darwin try to tear themselves away from the internet but end up falling down the Elmore Stream-hole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 19:10:00" d="2020-11-04 19:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (18)</n>    <k>81% The Wicked
After being framed for feeding coffee to the squirrels in the park, Gumball proclaims that Mrs Robinson is pure evil. Darwin tells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 19:30:00" d="2020-11-04 19:40:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (12)</n>    <k>Bear-Knuckle Brawl
Axel must team up with Bearbarian to stop Madcap from transforming Luka's stuffed bear collection into an invincible army</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 19:40:00" d="2020-11-04 20:00:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (19)</n>    <k>The Other Side
Axel must 'save' Bobbie Blobby after she defects to Madcap's team tempted by Porcupunk and his assertion that she belongs with the bad toys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 20:00:00" d="2020-11-04 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (30)</n>    <k>Zombozo-Land
Ben, Gwen and Max revisit their favourite amusement park – renovated and rebranded as AdrenaWORLD! Unfortunately, the new management</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 20:10:00" d="2020-11-04 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (29)</n>    <k>Don't Laze Me Bro
Ben and his arch-enemy Billy Billions clash in a duel for supremacy at the world’s largest Laser Tag Park, Laser Town. But when Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 20:30:00" d="2020-11-04 20:40:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan I (25)</n>    <k>48% Hostile Take Over
After more unsuccessful attempts to harness Core Cell energy the AO must battle their own Bakugan with AAAnimus tech in order to save them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 20:40:00" d="2020-11-04 21:00:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan I (25)</n>    <k>48% The Big Bounce
The AO confront Philomena with concerns about her control over the Core Cell ene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 21:00:00" d="2020-11-04 21:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (5)</n>    <k>59% Sleepover
Angelo gives us his tips and tricks for the most awesome sleepover ever. Until the “prank call” trick ruins the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 21:10:00" d="2020-11-04 21:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (6)</n>    <k>59% Fake Stuntman
Angelo stupidly boasts that his Dad used to be a stuntman. And the next day Dad has been invited to speak to Angelo’s class for career day. Gah!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 21:25:00" d="2020-11-04 21:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (7)</n>    <k>59% The Balance Of Nature
Angelo makes Tracy cry and feels terrible about it. He declares a truce. Problem is… their growing friendship throws off the balance of nature!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 21:35:00" d="2020-11-04 21:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (8)</n>    <k>59% Cat Burglar
Joe Mama has been stealing stuff from around town and storing it under Angelo’s bed. Angelo and friends embark on a reverse scavenger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 21:55:00" d="2020-11-04 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (9)</n>    <k>Here Comes The Science
Angelo and Lola are stuck with Manetti as a science project partner. The only way to complete the project is turn Manetti into the science project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 22:05:00" d="2020-11-04 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (10)</n>    <k>59% The Arm
Tracy claims Angelo broke her arm. Angelo’s punishment—become Tracy’s slave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 22:20:00" d="2020-11-04 22:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (11)</n>    <k>59% Catnapped
Angelo discovers Cathy cat and Joe Mama have been accidentally switched at the Vet. And no one believes Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 22:30:00" d="2020-11-04 22:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (12)</n>    <k>59% Pen Pal
Angelo creates a fake Guatemalan pen pal so he doesn’t fail Mr. Foot’s class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 22:50:00" d="2020-11-04 23:20:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (10)</n>    <k>The Weakest Link
Lloyd turns the tables on Harumi to take his father’s power away and the Ninja learn what it takes to be a Dragon Hunter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 23:20:00" d="2020-11-04 23:45:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (7)</n>    <k>Saving Faith
NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu centers on the adventures of five ninjas. The show is set in the fictional world of Ninjago a place inspired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 23:45:00" d="2020-11-04 23:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (17)</n>    <k>The Helmet
Gumball’s magic tinfoil helmet threatens to tear the Watterson family apart!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-04 23:55:00" d="2020-11-05 00:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (17)</n>    <k>The Fight
Anais is convinced that Gumball is being bullied by Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 00:05:00" d="2020-11-05 00:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (18)</n>    <k>The End
Gumball and Darwin are convinced that the world will end in 24 hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 00:20:00" d="2020-11-05 00:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (39)</n>    <k>The Singing
Join the citizens of Elmore for a song and dance spectacular that will have you covering your ears with joy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 00:30:00" d="2020-11-05 00:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (40)</n>    <k>81% The Puppets
While searching the attic for items to put in their yard sale, Gumball and Darwin stumble upon a load of their old toys. Darwin is especially</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 00:40:00" d="2020-11-05 00:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (1)</n>    <k>81% The Kids
Whilst Gumball and Darwin make fun of Mum and Dad for being old their voices start to break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 00:50:00" d="2020-11-05 01:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (1)</n>    <k>The Fan
Sarah the new kid in school is Gumball and Darwin's number one slightly obsessive fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 01:00:00" d="2020-11-05 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (25)</n>    <k>59% Van Dunk's Mojo
Everyone’s favorite skater Ollie Van Dunk crashes out in a big contest loses his mojo and quits skating. Angelo and friends try to raise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 01:10:00" d="2020-11-05 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (26)</n>    <k>59% Das Fence
When Angelo gets stuck with the chore of painting Geezer’s old broken down fence he channels his inner Tom Sawyer and manages to convince</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 01:25:00" d="2020-11-05 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (27)</n>    <k>59% The World According To Angelo
Angelo and friends make a TV show pilot called “Angelo Rules” with Lola producing Sherwood directing Angelo writing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 01:35:00" d="2020-11-05 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (28)</n>    <k>In The Game
After Mom cuts off Angelo’s videogame time Angelo attempts to change her mind. He sets out to prove to her that gaming is an important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 01:45:00" d="2020-11-05 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (29)</n>    <k>59% Geezer's Nephew
Angelo and friends are stuck hanging out with Geezer’s Nephew -- a terrible horrible no good delinquent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 01:55:00" d="2020-11-05 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (30)</n>    <k>Enter The Karate Kid
Angelo and friends attempt to raise Butterfingers flagging self-esteem by training him in the art of Angelo-fu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 02:05:00" d="2020-11-05 02:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (31)</n>    <k>59% A Perfect Day
Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 02:20:00" d="2020-11-05 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (32)</n>    <k>59% Home Security
When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 02:25:00" d="2020-11-05 02:35:00"><n u="Mighty Magiswords">Mighty Magiswords III (17)</n>    <k>52% Phil's in the House
To exact his revenge on the Warriors Phil the philanderer hides in The Warriors’ house and turns the siblings against each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 02:35:00" d="2020-11-05 02:55:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu X (13)</n>    <k>66% The Darkness Comes
As NinjaGo City rebuilds Faith arrives with a dire warning: the Oni have returned and are destroying the realms one by one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 02:55:00" d="2020-11-05 03:15:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu X (15)</n>    <k>66% Into the Breach
Having freed Lord Garmadon from Kryptarium Prison the ninja are beset by doubts particularly Lloyd. Lord Garmadon and Lloyd journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 03:15:00" d="2020-11-05 03:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (12)</n>    <k>The Bros
When Darwin and Gumball reveal how they’d spend their perfect day Gumball confesses that he would spend it with Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 03:25:00" d="2020-11-05 03:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (12)</n>    <k>The Man
Granny Jojo has brought a boyfriend to her birthday meal and Dad isn’t happy about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 03:35:00" d="2020-11-05 03:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (13)</n>    <k>The Pizza
The Wattersons complain about their day and order a pizza from Larry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 03:45:00" d="2020-11-05 03:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (30)</n>    <k>The Uncle
When Gumball finds out that their 8-bit friend Ocho has an Italian plumber called Mario for an uncle, he assumes it's 'that' Mario</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 03:55:00" d="2020-11-05 04:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (31)</n>    <k>The Heist
Richard's got a motorcycle helmet stuck on his head, so when he goes into a bank the terrified staff all assume he's there to rob the place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 04:10:00" d="2020-11-05 04:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (32)</n>    <k>The Petals
When Leslie's petals begin falling off he feels like his good looks are fading, Gumball and Darwin use everything they know about style</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 04:20:00" d="2020-11-05 04:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (33)</n>    <k>The Nuisance
The Wattersons fear the worst when they are summoned to a Town Hall meeting, but are pleasantly surprised when they're offered a brand new house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 04:30:00" d="2020-11-05 04:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (34)</n>    <k>The Best
No matter what Gumball does Carmen thinks she knows better. Gumball attempts to gain the moral high ground but fails spectacularly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 04:40:00" d="2020-11-05 04:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (35)</n>    <k>The Worst
Each member of the family thinks their demographic has it the toughest. Gumball and Darwin think guys have it the worst. Mom thinks women do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-05 04:50:00" d="2020-11-05 05:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (36)</n>    <k>The List
When the kids find out that Mom's life hasn't panned out exactly as she'd hoped, they try to make her day a bit easier by taking on her chores</k>  </p>
</a>
