<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="108" t="2020-10-30 03:45:28"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 05:00:00" d="2020-11-06 05:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (11)</n>    <k>The Pact
Gumball finds Penny's laugh annoying, but can't think of a way to tell her without offending her. When he discovers that Principal Brown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 05:15:00" d="2020-11-06 05:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (13)</n>    <k>The Candidate
When their parents all go to a charity gala at the school, the kids are locked in a classroom with a VHS tape. However, when the room starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 05:25:00" d="2020-11-06 05:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (10)</n>    <k>81% The Anybody
Gumball wants Clayton to sit his detention for him, so convinces him it's way more exciting to be take the shapes of other people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 05:35:00" d="2020-11-06 05:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (14)</n>    <k>81% The Shippening
When people that barely know each other start falling in love, Gumball thinks he knows who's behind it. He rushes to Sarah's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 05:45:00" d="2020-11-06 06:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (16)</n>    <k>The Stink
Gumball decides to put Mr.Small's eco-friendly principles to the test but it doesn't quite go as planned. Mr.Small disappears after deciding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 06:00:00" d="2020-11-06 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 IV (5)</n>    <k>Tokyo Fun Part 1: Big Bugg Bash
While in Tokyo, Team Tennyson come face to face with a horrible secret, Japan's hottest new restaurant is being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 06:10:00" d="2020-11-06 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 IV (6)</n>    <k>Tokyo Fun Part 2: Slamming It Up
While on a visit to the Sumo Slammers Amusement Park in Tokyo, Team Tennyson gets to watch a genuine sumo wrestling match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 06:25:00" d="2020-11-06 06:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (30)</n>    <k>The Points
Gumball and Darwin agree to do all of Tobias’s chores in exchange for good points! Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias is doing way better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 06:35:00" d="2020-11-06 06:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (31)</n>    <k>The Bus
When Rocky suggests that the Elmore Junior High kids skip school, the bus is boarded by criminals who seem to want to teach them the importance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 06:55:00" d="2020-11-06 07:05:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (3)</n>    <k>52% Kabooms: Part 1
The Titans are excited to see the movie version of their favorite show, &quot;Babies vs. Dogs&quot; until the movie's exposition makes watching it super-boring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 07:05:00" d="2020-11-06 07:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (4)</n>    <k>52% Kabooms: Part 2
Inspired by the &quot;Babies vs Dogs&quot; movie, the Titans decide to make a big Hollywood film of their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 07:25:00" d="2020-11-06 07:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! II (14)</n>    <k>Robin Backwards
Nibor the Bizzaro World's Robin arrives in Jump City and the Titans decide they should keep an eye on him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 07:35:00" d="2020-11-06 07:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! II (14)</n>    <k>Crazy Day
It's Crazy Day again and Raven must do her best to avoid being driven crazy by the other Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 07:50:00" d="2020-11-06 08:00:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (19)</n>    <k>65% #GothamCon
A fun day for Barbara Gordon and her bestie Harleen Quinzel (at Gotham City's annual geekfest, the Annual Convention of Gotham City Enthusiats!) is turned on its head when, out of nowhere, the villainous Harley Quinn shows up to wreak havoc! Lucky for eve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 08:00:00" d="2020-11-06 08:20:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (16)</n>    <k>65% #MisgivingTree
Jessica Cruz and Pam Isley bond over protecting an ancient tree from being cut down. Neither of them realizes who the other's alter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 08:20:00" d="2020-11-06 08:30:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears I (17)</n>    <k>Emergency
When Grizz comes home with a live crab, he thinks it can become a pet for the brothers to share. However, after the crab pinches Ice Bear's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 08:30:00" d="2020-11-06 08:40:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears I (18)</n>    <k>Cupcake Job
When the Bears' beloved laptop breaks, they finally have the need to do something they've never done before: get jobs. Working at a trendy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 08:40:00" d="2020-11-06 09:00:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears I (20)</n>    <k>Brother Up
After Panda stumbles and accidentally scares a pack of wolves away in the process, the hierarchy of the Bears is disrupted. Suddenly, Panda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 09:00:00" d="2020-11-06 09:10:00"><n u="Craig of the Creek">Craig of the Creek I (12)</n>    <k>Dog Decider
Unable to make tough decisions Craig decides to put his choices in the hands of a dog named Fred</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 09:10:00" d="2020-11-06 09:25:00"><n u="Craig of the Creek">Craig of the Creek I (13)</n>    <k>Bring Out Your Beast
Craig wants to play a popular card game so he decides to borrow Bernard's vintage and valuable cards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 09:25:00" d="2020-11-06 09:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan I (11)</n>    <k>48% Home on the Run
We are introduced to Shun's mysterious backstory his relationship with his industrialist father and desire for a closer knit family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 09:35:00" d="2020-11-06 09:55:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan I (11)</n>    <k>48% Top Slot
Dan and Shun butt heads on how best to make the AO a real team amidst growing threats includin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 09:55:00" d="2020-11-06 10:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (44)</n>    <k>81% The Inquisition
The students find their world turned upside down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 10:05:00" d="2020-11-06 10:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (1)</n>    <k>81% The Third
Gumball and Darwin spice up their friendship by introducing a third best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 10:25:00" d="2020-11-06 10:35:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (32)</n>    <k>65% Lucky Ducky Mug
When Adorabat and Badgerclops break Mao Mao's favorite mug he gives them the silent treatment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 10:35:00" d="2020-11-06 10:50:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (13)</n>    <k>Popularity Conquest
When Mao Mao discovers that he is not as popular as Badgerclops and Adorabat they decide to reinvent him as a kinder cuddlier hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 10:50:00" d="2020-11-06 11:00:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (12)</n>    <k>Bear-Knuckle Brawl
Axel must team up with Bearbarian to stop Madcap from transforming Luka's stuffed bear collection into an invincible army</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 11:00:00" d="2020-11-06 11:20:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (14)</n>    <k>Attack of Thermometron 9000
Axel must wrangle Galileo and Bobbie to shut down a rogue thermostat - improperly upgraded by Slobot - as it plunges the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 11:20:00" d="2020-11-06 11:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! VI (16)</n>    <k>Rain On Your Wedding Day
While facing off with The Brain, Robin tries to teach the other Titans the proper definition of irony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 11:30:00" d="2020-11-06 11:45:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (5)</n>    <k>52% Spice Game
Tired of Robin's bland cooking the other Titans try their hand at spicing up their food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 11:45:00" d="2020-11-06 11:55:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (40)</n>    <k>Forest Pirates
The Titans are at Super Hero Summer Camp for the week and they may need to add another teammate to win the big canoe race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 11:55:00" d="2020-11-06 12:15:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (41)</n>    <k>The Bergerac
The Titans give Robin advice to guide him through his camp romance with Wonder Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 12:15:00" d="2020-11-06 12:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (8)</n>    <k>52% Inner Beauty of a Cactus
The Titans play Spin The Bottle as Starfire tries to improve her vocabulary through kissing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 12:25:00" d="2020-11-06 12:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (9)</n>    <k>52% The Streak: Part 1
It's Crime Season and Robin is determined to continue his streak of stopping 52 crimes every year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 12:40:00" d="2020-11-06 12:50:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (33)</n>    <k>65% Lonely Kid
When AD has trouble making friends at school MM tells her the story of how he made his first real friend —BB</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 12:50:00" d="2020-11-06 13:05:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (14)</n>    <k>Mao Mao's Bike Adventure
When Mao Mao underestimates enemy and friend alike it almost costs him the entire kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 13:05:00" d="2020-11-06 13:15:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (17)</n>    <k>52% Borrowed
Richard discovers his library books have been borrowed by Master Frown and sets off on a crazed mission to return the books before they're overdue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 13:15:00" d="2020-11-06 13:35:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (18)</n>    <k>52% Best Friend Boot Camp
Master Frown and Brock attend a friendship-themed competition intending to ruin it for everyone else, but soon discover their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 13:35:00" d="2020-11-06 13:50:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (28)</n>    <k>Toys Will Be Toys
Courtney becomes a toy tester but forgets that the most important thing is to have fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 13:50:00" d="2020-11-06 14:05:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (29)</n>    <k>49% Stay Goth, Poodle Girl, Stay Goth
Gwen accidentally brings a pink stuffed pony she loves to daycare and spends the day denying it's hers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 14:05:00" d="2020-11-06 14:10:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (30)</n>    <k>49% Gum and Gummer
Beth gets her gum stuck in Leshawna's hair and has to get it out - without Leshawna finding out it's there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 14:10:00" d="2020-11-06 14:25:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (31)</n>    <k>49% Invasion of the Booger Snatchers
Harold believes that the picture day photographer is somehow turning the kids into well behaved zombies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 14:25:00" d="2020-11-06 14:35:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (32)</n>    <k>49% Wristy Business
Beth and Leshawna try to one-up each other with fake injuries as they compete for the attention and sympathy of the other kids at daycare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 14:35:00" d="2020-11-06 14:55:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (33)</n>    <k>49% Melter Skelter
When Chef tells Beth he won't buy the new super amazing toy she wants because they already have plenty to play with she goes on a mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 14:55:00" d="2020-11-06 15:05:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (27)</n>    <k>65% #RageCat
Jessica Cruz is convinced she can find the purr-fect forever home for Dexter, a cat who has been deemed unadoptable because he's basically</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 15:05:00" d="2020-11-06 15:25:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (18)</n>    <k>65% #BeastsInShow
When Babs and Kara spar over whose dog is better they decide to settle it at the Metropolis Dog Show where Ace the Bat-Hound and Krypto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 15:25:00" d="2020-11-06 15:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! VI (17)</n>    <k>52% Egg Hunt
Robin still regrets not being able to find an Easter egg when he was a kid, so the Titans head to Gotham to solve this mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 15:35:00" d="2020-11-06 15:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (2)</n>    <k>Dog Hand
Raven's supervillain father comes to visit and the rest of the team thinks he's the coolest~a5~until he steals their souls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 15:50:00" d="2020-11-06 16:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (14)</n>    <k>Black Friday
Starfire is visited by three ghosts and shown the true meaning of Black Friday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 16:00:00" d="2020-11-06 16:20:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (20)</n>    <k>52% Squash and Stretch
The Titans learn about cartoon-style violence in order to get revenge on a snack-stealing squirrel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 16:20:00" d="2020-11-06 16:30:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (36)</n>    <k>The Price of Advice
After a paper origami fortune teller tells Izzy she's the world's best advice giver she's determined to prove it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 16:30:00" d="2020-11-06 16:40:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (37)</n>    <k>There Are No Hoppy Endings
Chef struggles to maintain his sanity when the kids continue to blame a stuffed rabbit named Hoppy for everything they do wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 16:40:00" d="2020-11-06 16:55:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (38)</n>    <k>Duncan Disorderly
Duncan escapes during a community walk only to discover he has to babysit Cody and Bridgette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 16:55:00" d="2020-11-06 17:05:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (39)</n>    <k>Soother or Later
A terrified Duncan who's afraid of lightning learns it's even harder to break back into school than it was to break out when he finally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 17:05:00" d="2020-11-06 17:15:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (40)</n>    <k>Mutt Ado About Owen
After accidentally hypnotizing Owen into being a dog Harold thinks he must reverse the hypnosis to avoid going to jail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 17:15:00" d="2020-11-06 17:25:00"><n u="Mighty Magiswords">Mighty Magiswords III (2)</n>    <k>52% The Desolation of Grup
The Warriors are hired to vanquish a dragon who turns out to be confoundingly sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 17:25:00" d="2020-11-06 17:35:00"><n u="Apple &amp; Onion">Apple &amp; Onion I (40)</n>    <k>60% Election Day
Apple runs for mayor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 17:35:00" d="2020-11-06 17:52:00"><n u="Apple &amp; Onion">Apple &amp; Onion I (1)</n>    <k>The Perfect Team
Onion worries his relationship with Apple is in jeopardy when a stray cat enters the picture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 17:52:00" d="2020-11-06 18:02:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (17)</n>    <k>52% Borrowed
Richard discovers his library books have been borrowed by Master Frown and sets off on a crazed mission to return the books before they're overdue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 18:02:00" d="2020-11-06 18:20:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (18)</n>    <k>52% Best Friend Boot Camp
Master Frown and Brock attend a friendship-themed competition intending to ruin it for everyone else, but soon discover their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 18:20:00" d="2020-11-06 18:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! VI (17)</n>    <k>52% Egg Hunt
Robin still regrets not being able to find an Easter egg when he was a kid, so the Titans head to Gotham to solve this mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 18:30:00" d="2020-11-06 18:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (14)</n>    <k>Monster Squad!
The Titans want to be the scariest trick-or-treaters in town so Raven casts a spell to turn them into real monsters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 18:40:00" d="2020-11-06 19:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (15)</n>    <k>52% Justice League's Next Top Talent Idol Star: Second Greatest Team Edition Part 1
The Justice League holds another talent competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 19:00:00" d="2020-11-06 19:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (21)</n>    <k>The Traitor
When Alan ditches Gumball to do something more fun Gumball is desperate to track him down and make him pay for his betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 19:10:00" d="2020-11-06 19:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (22)</n>    <k>The Advice
To make Mr Small feel like he's inspired the students, Gumball and Darwin try to follow every piece of advice Mr Small gives them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 19:30:00" d="2020-11-06 19:40:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (9)</n>    <k>Bobbie Not Blobby
Axel discovers that the culprit behind Bobbie Blobby's missing mech-suit is Masko who only wanted to clean out its clogged clay cannons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 19:40:00" d="2020-11-06 20:00:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (10)</n>    <k>Access Denied
When Axel and the team try to figure out what Sarge Charge's secret weapon is they get ejected from the house by his newly upgraded security</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 20:00:00" d="2020-11-06 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (39)</n>    <k>Omni-Tricked Part 3
Ben is taken deep into the forest to keep his unpredictable transformations from endangering the public. But when a seemingly benign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 20:10:00" d="2020-11-06 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (40)</n>    <k>Omni-Tricked Part 4
Ben's holiday to Portland is cut short when he discovers an 11th alien while battling a Dr. Animo Mega-Creature. But when the fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 20:30:00" d="2020-11-06 21:00:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (1)</n>    <k>48% The Forbidden Isle
When Bakugan begin emerging from the earth's crust in a mysterious worldwide &quot;awakening,&quot; Dan and his friends find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 21:00:00" d="2020-11-06 21:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (20)</n>    <k>Best Sister Ever
In honor of older sisters Slobber offers free tickets to whomever can make the best short film about their older sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 21:10:00" d="2020-11-06 21:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (21)</n>    <k>Snow And Tell
Angelo searches for the ultimate object to bring to show and tell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 21:25:00" d="2020-11-06 21:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (22)</n>    <k>Photobomb
Angelo’s photo bombs make him a big hit on the internet and he is loving his newfound popularity. Until Butterfingers starts getting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 21:35:00" d="2020-11-06 21:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (23)</n>    <k>Not Gym Class
The equipment in Coach Zonka’s gym class is deemed a safety hazard so gym class is canceled permanently. Angelo attempts to rally the school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 21:55:00" d="2020-11-06 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (25)</n>    <k>59% Van Dunk's Mojo
Everyone’s favorite skater Ollie Van Dunk crashes out in a big contest loses his mojo and quits skating. Angelo and friends try to raise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 22:05:00" d="2020-11-06 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (26)</n>    <k>59% Das Fence
When Angelo gets stuck with the chore of painting Geezer’s old broken down fence he channels his inner Tom Sawyer and manages to convince</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 22:20:00" d="2020-11-06 22:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (27)</n>    <k>59% The World According To Angelo
Angelo and friends make a TV show pilot called “Angelo Rules” with Lola producing Sherwood directing Angelo writing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 22:30:00" d="2020-11-06 22:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (28)</n>    <k>In The Game
After Mom cuts off Angelo’s videogame time Angelo attempts to change her mind. He sets out to prove to her that gaming is an important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 22:50:00" d="2020-11-06 23:20:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu X (13)</n>    <k>66% The Darkness Comes
As NinjaGo City rebuilds Faith arrives with a dire warning: the Oni have returned and are destroying the realms one by one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 23:20:00" d="2020-11-06 23:45:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu X (15)</n>    <k>66% Into the Breach
Having freed Lord Garmadon from Kryptarium Prison the ninja are beset by doubts particularly Lloyd. Lord Garmadon and Lloyd journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 23:45:00" d="2020-11-06 23:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (2)</n>    <k>81% The Remote
The Wattersons are a totally normal family. Dad is your regular 6”4 pink rabbit who stays at home while Mom works in a rainbow factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-06 23:55:00" d="2020-11-07 00:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (2)</n>    <k>81% The Remote
The Wattersons are a totally normal family. Dad is your regular 6”4 pink rabbit who stays at home while Mom works in a rainbow factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 00:05:00" d="2020-11-07 00:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (3)</n>    <k>The Flower
The Wattersons are a totally normal family. Dad is your regular 6”4 pink rabbit who stays at home while Mom works in a rainbow factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 00:20:00" d="2020-11-07 00:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (4)</n>    <k>The Extras
Nothing much is happening for Gumball and Darwin and the background characters in Elmore seize their moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 00:30:00" d="2020-11-07 00:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (5)</n>    <k>The Gripes
Gumball is in such a bad mood that it spreads to Darwin who joins him in complaining about everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 00:40:00" d="2020-11-07 00:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (5)</n>    <k>The Vacation
The Wattersons are swapping scary stories on a family vacation when their car breaks down in the middle of the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 00:50:00" d="2020-11-07 01:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (6)</n>    <k>The Fraud
When Gumball and Darwin discover his diploma is fake Principal Brown is determined to keep their discovery a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 01:00:00" d="2020-11-07 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (41)</n>    <k>59% Professor Angelo
After making a bet that their life is harder Angelo and Mr. Foot trade places. Angelo becomes the teacher and Mr. Foot the unruly student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 01:10:00" d="2020-11-07 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (42)</n>    <k>59% The Future Of Us
After taking a career test that claims to predict your future and receiving disappointing results Angelo and friends set out to change their destinies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 01:25:00" d="2020-11-07 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (43)</n>    <k>59% Fake News
The line for Adventureparkland’s newest ride is way too long so Angelo and the gang decide to spread rumors of wolves attacking people at the park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 01:35:00" d="2020-11-07 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (44)</n>    <k>59% The Replacements
With Lola and Sherwood away Angelo interviews and auditions potential replacements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 01:45:00" d="2020-11-07 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (45)</n>    <k>59% Monster at the Door
After Angelo trashes Burst’s stage set his punishment is that he must star in Burst’s unusual arty play. With Sherwood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 01:55:00" d="2020-11-07 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (46)</n>    <k>59% Videogame Style
After accidentally breaking a window Angelo and friends complete a series of chores at the rec center as pay back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 02:05:00" d="2020-11-07 02:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (1)</n>    <k>59% Dumb Phone
To convince his parents to buy him a phone Angelo must turn his text addicted sister into a smart phone role model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 02:20:00" d="2020-11-07 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (2)</n>    <k>59% The Note King
After Mr. Foot confiscates all electronics before class Angelo and friends have to kick it old school and pass hand written notes to communicate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 02:25:00" d="2020-11-07 02:35:00"><n u="Mighty Magiswords">Mighty Magiswords III (19)</n>    <k>52% Working Grup
The Warriors go to Grup’s workplace and must resist the temptation to steal the sword that is Grup’s job to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 02:35:00" d="2020-11-07 02:55:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu VIII (8017)</n>    <k>66% The Mask of Deception
When an unknown criminal syndicate threatens the Royal Family the Ninja are called back into action and must protect the royal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 02:55:00" d="2020-11-07 03:15:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu VIII (8018)</n>    <k>66% The Jade Princess
NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu centers on the adventures of five ninjas. The show is set in the fictional world of Ninjago a place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 03:15:00" d="2020-11-07 03:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (15)</n>    <k>The Oracle
Gumball Darwin and Anais discover that Banana Joe’s mom paints pictures which predict the future</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 03:25:00" d="2020-11-07 03:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (15)</n>    <k>The Safety
When Mr Small shows a health and safety video in class Darwin becomes obsessed with the idea of keeping the Wattersons safe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 03:35:00" d="2020-11-07 03:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (16)</n>    <k>The Friend
Anais throws a party but no-one shows up as she has no friends or social skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 03:45:00" d="2020-11-07 03:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (17)</n>    <k>The Awareness
Gumball tries to convince Leslie he's an expert on all things plant-related. However, when Leslie realises Gumball hasn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 03:55:00" d="2020-11-07 04:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (18)</n>    <k>The Parents
After accidentally bumping into each other in the grocery aisle, Nicole and her parents have it out. The Wattersons discover why Nicole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 04:10:00" d="2020-11-07 04:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (19)</n>    <k>The Founder
When Nicole decides to pay the cable bill in person at Chanax , she leaves specific instructions for Richard to stay in the car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 04:20:00" d="2020-11-07 04:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (20)</n>    <k>The Schooling
Gumball and Darwin are at the convenience store considering playing truant. Larry warns them that if they don't take their education</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 04:30:00" d="2020-11-07 04:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (21)</n>    <k>The Intelligence
Gumball and Darwin argue with the Internet and make him mad. So mad in fact that he seeks to wipe out humanity and, whilst doing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 04:40:00" d="2020-11-07 04:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (22)</n>    <k>The Potion
Gumball and Darwin learn that Hector is not so happy being giant-sized. So they decide to help him by creating a potion that will shrink</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-11-07 04:50:00" d="2020-11-07 05:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (23)</n>    <k>The Spinoffs
Wishing to get rid of Gumball once and for all his nemesis Rob offers up a variety of reality action and comedy shows featuring characters</k>  </p>
</a>
