<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="109" t="2020-10-23 04:49:39"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 05:00:00" d="2020-10-30 05:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (9)</n>    <k>The Cringe
Gumball and Hotdog Kid discover why they're so awkward with each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 05:15:00" d="2020-10-30 05:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (8)</n>    <k>The Neighbor
When their neighbour tries to bring over a package for them, Gumball and Darwin realise they have never learned his name</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 05:25:00" d="2020-10-30 05:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (11)</n>    <k>The Pact
Gumball finds Penny's laugh annoying, but can't think of a way to tell her without offending her. When he discovers that Principal Brown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 05:35:00" d="2020-10-30 05:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (13)</n>    <k>The Candidate
When their parents all go to a charity gala at the school, the kids are locked in a classroom with a VHS tape. However, when the room starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 05:45:00" d="2020-10-30 06:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (10)</n>    <k>81% The Anybody
Gumball wants Clayton to sit his detention for him, so convinces him it's way more exciting to be take the shapes of other people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 06:00:00" d="2020-10-30 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (15)</n>    <k>Steam is the Word
In the heart of Silicon Valley, Ben has to stop Victorian villain Steam Smythe from securing an epic power source sealed in a Tesla time capsule</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 06:10:00" d="2020-10-30 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (24)</n>    <k>Recipe for Disaster
During Chefapalooza in the Rocky Mountains, three famous chefs and infamous bad-guys The Tri-Chefta hunt down Wildvine in hopes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 06:25:00" d="2020-10-30 06:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (16)</n>    <k>The Romantic
After Gumball convinces himself that Penny doesn't love him as much as she used to, he decides to put together a romantic quest to remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 06:40:00" d="2020-10-30 06:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (17)</n>    <k>The Uploads
Gumball and Darwin try to tear themselves away from the internet but end up falling down the Elmore Stream-hole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 06:55:00" d="2020-10-30 07:05:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (41)</n>    <k>Costume Contest
Sick of losing the costume contest to the Hive Five every year the Titans hatch a scheme to win</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 07:05:00" d="2020-10-30 07:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (42)</n>    <k>52% The Self-Indulgent 200th Episode Spectacular!: Part 1
The Titans must confront their creators</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 07:25:00" d="2020-10-30 07:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (9)</n>    <k>52% The Streak: Part 1
It's Crime Season and Robin is determined to continue his streak of stopping 52 crimes every year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 07:35:00" d="2020-10-30 07:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (10)</n>    <k>52% The Streak: Part 2
Robin's streak of stopping 52 crimes every year is in jeopardy when members of his team are poached by Kid Flash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 07:50:00" d="2020-10-30 08:00:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (5)</n>    <k>65% #AdventuresInBunnysitting
Zee asks Kara to look after her two magical bunnies which quickly start to multiply wreaking havoc all across Metropolis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 08:00:00" d="2020-10-30 08:20:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (6)</n>    <k>#HateTriangle
When Hal's ex-girlfriend shows up at the Metropolis High homecoming game and goes love-ballistic as the villain Star Sapphire Jessica begins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 08:20:00" d="2020-10-30 08:30:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears I (2)</n>    <k>Viral Video
The Bears think they have what it takes to make a viral video and star in it, but when Nom-Nom decides that they don’t, Grizz breaks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 08:30:00" d="2020-10-30 08:40:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears I (3)</n>    <k>Our Stuff
After the Bears play a little pickup basketball (they're very bad), they go back to grab their stuff by the side of the court</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 08:40:00" d="2020-10-30 08:55:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears I (4)</n>    <k>Chloe
Chloe spends time with the Bears in an effort to research them for an upcoming presentation. But when the Bears sneak a peek at her very dry report</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 08:55:00" d="2020-10-30 09:05:00"><n u="Craig of the Creek">Craig of the Creek I (2)</n>    <k>Itch to Explore
Craig's quest to map the entire Creek takes him and his friends into the treacherous Poison Ivy Grove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 09:05:00" d="2020-10-30 09:25:00"><n u="Craig of the Creek">Craig of the Creek I (3)</n>    <k>70% Jessica Goes to the Creek
When Craig and Jessica are locked out of the house Craig has no choice but to bring his little sister to the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 09:25:00" d="2020-10-30 09:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan I (6)</n>    <k>48% Dog Daze
Lightning discovers a new Bakugan Artulean leading to an unhealthy rivalry with Howlkor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 09:35:00" d="2020-10-30 09:55:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan I (6)</n>    <k>48% In Focus
While Lia's newswoman mom does an expose on the AO Strata the Hunter tries to capture Hydorous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 09:55:00" d="2020-10-30 10:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (34)</n>    <k>The Factory
Gumball and Darwin follow Nicole to the Rainbow Factory for Bring your Kids to Work Day. They are expecting a magical place full of dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 10:05:00" d="2020-10-30 10:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (35)</n>    <k>The Revolt
Darwin tries to highlight the plight of all the household objects he feels are being oppressed and maltreated by the uncaring residents of Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 10:20:00" d="2020-10-30 10:30:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (38)</n>    <k>65% Badge-a-fire Explosion
When BC comes out of a rare state of hyper-focused creativity he may have made something that could destroy all of PHV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 10:30:00" d="2020-10-30 10:50:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (9)</n>    <k>Bao Bao's Revenge
When Mao Mao's old partner threatens the kingdom his friends will need to learn about his past in order to protect the present</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 10:50:00" d="2020-10-30 11:00:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (1)</n>    <k>Unboxing Part 1
Axel ventures into his uncle's strictly off-limits basement lab in hopes of fixing a broken toy and ends up unleashing living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 11:00:00" d="2020-10-30 11:20:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (2)</n>    <k>Unboxing Part 2
Axel discovers that he can transform into a toy and teams up with his new team of toys to stop Madcap from stealing a Minergy battery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 11:20:00" d="2020-10-30 11:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (14)</n>    <k>Black Friday
Starfire is visited by three ghosts and shown the true meaning of Black Friday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 11:30:00" d="2020-10-30 11:45:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (20)</n>    <k>52% Squash and Stretch
The Titans learn about cartoon-style violence in order to get revenge on a snack-stealing squirrel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 11:45:00" d="2020-10-30 11:55:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (30)</n>    <k>52% Stockton CA!
The Titans must find a way to keep all the Jump City residents from moving to Stockton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 11:55:00" d="2020-10-30 12:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (31)</n>    <k>Collect Them All
After the other Titans are turned into collectibles and disappear Robin must search yard sales and stores to find them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 12:10:00" d="2020-10-30 12:20:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (22)</n>    <k>52% Orangins
The Titans tell their slightly inaccurate origin stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 12:20:00" d="2020-10-30 12:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (23)</n>    <k>52% Jinxed
Robin ignores the rules for a game of jinx and ends up losing his voice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 12:40:00" d="2020-10-30 12:50:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (39)</n>    <k>65% Zing Your Heart Out
When Adorabat starts to aggressively heckle everyone with her new zing power she threatens the entire kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 12:50:00" d="2020-10-30 13:05:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (10)</n>    <k>The Truth Stinks
Badgerclops smells but Mao Mao and Adorabat don't know how to tell him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 13:05:00" d="2020-10-30 13:15:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (6)</n>    <k>Guardian of the Unikingdom
Hawkodile insists the Unikingdom is more dangerous than it looks and sets out to prove it by taking his friends on bodyguard patrol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 13:15:00" d="2020-10-30 13:35:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (7)</n>    <k>Cast Aside the Truth
Hawkodile breaks his arm in a careless spill and lies to his friends about the accident to keep from looking bad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 13:35:00" d="2020-10-30 13:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (4)</n>    <k>81% The Boredom
Gumball and Darwin are convinced it's one of those days when nothing interesting is happening. But as they walk around Elmore in search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 13:50:00" d="2020-10-30 14:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (5)</n>    <k>81% The Vision
When Gumball and Darwin accidentally find a sinister secret manifesto on Alan's memory stick, they decide they have to foil his plan for total</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 14:05:00" d="2020-10-30 14:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (6)</n>    <k>81% The Choices
When a typically stressful Watterson family dinner pushes her to the edge of her sanity, Nicole starts reminiscing about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 14:15:00" d="2020-10-30 14:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (7)</n>    <k>81% The Code
Gumball learns that the Wattersons have been stealing Mr Robinson's wi-fi for years. When it goes down they try and live without</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 14:30:00" d="2020-10-30 14:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (8)</n>    <k>81% The Test
Gumball is livid when an online test keeps telling him that his character-type is &quot;The Loser&quot;. He's convinced that the only way to shake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 14:40:00" d="2020-10-30 14:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (9)</n>    <k>81% The Slide
A chance encounter with the woman of his dreams inspires Rocky to stop living life online and find love with the help of the latest dating app</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 14:55:00" d="2020-10-30 15:05:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (12)</n>    <k>65% #SheMightBeGiant
Karen Beecher is always getting picked on at school but when the local mall is attacked by a monstrous supervillain called Giganta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 15:05:00" d="2020-10-30 15:25:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (8)</n>    <k>65% #MeetTheCheetah
Barbara Minerva is super-jealous of little Miss Perfect Diana Prince</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 15:25:00" d="2020-10-30 15:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (33)</n>    <k>52% Next Top Talent Idol Star: Part 1
The Justice League holds a talent competition to find a superhero worthy of joining the team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 15:35:00" d="2020-10-30 15:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (34)</n>    <k>52% Justice League's Next Top Talent Idol Star: Part 2
The competition heats up as Robin tries everything to win</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 15:50:00" d="2020-10-30 16:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (6)</n>    <k>52% I'm the Sauce
Stuck inside because of bad weather the Titans play rainy day games after Robin convinces them that indoor activites will cheer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 16:00:00" d="2020-10-30 16:20:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (7)</n>    <k>Accept the Next Proposition You Hear
Robin refuses to give the Titans any more orders so that they'll learn to think for themselves. Instead the Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 16:20:00" d="2020-10-30 16:30:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (26)</n>    <k>Snow Way Out
Owen wants everyone to love his new snowsuit and envy him but it's just not working out that way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 16:30:00" d="2020-10-30 16:40:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (27)</n>    <k>49% All Up in Your Drill
Duncan stages a small coup to oust Courtney as their official class firefighter so that he can wear the shiny firefighter helmet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 16:40:00" d="2020-10-30 16:55:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (28)</n>    <k>Toys Will Be Toys
Courtney becomes a toy tester but forgets that the most important thing is to have fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 16:55:00" d="2020-10-30 17:05:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (33)</n>    <k>49% Melter Skelter
When Chef tells Beth he won't buy the new super amazing toy she wants because they already have plenty to play with she goes on a mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 17:05:00" d="2020-10-30 17:15:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (34)</n>    <k>49% The Never Gwending Story
When Chef loses the last page of the story-time book Gwen takes over and creates a monster that all the kids start to believe in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 17:15:00" d="2020-10-30 17:25:00"><n u="Mighty Magiswords">Mighty Magiswords III (15)</n>    <k>52% The Saddest Little Bunny
The Warriors encounter a stoic warrior bunny whom they misinterpret as “sad” and try to cheer him up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 17:25:00" d="2020-10-30 17:35:00"><n u="Apple &amp; Onion">Apple &amp; Onion I (25)</n>    <k>Face Your Fears
Apple and Onion must face their fears while trapped in a pet shop so they can save French Fry from facing hers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 17:35:00" d="2020-10-30 17:55:00"><n u="Apple &amp; Onion">Apple &amp; Onion I (26)</n>    <k>60% Follow Your Dreams
Apple and Onion need to find a dream to follow so that their lives don't head nowhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 17:55:00" d="2020-10-30 18:05:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (6)</n>    <k>Guardian of the Unikingdom
Hawkodile insists the Unikingdom is more dangerous than it looks and sets out to prove it by taking his friends on bodyguard patrol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 18:05:00" d="2020-10-30 18:20:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (7)</n>    <k>Cast Aside the Truth
Hawkodile breaks his arm in a careless spill and lies to his friends about the accident to keep from looking bad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 18:20:00" d="2020-10-30 18:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (12)</n>    <k>52% Animals It's Just a Word!
After the other Titans are injured Beast Boy donates his blood to save them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 18:30:00" d="2020-10-30 18:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (50)</n>    <k>Scary Figure Dance
The Titans' Halloween party is interupted by the Hive Five robbing a candy factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 18:40:00" d="2020-10-30 19:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (13)</n>    <k>BBBDay!
It's Beast Boy's birthday! But will the other Titans remember?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 19:00:00" d="2020-10-30 19:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (9)</n>    <k>The Pest
When they find Anais training herself for a brutal showdown Gumball and Darwin realise that their sister is being pestered at school by an annoying kid: Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 19:10:00" d="2020-10-30 19:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (10)</n>    <k>The Hug
When Darwin taunts Gumball about how predictable he is Gumball tries to prove that he can still surprise his buddy. He thinks that greeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 19:30:00" d="2020-10-30 19:40:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (1)</n>    <k>Unboxing Part 1
Axel ventures into his uncle's strictly off-limits basement lab in hopes of fixing a broken toy and ends up unleashing living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 19:40:00" d="2020-10-30 20:00:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (2)</n>    <k>Unboxing Part 2
Axel discovers that he can transform into a toy and teams up with his new team of toys to stop Madcap from stealing a Minergy battery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 20:00:00" d="2020-10-30 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (17)</n>    <k>All Wet
No one believes Ben when he insists that one of the other patrons waiting on line at the World of Wet Water Park is the nefarious Frightwig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 20:10:00" d="2020-10-30 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (26)</n>    <k>Story Bored
During a book signing at a medieval castle, Ben must stop Hex from getting his hands on a grimoire that can fuse its user with mythical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 20:30:00" d="2020-10-30 20:40:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan I (20)</n>    <k>48% Tripped Up
Dan and Wynton stumble on both a possible hidden location of the Mind Core Cell and Colonel Tripp who wants the energy source for himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 20:40:00" d="2020-10-30 21:00:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan I (20)</n>    <k>48% Power Tripp
After a falling out with Dan Wynton is mind-controlled by Tripp who stages an attack to ig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 21:00:00" d="2020-10-30 21:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (11)</n>    <k>59% Catnapped
Angelo discovers Cathy cat and Joe Mama have been accidentally switched at the Vet. And no one believes Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 21:10:00" d="2020-10-30 21:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (12)</n>    <k>59% Pen Pal
Angelo creates a fake Guatemalan pen pal so he doesn’t fail Mr. Foot’s class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 21:25:00" d="2020-10-30 21:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (13)</n>    <k>59% Employee Of The Month
Angelo becomes an intern at Adventureparkland. But his dream job isn’t all it’s cracked up to be because he has to actually… work!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 21:35:00" d="2020-10-30 21:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (14)</n>    <k>59% Bobbleheads Are Gonna Roll
Miss Perla turns detention time into art therapy where Angelo makes cool bobble-head sculptures which become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 21:55:00" d="2020-10-30 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (15)</n>    <k>59% Secret Recipe
When Cathy hikes the price of her famous cupcake the “Brooklyn Blackout” Lola goes undercover in search of the secret recipe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 22:05:00" d="2020-10-30 22:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (16)</n>    <k>59% Angelo vs. The Test
Angelo shares his tips and tricks for delaying a test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 22:25:00" d="2020-10-30 22:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (17)</n>    <k>59% What Now?
Because of his cunning and tenacity Angelo always gets what he wants. Is this the way life is always going to be? Angelo has an existential crisis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 22:35:00" d="2020-10-30 22:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (18)</n>    <k>59% Grounded
Elena and Angelo are grounded for fighting with each other. They have to put aside their differences and work together to escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 22:50:00" d="2020-10-30 23:20:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu VIII (8011)</n>    <k>66% The Mask of Betrayal
As Lloyd and Harumi search the Oni Temple for the last mask the ninja are taken hostage and discover Princess Harumi’s true intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 23:20:00" d="2020-10-30 23:45:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu VIII (8019)</n>    <k>66% Dread On Arrival
NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu centers on the adventures of five ninjas. The show is set in the fictional world of Ninjago a place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 23:45:00" d="2020-10-30 23:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (9)</n>    <k>The Secret
Gumball almost loses his mind trying to guess Darwin’s secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-30 23:55:00" d="2020-10-31 00:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (10)</n>    <k>The Sock
Gumball and Darwin are taught confusing lessons about honesty by the school councillor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 00:05:00" d="2020-10-31 00:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (10)</n>    <k>The Genius
Darwin is sent away to a government institute for geniuses. Yes. Really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 00:20:00" d="2020-10-31 00:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (19)</n>    <k>The Copycats
Gumball and Darwin are confused when they meet Kiki and Quack, a pair of siblings that copy everything they do and say</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 00:30:00" d="2020-10-31 00:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (20)</n>    <k>81% The Catfish
When Gumball and Darwin realise Grandpa Louie has no friends on Elmore Plus, they feel bad. So they create one - called Muriel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 00:40:00" d="2020-10-31 00:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (21)</n>    <k>81% The Cycle
Gumball, Darwin and Anais discover that Mr Wilson has been picking on their dad for most of his life: ever since he humiliated Richard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 00:50:00" d="2020-10-31 01:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (22)</n>    <k>81% The Stars
When Dad gives Larry's Hairdressers a bad review for saying he's bald, he gets offered a free haircut. This inspires Gumball and Darwin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 01:00:00" d="2020-10-31 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (31)</n>    <k>59% A Perfect Day
Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 01:10:00" d="2020-10-31 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (32)</n>    <k>59% Home Security
When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 01:25:00" d="2020-10-31 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (33)</n>    <k>59% Pow!
Angelo and friends attempt to negotiate a deal for Peter and Cooper’s nonsensical home-made comic book with a famous comic book publisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 01:35:00" d="2020-10-31 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (34)</n>    <k>59% Better Call Angelo
Angelo attempts to rack up the high score on an online business rating service to win free dinner at a fancy Japanese Steak House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 01:45:00" d="2020-10-31 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (35)</n>    <k>59% Electra
When Dad surprises the family with a brand new Electra smart home device everyone loves it at first then Dad gets hooked and Angelo and Elena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 01:55:00" d="2020-10-31 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (36)</n>    <k>59% Best Friends Forever
After failing an online “best friends” quiz Sherwood and Angelo drift apart. Angelo discovers the quiz was fake and tries to repair his relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 02:05:00" d="2020-10-31 02:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (37)</n>    <k>59% Cook Off
Angelo enters a pie baking contest with his Dad as his partner until the two have creative differences and go it alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 02:15:00" d="2020-10-31 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (38)</n>    <k>59% Most Likely to Succeed
Angelo and Lola start a campaign to help Sherwood get voted “most likely to succeed” by his classmates instead of Tracy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 02:25:00" d="2020-10-31 02:35:00"><n u="Mighty Magiswords">Mighty Magiswords III (12)</n>    <k>52% Do We Decimal System?
The Warriors seek a secret book in the Library of Shhh! and their best friend from warrior school Witchy Simone follows them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 02:35:00" d="2020-10-31 02:55:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (12)</n>    <k>66% Firstbourne
While Lloyd and Nya resist Emperor Garmadon's oppressive hold on Ninjago City, Young Wu and the other Ninjas are stranded in a barbaric realm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 02:55:00" d="2020-10-31 03:15:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (8)</n>    <k>66% Iron and Stone
Cole and Young Wu attempt to free their friends who have been taken captive by a tribe of Dragon Hunters. Meanwhile in Ninjago Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 03:15:00" d="2020-10-31 03:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (10)</n>    <k>The Hug
When Darwin taunts Gumball about how predictable he is Gumball tries to prove that he can still surprise his buddy. He thinks that greeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 03:25:00" d="2020-10-31 03:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (11)</n>    <k>The Sale
Gumball and Darwin are devastated to learn that Mr Robinson - their favourite person in the world - is selling his house and leaving town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 03:35:00" d="2020-10-31 03:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (12)</n>    <k>The Routine
Mum and the kids depart for their hard day's work, leaving a seemingly lazy Dad half-asleep on the sofa. Mum has given him one very simple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 03:45:00" d="2020-10-31 03:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (14)</n>    <k>81% The Shippening
When people that barely know each other start falling in love, Gumball thinks he knows who's behind it. He rushes to Sarah's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 03:55:00" d="2020-10-31 04:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (16)</n>    <k>The Stink
Gumball decides to put Mr.Small's eco-friendly principles to the test but it doesn't quite go as planned. Mr.Small disappears after deciding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 04:10:00" d="2020-10-31 04:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (17)</n>    <k>The Awareness
Gumball tries to convince Leslie he's an expert on all things plant-related. However, when Leslie realises Gumball hasn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 04:20:00" d="2020-10-31 04:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (18)</n>    <k>The Parents
After accidentally bumping into each other in the grocery aisle, Nicole and her parents have it out. The Wattersons discover why Nicole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 04:30:00" d="2020-10-31 04:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (19)</n>    <k>The Founder
When Nicole decides to pay the cable bill in person at Chanax , she leaves specific instructions for Richard to stay in the car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 04:40:00" d="2020-10-31 04:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (20)</n>    <k>The Schooling
Gumball and Darwin are at the convenience store considering playing truant. Larry warns them that if they don't take their education</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-10-31 04:50:00" d="2020-10-31 05:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (21)</n>    <k>The Intelligence
Gumball and Darwin argue with the Internet and make him mad. So mad in fact that he seeks to wipe out humanity and, whilst doing</k>  </p>
</a>
