<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="113" t="2020-10-26 03:39:04"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 05:05:00" d="2020-11-02 05:15:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Brain Food
BB avoids being the dumb one by making the rest of the Titans dumber which leaves only Silkie to save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 05:15:00" d="2020-11-02 05:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In and Out
Robin goes undercover to destroy the Hive. ight after he enjoys some of their perks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 05:25:00" d="2020-11-02 05:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Little Buddies
Cyborg wants Pain Bot to be his “little buddy” but is the destructive robot too dangerous to be a sidekick?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 05:35:00" d="2020-11-02 05:45:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Missing
Killer Moth offers a reward for Silkie's return but will Silkier be happier away from the Titans?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 05:45:00" d="2020-11-02 06:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Uncle Jokes
BB and Cyborg invite Starfire to join in their fun as long as she avoids dreaded uncle jokes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 06:00:00" d="2020-11-02 06:05:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Swine Dining
When Daffy discovers he's on the menu at Porky's restaurant he decides to change the main ingredient to mayhem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 06:05:00" d="2020-11-02 06:10:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Love Is in the Hare
Bugs' day at the lake is interrupted by Yosemite Sam. To get Sam off his back Bugs puts him through obstacles and a full makeover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 06:10:00" d="2020-11-02 06:15:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Valentine's Dayffy
On Valentine's Day Daffy runs into Cupid and knocks him out. The incapacitated Cupid gives Daffy his quiver and bow and tells him to spread love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 06:15:00" d="2020-11-02 06:20:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Bigs Bunny
A search for food lands Bugs and Squeaks in a run-in with the Barbarian and Krakos the Bear. When the Barbarian decides he wants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 06:20:00" d="2020-11-02 06:32:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Wahder Wahder Everywhere
Before his home lake is drained away Daffy has to step in to put stop Elmer Fudd's new artesian mineral water bottling business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 06:32:00" d="2020-11-02 06:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Porky the Disorderly
When Daffy runs wild in a hospital it's up to Porky the orderly to get him to leave but Daffy has different plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 06:35:00" d="2020-11-02 06:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Game Set Wabbit
Bugs serves up trouble as he teaches Viktor a lesson in humility competing for the championship at the Simpledon tennis tournament</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 06:40:00" d="2020-11-02 06:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Lucky Duck
Down on his luck Shameless O'Scanty mistakes Daffy for a lucky charm. Shameless tries to capture the Lucky Duck only to find himself more luckless than ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 06:45:00" d="2020-11-02 07:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Free Range Foghorn
Daffy stumbles across Foghorn's farm and witnesses the sweet life of the free range chickens. Daffy sneaks in to take advantage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 07:00:00" d="2020-11-02 07:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Choices
When a typically stressful Watterson family dinner pushes her to the edge of her sanity, Nicole starts reminiscing about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 07:10:00" d="2020-11-02 07:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Code
Gumball learns that the Wattersons have been stealing Mr Robinson's wi-fi for years. When it goes down they try and live without</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 07:30:00" d="2020-11-02 07:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Test
Gumball is livid when an online test keeps telling him that his character-type is &quot;The Loser&quot;. He's convinced that the only way to shake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 07:40:00" d="2020-11-02 08:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Slide
A chance encounter with the woman of his dreams inspires Rocky to stop living life online and find love with the help of the latest dating app</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 08:00:00" d="2020-11-02 08:10:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% Dungeon Party!
Cole awakens from a dream to find himself surrounded by the Lowly, Master Wu and Princess Vania. The Lowly reveal they were adventurers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 08:10:00" d="2020-11-02 08:25:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% Dungeon Crawl!
Cole leads the Lowly and Princess Vania and Wu in a series of fruitless efforts to find a way out of Rock-Bottom. Wu tells Cole about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 08:25:00" d="2020-11-02 08:35:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% The Cliffs of Hysteria
The ninja arrive at the Cliffs of Hysteria and are spotted by one of Unagami’s aerial drones. A squadron of Red Visors quickly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 08:35:00" d="2020-11-02 08:45:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% The Maze of the Red Dragon
Unagami promises Okino that if he betrays the ninja, he will bring him with into the real world. Okino struggles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 08:45:00" d="2020-11-02 09:00:00"><n u="The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe">The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Prince and the Hissy Swan
Ivandoe comes face to face with a cocky young swan prince. To settle their differences they engage in a good old-fashioned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 09:00:00" d="2020-11-02 09:10:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Adoradad
When AD's dad forbids her from working with the Sheriff's Dept because it's too dangerous AD sets out to prove that she can take care of herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 09:10:00" d="2020-11-02 09:25:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Badge-a-fire Explosion
When BC comes out of a rare state of hyper-focused creativity he may have made something that could destroy all of PHV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 09:25:00" d="2020-11-02 09:35:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% I Love You Mao Mao
An explosive loner and his slacker best friend are waylaid from their journey into legend, only to find that their story is just beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 09:35:00" d="2020-11-02 10:00:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The Perfect Adventure
When Mao Mao gets hungry for the perfect adventure Adorabat tells a white lie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 10:00:00" d="2020-11-02 10:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% I'm the Sauce
Stuck inside because of bad weather the Titans play rainy day games after Robin convinces them that indoor activites will cheer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 10:10:00" d="2020-11-02 10:15:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Accept the Next Proposition You Hear
Robin refuses to give the Titans any more orders so that they'll learn to think for themselves. Instead the Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 10:15:00" d="2020-11-02 10:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hey You, Don't Forget About Me in Your Memory
Robin convinces the Titans to go back to school with him so he can finally become the all-American class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 10:35:00" d="2020-11-02 10:45:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Fourth Wall
Control Freak informs the Titans that they are on a TV show he created and demands they earn him an award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 10:45:00" d="2020-11-02 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>40%, 40%, 20%
Cyborg's real strength comes not from his robot parts but from his favourite song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 11:00:00" d="2020-11-02 11:10:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Road Trip
Chloe and the Bears take a road trip to see a meteor shower. Ice Bear, the only one licensed to drive, is put in charge, which becomes harder than he thought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 11:10:00" d="2020-11-02 11:30:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Chloe and Ice Bear
On a day out with just Chloe and Ice Bear, she realises that Ice Bear only runs errands for his brothers. Determined to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 11:30:00" d="2020-11-02 11:40:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Chicken and Waffles
Panda needs to meet his brothers at the most exclusive restaurant in town. But when he loses his contacts lenses and can't see, Panda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 11:40:00" d="2020-11-02 12:00:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Icy Nights
Ice Bear rides his custom vacuum into the city. But when a gang of techies steal the vacuum, Ice Bear goes on a rescue mission that takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 12:00:00" d="2020-11-02 12:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Responsible
Gumball and Darwin babysit Anais “responsibly” whilst “irresponsibly” flooding the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 12:10:00" d="2020-11-02 12:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Dress
Gumball goes to school in a dress and becomes the darling of Elmore High</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 12:30:00" d="2020-11-02 12:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Laziest
Gumball and Darwin challenge Dad to a “lazy-off”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 12:40:00" d="2020-11-02 13:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Ghost
Gumball must learn to say “no” when Carrie the Ghost uses his body against his will</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 13:00:00" d="2020-11-02 13:10:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unikitty and the Ice Pop Factory
An eccentric figure announces a contest to tour her marvelous ice pop factory sending the gang on a frantic quest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 13:10:00" d="2020-11-02 13:25:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Castles and Kitties
Score Creeper traps the gang in a fantasy role playing game where they must follow a complex set of rules to win their freedom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 13:25:00" d="2020-11-02 13:35:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dinner Apart-y
Unikitty and Puppycorn are invited to Master Frown and Brock's apartment for a dinner party. But the two roommates are butting heads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 13:35:00" d="2020-11-02 14:00:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>License to Punch
In a joyous kingdom full of sparkle matter, happy thoughts and the occasional rage-out, join Unikitty and a whole cast of friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 14:00:00" d="2020-11-02 14:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% I'm the Sauce
Stuck inside because of bad weather the Titans play rainy day games after Robin convinces them that indoor activites will cheer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 14:10:00" d="2020-11-02 14:15:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Accept the Next Proposition You Hear
Robin refuses to give the Titans any more orders so that they'll learn to think for themselves. Instead the Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 14:15:00" d="2020-11-02 14:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hey You, Don't Forget About Me in Your Memory
Robin convinces the Titans to go back to school with him so he can finally become the all-American class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 14:35:00" d="2020-11-02 14:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Fourth Wall
Control Freak informs the Titans that they are on a TV show he created and demands they earn him an award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 14:40:00" d="2020-11-02 15:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>40%, 40%, 20%
Cyborg's real strength comes not from his robot parts but from his favourite song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 15:00:00" d="2020-11-02 15:10:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Zing Your Heart Out
When Adorabat starts to aggressively heckle everyone with her new zing power she threatens the entire kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 15:10:00" d="2020-11-02 15:25:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Strange Bedfellows
After an insane battle MM and OS end up in the same hospital room. But even in full body casts the sworn enemies continue the fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 15:25:00" d="2020-11-02 15:35:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>All By Mao Self
Mao Mao's desire to be a legend drives him to keep topping himself. But how much is enough?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 15:35:00" d="2020-11-02 16:00:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ultraclops
Badgerclops gets huge to destroy a towering monster but when he refuses to shrink down the kingdom faces a new terror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 16:00:00" d="2020-11-02 16:10:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% Grief-Bringer
Nya uses her elemental powers to coerce the Munce into agreeing to a truce meeting with the Geckles. At the same time, in the Geckle camp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 16:10:00" d="2020-11-02 16:25:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% Masters Never Quit
Cole, Princess Vania, Master Wu and the Lowly arrive at an ancient abandoned temple. Wu realizes it is The Heart Of the Mountain.The</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 16:25:00" d="2020-11-02 16:35:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% Wasted True Potential
Having grown complacent in the wake of their victory over the Oni, the ninja are enjoying life, playing video-games, sleeping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 16:35:00" d="2020-11-02 17:00:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% Questing For Quests
The ninja set about trying to find a quest to get back in shape. Unfortunately, they discover this is easier said than done</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 17:00:00" d="2020-11-02 17:10:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>That Slobot is No Bot of Mine
Axel and the team compete against themselves in tests of skill, strength and stamina, but when SloBot gets belittled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 17:10:00" d="2020-11-02 17:25:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sarge in Charge
Axel and the team must rescue Sarge Charge from a solo mission in the backyard which Orangutank has turned into his own personal heart of darkness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 17:25:00" d="2020-11-02 17:35:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bobbie Not Blobby
Axel discovers that the culprit behind Bobbie Blobby's missing mech-suit is Masko who only wanted to clean out its clogged clay cannons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 17:35:00" d="2020-11-02 17:50:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Access Denied
When Axel and the team try to figure out what Sarge Charge's secret weapon is they get ejected from the house by his newly upgraded security</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 17:50:00" d="2020-11-02 18:00:00"><n u="The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe">The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Prince and the Kissy Frog
Ivandoe and Bert come across a tiny miserable prince in the forest. He needs a kiss to transform him back into the beautiful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 18:00:00" d="2020-11-02 18:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Villain Time
Ben must go alien to save the Hoover Dam from disaster but when tough guy hero Tim Buktu swoops in to &quot;help&quot; Ben must figure out if Tim is friend… or foe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 18:10:00" d="2020-11-02 18:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Something I Ate
Ben, Gwen and Max go on a tour of the impervious Fort Knox but when Dr. Animo sicks a hungry ani-mutate on the Fort</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 18:30:00" d="2020-11-02 18:40:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% The Mysterious Boy
After stopping Tiko’s rampage, the Awesome Brawlers have become world-famous heroes and Bakugan-mania sweeps the globe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 18:40:00" d="2020-11-02 19:00:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% A New Power
A Rogue brawler, Ajit and his golden Bakugan have crashed the Awesome Brawlers party. Who is this brawler? How can he control a Golden Bakugan? Only one way to find out – Bakugan Brawl! Dan and Drago go head to head with the outsides to get to the botto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 19:00:00" d="2020-11-02 19:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Double Trouble
Cyborg and Beast Boy create clones of themselves to do their chores and the clones create more clones until the situation grows out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 19:10:00" d="2020-11-02 19:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Date
Robin poses as Speedy to sabotage his upcoming date with Starfire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 19:25:00" d="2020-11-02 19:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Dude Relax!
Robin’s intensity is distracting the team so they put him on forced hiatus where Beast Boy teaches him how to goof off and relax</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 19:35:00" d="2020-11-02 20:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Laundry Day
The gang don't do they're chores until their laundry comes alive and attacks them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 20:00:00" d="2020-11-02 20:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Name
When Mum reveals that Gumball's real name is Zach Gumball adopts a cheesy annoying persona to match the name</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 20:10:00" d="2020-11-02 20:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Extras
Nothing much is happening for Gumball and Darwin and the background characters in Elmore seize their moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 20:20:00" d="2020-11-02 20:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Gripes
Gumball is in such a bad mood that it spreads to Darwin who joins him in complaining about everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 20:40:00" d="2020-11-02 20:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Vacation
The Wattersons are swapping scary stories on a family vacation when their car breaks down in the middle of the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 20:50:00" d="2020-11-02 21:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fraud
When Gumball and Darwin discover his diploma is fake Principal Brown is determined to keep their discovery a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 21:00:00" d="2020-11-02 21:10:00"><n u="Steven Universe">Steven Universe I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Together Breakfast
Steven tries to get the Crystal Gems to take part in his special breakfast tradition but instead finds himself tumbling through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 21:10:00" d="2020-11-02 21:20:00"><n u="Steven Universe">Steven Universe I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cat Fingers
Steven attempts to master the power of shape shifting but can only shape shift his fingers into tiny cat heads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 21:20:00" d="2020-11-02 21:35:00"><n u="Steven Universe">Steven Universe I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bubble Buddies
Steven looks like a hero when he forms a magic crystal bubble around himself to protect a girl he likes from danger but then panics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 21:35:00" d="2020-11-02 21:55:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu X (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Endings
At the Monastery of Spinjitzu, everyone is preparing for the final battle. Kai recreates the Four Golden Weapons which is their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 21:55:00" d="2020-11-02 22:20:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu VIII (8017)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Mask of Deception
When an unknown criminal syndicate threatens the Royal Family the Ninja are called back into action and must protect the royal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 22:20:00" d="2020-11-02 22:40:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu VIII (8018)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Jade Princess
NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu centers on the adventures of five ninjas. The show is set in the fictional world of Ninjago a place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 22:40:00" d="2020-11-02 23:00:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu VIII (8015)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Sons of Garmadon
While Princess Harumi adjusts to life with the ninja Lloyd and Jay search for answers about the Oni Masks while Cole and Zane attempt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 23:00:00" d="2020-11-02 23:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Picnic
Gumball and Darwin barely survive a school picnic in the Forest of Doom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 23:15:00" d="2020-11-02 23:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Goons
Gumball sets out to win his Dad back by winning a blindfolded “dumb” race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 23:25:00" d="2020-11-02 23:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Secret
Gumball almost loses his mind trying to guess Darwin’s secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 23:35:00" d="2020-11-02 23:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Sock
Gumball and Darwin are taught confusing lessons about honesty by the school councillor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-02 23:45:00" d="2020-11-03 00:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Genius
Darwin is sent away to a government institute for geniuses. Yes. Really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 00:00:00" d="2020-11-03 00:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The GI
Gumball and Darwin’s martial arts costumes make them a laughing stock at school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 00:10:00" d="2020-11-03 00:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Kiss
Gumball is traumatised when accidentally kissed on the mouth by his Grandma JoJo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 00:20:00" d="2020-11-03 00:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Party
Gumball and Darwin are invited to a high school party and have to bring a date!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 00:35:00" d="2020-11-03 00:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Refund
Gumball and Darwin unsuccessfully attempt to get a refund for their computer game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 00:45:00" d="2020-11-03 01:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Robot
Gumball discovers that Bobert is planning to take over his identity and replace him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 01:00:00" d="2020-11-03 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Best Sister Ever
In honor of older sisters Slobber offers free tickets to whomever can make the best short film about their older sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 01:10:00" d="2020-11-03 01:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Snow And Tell
Angelo searches for the ultimate object to bring to show and tell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 01:20:00" d="2020-11-03 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Photobomb
Angelo’s photo bombs make him a big hit on the internet and he is loving his newfound popularity. Until Butterfingers starts getting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 01:35:00" d="2020-11-03 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Not Gym Class
The equipment in Coach Zonka’s gym class is deemed a safety hazard so gym class is canceled permanently. Angelo attempts to rally the school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 01:45:00" d="2020-11-03 02:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Van Dunk's Mojo
Everyone’s favorite skater Ollie Van Dunk crashes out in a big contest loses his mojo and quits skating. Angelo and friends try to raise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 02:00:00" d="2020-11-03 02:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Picnic
Gumball and Darwin barely survive a school picnic in the Forest of Doom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 02:10:00" d="2020-11-03 02:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Goons
Gumball sets out to win his Dad back by winning a blindfolded “dumb” race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 02:20:00" d="2020-11-03 02:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Secret
Gumball almost loses his mind trying to guess Darwin’s secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 02:35:00" d="2020-11-03 02:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Sock
Gumball and Darwin are taught confusing lessons about honesty by the school councillor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 02:45:00" d="2020-11-03 03:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Genius
Darwin is sent away to a government institute for geniuses. Yes. Really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 03:00:00" d="2020-11-03 03:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Mustache
Gumball and Darwin’s wish comes true when they suddenly turn into men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 03:10:00" d="2020-11-03 03:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Date The
Gumball discovers the difference between a “date” and a “pet’s funeral”. he hard way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 03:20:00" d="2020-11-03 03:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Club
When Gumball rejects “The Rejects Club” the rejects wreak their revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 03:35:00" d="2020-11-03 03:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Wand
Gumball and Darwin make their dad believe in magic again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 03:45:00" d="2020-11-03 04:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Ape
Ms Simian sets out to “befriend” Gumball in order to win a Favourite Teacher Award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 04:00:00" d="2020-11-03 04:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>High Stress Express
During a live feed of the new transcontinental bullet train, La Grange enters the picture to outrace the train but Ben joins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 04:10:00" d="2020-11-03 04:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Creature Feature
When Max dozes off before a double feature, Ben and Gwen are left to save the drive-in by themselves as the evil magician Hex brings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 04:20:00" d="2020-11-03 04:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Drone On
Ben and Gwen are in a highly competitive paper airplane war but when alien-tech drones bombard the Rustbucket, the cousins must work together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 04:30:00" d="2020-11-03 04:40:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% The Mysterious Boy
After stopping Tiko’s rampage, the Awesome Brawlers have become world-famous heroes and Bakugan-mania sweeps the globe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 04:40:00" d="2020-11-03 04:55:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% A New Power
A Rogue brawler, Ajit and his golden Bakugan have crashed the Awesome Brawlers party. Who is this brawler? How can he control a Golden Bakugan? Only one way to find out – Bakugan Brawl! Dan and Drago go head to head with the outsides to get to the botto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-11-03 04:55:00" d="2020-11-03 05:05:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mas Y Menos
Robin tries to teach his superhero ways to Spanish speaking brothers Mas y Menos</k>  </p>
</a>
