<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="118" t="2020-10-23 04:34:58"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 05:00:00" d="2020-10-30 05:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Left Leg
When the gang bands together to form a giant robot Robin is relegated to the left leg - but he makes the left leg count!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 05:10:00" d="2020-10-30 05:20:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Books
Raven shows the rest of the Titans that books can be fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 05:20:00" d="2020-10-30 05:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lazy Sunday
When the Titans replace the couch with a treadmill Cyborg and Beast Boy must get guidance from the couch spirit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 05:30:00" d="2020-10-30 05:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Starfire the Terrible
When Robin needs an archenemy Starfire generously offers to fill the role and she exceeds expectations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 05:40:00" d="2020-10-30 05:54:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Second Christmas
The Titans trick Starfire into believing in second Christmas with second Santa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 05:54:00" d="2020-10-30 06:00:00"><n u="The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe">The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Prince and the Kissy Frog
Ivandoe and Bert come across a tiny miserable prince in the forest. He needs a kiss to transform him back into the beautiful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 06:00:00" d="2020-10-30 06:05:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The Grand Barbari-yon
Bugs and Squeaks take a trip to the Grand Canyon only to have their travels sidelined by a run-in with the Barbarian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 06:05:00" d="2020-10-30 06:10:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Giant Rabbit Hunters
The dim hunters believe Bigfoot is a giant rabbit and hunt him. Bugs just wants to be left alone but keeps getting involved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 06:10:00" d="2020-10-30 06:15:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Amusement Pork
Bugs wants to be the first to ride a new mega roller coaster and finds himself lucky to be front and center with Porky Pig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 06:15:00" d="2020-10-30 06:20:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Now You See Me Now You Still See Me
Bugs attempts to help Dr. Clovenhoof become the Superhero he's always dreamed of becoming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 06:20:00" d="2020-10-30 06:25:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Tis the Seasoning
Bugs and Yosemite Sam fight over the last hot toy of the holiday season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 06:25:00" d="2020-10-30 06:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Winter Blunderland
When Squeaks mistakes the Barbarian for Santa Claus Bugs has to intervene in order to retrieve his Holiday Wish List</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 06:35:00" d="2020-10-30 06:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Ear! We! Go!
Bugs' slumber is interrupted when his ears decide it's time to go dancing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 06:40:00" d="2020-10-30 06:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Hare Band
Bugs and Squeaks square off as street musicians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 06:45:00" d="2020-10-30 06:50:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Bugs in the Petting Zoo
Bugs is tricked into Elmer Fudd's new Petting Zoo but Bugs is quick to make his escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 06:50:00" d="2020-10-30 07:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Hawaiian Ice
Bugs' vacation to Hawaii is frozen over when The Winter Stag shows up with the same idea. Is the vacation of a lifetime hot or cold?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 07:00:00" d="2020-10-30 07:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Butterfly
In Biology class Gumball and Darwin are waiting for a butterfly to emerge from its chrysalis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 07:10:00" d="2020-10-30 07:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Question
After Gumball and Darwin have too much sugary cereal they begin thinking about the mysteries of the universe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 07:20:00" d="2020-10-30 07:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Oracle
Gumball Darwin and Anais discover that Banana Joe’s mom paints pictures which predict the future</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 07:35:00" d="2020-10-30 07:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Safety
When Mr Small shows a health and safety video in class Darwin becomes obsessed with the idea of keeping the Wattersons safe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 07:45:00" d="2020-10-30 08:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Society
Things aren’t going Gumball’s way at school so he assumes there must be a Secret Society</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 08:00:00" d="2020-10-30 08:10:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% The Skull Sorcerer
Cole runs first into a nest of Dire-Bats, and then into a cave tunnel filled with giant spiders but Princess Vania and her pet dragon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 08:10:00" d="2020-10-30 08:30:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% The Real Fall
Princess Vania attempts to catch the falling Master Wu and Cole, but their combined weight tears her wings loose. All 3 friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 08:30:00" d="2020-10-30 08:40:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% I Am Okino
The stoic samurai warrior, Okino, is a serious, duty-bound warrior who is unaware that Prime Empire is a game, since he is part of it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 08:40:00" d="2020-10-30 09:00:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% The Glitch
Okino leads the ninja into the first of Terra Karana’s deadly challenges and are ambushed by the deceiving creatures, the Whack Rats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 09:00:00" d="2020-10-30 09:10:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Scared of Puppets
Mao Mao is scared of puppets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 09:10:00" d="2020-10-30 09:20:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The Perfect Couple
When Mao Mao accidentally breaks up the most perfect couple in Pure Heart Valley he has to figure out how to get them back together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 09:20:00" d="2020-10-30 09:35:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bao Bao's Revenge
When Mao Mao's old partner threatens the kingdom his friends will need to learn about his past in order to protect the present</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 09:35:00" d="2020-10-30 09:45:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Truth Stinks
Badgerclops smells but Mao Mao and Adorabat don't know how to tell him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 09:45:00" d="2020-10-30 10:00:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Outfoxed
When Rufus and Reg come to swindle the town Sheriff Mao Mao teaches them a lesson in justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 10:00:00" d="2020-10-30 10:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Ones and Zeros
The Titans build an AI robot so it will create a pizza that's never been made before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 10:10:00" d="2020-10-30 10:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Career Day
Robin forces the other Titans to forget their dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 10:30:00" d="2020-10-30 10:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>TV Knight 2
Batman and Commissioner Gordon have a slumber party and watch their favorite TV shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 10:40:00" d="2020-10-30 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Academy
Robin creates the Teen Titan Awards in an effort to get his teammates to clean up the Tower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 11:00:00" d="2020-10-30 11:10:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears IV (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Mummy's Curse
The Baby Bears must return a mummy to its tomb or else they’ll be cursed forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 11:10:00" d="2020-10-30 11:20:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears IV (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lord of the Poppies
Grizz and the Poppy Rangers go camping on an island, but they soon find themselves deserted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 11:20:00" d="2020-10-30 11:35:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears IV (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sandcastle
The Baby Bears build a giant sandcastle. But when some kids declare war on the Bears, they must fight to defend their new home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 11:35:00" d="2020-10-30 11:45:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears IV (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shmorby
The Bears get a Shmorby home assistant device and become lazy couch potatoes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 11:45:00" d="2020-10-30 12:00:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears IV (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bros in the City
The Bears star in a reality TV show along with Griff, Tom, and Isaac</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 12:00:00" d="2020-10-30 12:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Uncle
When Gumball finds out that their 8-bit friend Ocho has an Italian plumber called Mario for an uncle, he assumes it's 'that' Mario</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 12:10:00" d="2020-10-30 12:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Heist
Richard's got a motorcycle helmet stuck on his head, so when he goes into a bank the terrified staff all assume he's there to rob the place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 12:20:00" d="2020-10-30 12:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Petals
When Leslie's petals begin falling off he feels like his good looks are fading, Gumball and Darwin use everything they know about style</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 12:35:00" d="2020-10-30 12:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Nuisance
The Wattersons fear the worst when they are summoned to a Town Hall meeting, but are pleasantly surprised when they're offered a brand new house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 12:45:00" d="2020-10-30 13:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Best
No matter what Gumball does Carmen thinks she knows better. Gumball attempts to gain the moral high ground but fails spectacularly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 13:00:00" d="2020-10-30 13:10:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Guardian of the Unikingdom
Hawkodile insists the Unikingdom is more dangerous than it looks and sets out to prove it by taking his friends on bodyguard patrol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 13:10:00" d="2020-10-30 13:20:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cast Aside the Truth
Hawkodile breaks his arm in a careless spill and lies to his friends about the accident to keep from looking bad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 13:20:00" d="2020-10-30 13:35:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Wishing Well
When Puppycorn uses a wishing well and it doesn't come true, Unikitty is shocked to discover the reason: all the wishes made over the years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 13:35:00" d="2020-10-30 13:40:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Action Forest
Hawkodile is the toughest action hero in the land, until his old rival shows up to take vengeance on him. Defeated and in need of help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 13:40:00" d="2020-10-30 14:00:00"><n u="Unikitty">Unikitty I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Stuck Together
When Master Frown's head is stuck on Unikitty's butt, she vows to help him get his own body back, but first, she has to attend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 14:00:00" d="2020-10-30 14:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Strength of a Grown Man
Needing a hero with shrinking powers but forgetting about Bumblebee Robin invites The Atom to join their fight against the Brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 14:10:00" d="2020-10-30 14:20:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Had to Be There
So she isn't left out of inside jokes the Titans time travel to past adventures and insert Bumblebee into their memories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 14:20:00" d="2020-10-30 14:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Girls Night In Part 1
The Girls Night Out Crew decide to stay in and have a slumber party but an unknown alien threat descends on Jump City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 14:35:00" d="2020-10-30 14:45:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Girls Night In Part 2
When Blackfire begins her plan to conquer Earth the girls must pull out all the stops to defeat her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 14:45:00" d="2020-10-30 15:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Great Disaster
Robin gets amnesia and starts thinking that Hawkman is his mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 15:00:00" d="2020-10-30 15:10:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Adoradad
When AD's dad forbids her from working with the Sheriff's Dept because it's too dangerous AD sets out to prove that she can take care of herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 15:10:00" d="2020-10-30 15:20:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Badge-a-fire Explosion
When BC comes out of a rare state of hyper-focused creativity he may have made something that could destroy all of PHV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 15:20:00" d="2020-10-30 15:35:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Enemy Mime
When the Sheriff's Dept fights a monster that copies their every move they'll have to find a way to fight without fighting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 15:35:00" d="2020-10-30 15:45:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sugar Berry Fever
Mao Mao tries to hide his love of cobbler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 15:45:00" d="2020-10-30 16:00:00"><n u="Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart">Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Orangusnake Begins
Mao Mao goads Orangusnake and the Sky Pirates into becoming truly terrible villains worthy of a legendary hero such as himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 16:00:00" d="2020-10-30 16:10:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% Dungeon Party!
Cole awakens from a dream to find himself surrounded by the Lowly, Master Wu and Princess Vania. The Lowly reveal they were adventurers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 16:10:00" d="2020-10-30 16:30:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% Dungeon Crawl!
Cole leads the Lowly and Princess Vania and Wu in a series of fruitless efforts to find a way out of Rock-Bottom. Wu tells Cole about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 16:30:00" d="2020-10-30 16:40:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% Ninjago Confidential
Zane and Pixal visits an old childhood contact of Milton Dyer’s who tells them that Dyer used to frequent an old video arcade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 16:40:00" d="2020-10-30 17:00:00"><n u="Ninjago">Ninjago II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>73% The Prodigal Father
The Mechanic’s henchmen capture Master Wu and bring him to the Mechanic’s warehouse. The Mechanic uses him as leverage to coerce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 17:00:00" d="2020-10-30 17:10:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On Your Toes
After a Porcupunk sighting Axel leads a recon mission that slowly but surely proves to be a wild goose chase devised by Sarge who's secretly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 17:10:00" d="2020-10-30 17:20:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Knockout
Axel and the team juggle not waking Uncle Andrew from his nap and stopping Orangutank from stealing Andrew's latest invention: the Knockout Box!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 17:20:00" d="2020-10-30 17:35:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Joyride
At a rummage sale with Uncle Andrew Axel and Zoe must stop Madcap from turning her long-lost tank toy Joyride into an agent of mayhem!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 17:35:00" d="2020-10-30 17:45:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sarge in Charge
Axel and the team must rescue Sarge Charge from a solo mission in the backyard which Orangutank has turned into his own personal heart of darkness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 17:45:00" d="2020-10-30 18:00:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bobbie Not Blobby
Axel discovers that the culprit behind Bobbie Blobby's missing mech-suit is Masko who only wanted to clean out its clogged clay cannons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 18:00:00" d="2020-10-30 18:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Forgeti
When Gwen drags Ben along on a hike in search of the legendary Forgeti, a yeti that makes people forget they ever saw it, Ben is dubious. But with Dr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 18:10:00" d="2020-10-30 18:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Filth
Ben is tasked with cleaning the Rust Bucket but when he is tricked into letting the villainous and vile Fly Guys steal it he must chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 18:30:00" d="2020-10-30 18:40:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Clown College
While tailgating at a State U. homecoming football game, Ben teams up with Grandpa Max’s old college buddies to keep the crazy clown Zombozo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 18:40:00" d="2020-10-30 19:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Ring Leader
While winning big on a Sumo Slammers video game, Ben gets the idea to win a wrestling match for real until an intimidating wrestler named</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 19:00:00" d="2020-10-30 19:10:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% The Race for Gold
When Bakugan begin emerging from the earth's crust in a mysterious worldwide &quot;awakening,&quot; Dan and his friends find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 19:10:00" d="2020-10-30 19:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Seek and Hide
When Bakugan begin emerging from the earth's crust in a mysterious worldwide &quot;awakening,&quot; Dan and his friends find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 19:35:00" d="2020-10-30 20:00:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% A Door Closes A Door Opens
When Bakugan begin emerging from the earth's crust in a mysterious worldwide &quot;awakening,&quot; Dan and his friends find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 20:00:00" d="2020-10-30 20:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Silence
When Gumball and Darwin's conversation dries up they worry that their friendship is coming to an end. They try to find</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 20:10:00" d="2020-10-30 20:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Future
Gumball Darwin and Banana Joe investigate Banana Barbara's mysterious disappearance and uncover an old rival's shadowy scheme in the process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 20:20:00" d="2020-10-30 20:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Wish
Darwin asks Gumball to teach him how to skate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 20:35:00" d="2020-10-30 20:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Factory
Gumball and Darwin follow Nicole to the Rainbow Factory for Bring your Kids to Work Day. They are expecting a magical place full of dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 20:45:00" d="2020-10-30 21:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Revolt
Darwin tries to highlight the plight of all the household objects he feels are being oppressed and maltreated by the uncaring residents of Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 21:00:00" d="2020-10-30 21:10:00"><n u="Steven Universe">Steven Universe IV (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Room for Ruby
Steven’s Gem family continues to grow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 21:10:00" d="2020-10-30 21:20:00"><n u="Steven Universe">Steven Universe IV (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lion 4: Alternate Ending
Lion coughs up a magical key and Steven goes on a quest to find what it unlocks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 21:20:00" d="2020-10-30 21:35:00"><n u="Steven Universe">Steven Universe IV (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doug Out
Steven and Connie join Connie’s father on a stake out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 21:35:00" d="2020-10-30 21:55:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Iron and Stone
Cole and Young Wu attempt to free their friends who have been taken captive by a tribe of Dragon Hunters. Meanwhile in Ninjago Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 21:55:00" d="2020-10-30 22:20:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Radio Free Ninjago
NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu centers on the adventures of five ninjas. The show is set in the fictional world of Ninjago a place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 22:20:00" d="2020-10-30 22:40:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% How to Build a Dragon
While Lloyd and the rebels celebrate their successful strike against Emperor Garmadon in the Realm of Oni and Dragon the Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 22:40:00" d="2020-10-30 23:00:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Gilded Path
The headquarters to the resistance is breached and Lloyd scrambles to avoid capture. Meanwhile the Ninja are caught by Heavy Metal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 23:00:00" d="2020-10-30 23:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Poltergeist
Gumball and Darwin give Mr Robinson a home and end up saving his marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 23:15:00" d="2020-10-30 23:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Quest
Gumball and Darwin help Anais rescue her doll from Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 23:25:00" d="2020-10-30 23:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Spoon
Gumball and Darwin are unwitting accomplices in a gas station robbery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 23:35:00" d="2020-10-30 23:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Microwave
Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-30 23:45:00" d="2020-10-31 00:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Meddler
Gumball is embarrassed when Mom comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 00:00:00" d="2020-10-31 00:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Game
The Wattersons must survive a bizarre game of Dodj or Daar through to the end</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 00:10:00" d="2020-10-31 00:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Promise
Darwin has promised to play video games with Gumball but his promise with Banana Joe interferes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 00:20:00" d="2020-10-31 00:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Voice
Gumball and Darwin must apologise to everyone they know after getting a threatening message on Elmore Plus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 00:35:00" d="2020-10-31 00:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Boombox
Gumball and Darwin try to understand Juke's urgent beatbox message</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 00:45:00" d="2020-10-31 01:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Castle
Richard is left in charge for the day but his lack of rules attracts unwanted guests to the Watterson house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 01:00:00" d="2020-10-31 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Fake Stuntman
Angelo stupidly boasts that his Dad used to be a stuntman. And the next day Dad has been invited to speak to Angelo’s class for career day. Gah!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 01:10:00" d="2020-10-31 01:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The Balance Of Nature
Angelo makes Tracy cry and feels terrible about it. He declares a truce. Problem is… their growing friendship throws off the balance of nature!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 01:20:00" d="2020-10-31 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Cat Burglar
Joe Mama has been stealing stuff from around town and storing it under Angelo’s bed. Angelo and friends embark on a reverse scavenger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 01:35:00" d="2020-10-31 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Here Comes The Science
Angelo and Lola are stuck with Manetti as a science project partner. The only way to complete the project is turn Manetti into the science project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 01:45:00" d="2020-10-31 02:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The Arm
Tracy claims Angelo broke her arm. Angelo’s punishment—become Tracy’s slave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 02:00:00" d="2020-10-31 02:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Poltergeist
Gumball and Darwin give Mr Robinson a home and end up saving his marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 02:10:00" d="2020-10-31 02:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Quest
Gumball and Darwin help Anais rescue her doll from Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 02:20:00" d="2020-10-31 02:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Spoon
Gumball and Darwin are unwitting accomplices in a gas station robbery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 02:35:00" d="2020-10-31 02:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Microwave
Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 02:45:00" d="2020-10-31 03:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Meddler
Gumball is embarrassed when Mom comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 03:00:00" d="2020-10-31 03:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Hero
Richard overhears Gumball and Darwin making fun of him which hurts his feelings and he has to regain his reputation as a hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 03:10:00" d="2020-10-31 03:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Photo
Gumball tries to look good in the school photo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 03:20:00" d="2020-10-31 03:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Tag
Gumball and Darwin get caught in the middle of a trash can war between Richard and Mr. Robinson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 03:35:00" d="2020-10-31 03:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Limit
Nicole gets upset with the family at the supermarket when her kids want chocolate but she says no</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 03:45:00" d="2020-10-31 04:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Game
The Wattersons must survive a bizarre game of Dodj or Daar through to the end</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 04:00:00" d="2020-10-31 04:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Beast Inside
Ben, Gwen and Max make a return to Max's alma-mater but this time it's no homecoming. Dr. Animo has made a scary transformation and found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 04:10:00" d="2020-10-31 04:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tomorrow Today
When Max drags the kids to see a defunct House of the Future built by his childhood idol, Ben discovers Steam Smythe is busy excavating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 04:20:00" d="2020-10-31 04:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bad Penny
Ben is at the annual Big Bacon Pig Parade but childhood friend Penny Heaven has met the family to ruin Ben's fun with her safety-obsessed self</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 04:30:00" d="2020-10-31 04:40:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Max to the Max
While Ben, Gwen and Max hike to a waterfall, the Bug Brothers are back with a plan to duplicate Diamondhead. But when their cloning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 04:40:00" d="2020-10-31 04:55:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zombozo-Land
Ben, Gwen and Max revisit their favourite amusement park – renovated and rebranded as AdrenaWORLD! Unfortunately, the new management</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-10-31 04:55:00" d="2020-10-31 05:00:00"><n u="The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe">The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Prince and the Talking Tree
Ivandoe and Bert come across a Talking Tree who promises to tell their fortune in exchange for gold. An enthusiastic</k>  </p>
</a>
