<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-10-27 04:14:31"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 07:00:00" d="2020-11-03 07:48:00"><n>Naples, City of Keyboards - Ascanio Mayone</n><t>M</t>    <k>'In compositions including passagework, out-of-tune notes which are not in accordance with the laws of counterpoint do indeed occasionally occur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 07:48:00" d="2020-11-03 08:46:00"><n>Josquin - Missa fortuna desperata</n><t>M</t>    <k>Long before upcycling became a trend, there was Josquin Desprez. To this day, his inventiveness in processing existing musical material remains unparalleled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 08:46:00" d="2020-11-03 09:39:00"><n u="Mozart - Piano Concertos No. 14 &amp; No.">Mozart - Piano Concertos No. 14 &amp; No. 23</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this recording of his 2016 Deeply Mozart concert tour, Francesco Attesti (.1975) performs Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart's piano concertos KV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 09:39:00" d="2020-11-03 11:04:00"><n>Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 26, Op. 81a</n><t>M</t>    <k>This performance is taken from Daniel Barenboim's highly esteemed complete rendition of Beethoven's 32 piano sonatas, recorded at the Palais Rasumofsky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 11:04:00" d="2020-11-03 12:16:00"><n u="Brahms - A German Requiem, Op.">Brahms - A German Requiem, Op. 45</n><t>M</t>    <k>Franz Welser-Möst conducts the Wiener Singverein and Cleveland Orchestra orchestra in a performance of Johannes Brahms' Ein Deutsches Requiem, Op 45</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 12:16:00" d="2020-11-03 13:31:00"><n u="Bach - Partitas for Solo Violin">Bach - Partitas for Solo Violin (BWV 1001-1006)</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2006, Gidon Kremer took on the greatest challenge for any violinist: Bach's &quot;Sonatas and Partitas for Solo Violin&quot; (BWV 1001-1006). With these pieces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 13:31:00" d="2020-11-03 13:54:00"><n>Sons of Vienna: Part 2 - A Lion's Roar</n><t>S</t>    <k>The six-part series Sons of Vienna portrays extraordinary composers who were active in the cultural city of Vienna and deserve the label of genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 13:54:00" d="2020-11-03 15:04:00"><n>Christmas Concert</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Valerius Ensemble, consisting of Robert Windak (violin), Annemarie van Vliegen (violin), Eva Šušliková (viola) and Réne Geesing (cello) plays</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 15:04:00" d="2020-11-03 17:32:00"><n>Verdi - Luisa Miller</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the musical direction of Massimo Zanetti, the Orchestre et Choeurs de l'Opéra Royal de Wallonie present the opera &quot;Luisa Miller&quot;. As the result</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 17:32:00" d="2020-11-03 18:42:00"><n u="Sibelius - Symphony No.">Sibelius - Symphony No. 4</n><t>M</t>    <k>Finnish Radio Symphony Orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 18:42:00" d="2020-11-03 20:04:00"><n u="Brahms - The 3 Violin Sonatas, Op. 78, 100 &amp;">Brahms - The 3 Violin Sonatas, Op. 78, 100 &amp; 108</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 20:04:00" d="2020-11-03 20:29:00"><n>Shostakovich - Chamber Symphony Op. 110a</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Casco Phil, The Chamber Music Orchestra of Belgium, conducted by Benjamin Haemhouts, performs Shostakovich's Chamber Symphony, Op</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 20:29:00" d="2020-11-03 20:58:00"><n>Chamber Music by Mozart and Von Dohnányi</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Valerius Ensemble, consisting of Carola Ligt (flute), Robert Windak (violin), Eva Šušlíková (viola) and René Geesing (cello) play a varied concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 20:58:00" d="2020-11-03 22:00:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 13, Op. 27, No.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 13, Op. 27, No. 1</n><t>M</t>    <k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986. One of his best known successes thus far, is the acclaimed concert cycle of Beethoven's 32 Sonatas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 22:00:00" d="2020-11-03 23:10:00"><n>Gaming in Symphony</n><t>L</t>    <k>From the streets of Florence to the fabled shrines of Shangri-La, the mythical world of Azeroth to the mysterious planet Halo, allow yourself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 23:10:00" d="2020-11-04 00:03:00"><n>Israel Philharmonic Orchestra: Coming Home</n><t>M</t>    <k>On the occasion of its 75th anniversary on the 24th of December, 2011, the Israel Philharmonic Orchestra celebrates with a beautiful documentary about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 00:03:00" d="2020-11-04 01:00:00"><n>Classical:NEXT 2019 - Trio Zukan</n><t>M</t>    <k>For this concert from the 2019 edition of Classical:NEXT!, Maria Zubimendi (accordion), Gorka Catediano (percussion) and Jon Ansorena (txistu) perform the works &quot;X</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 01:00:00" d="2020-11-04 03:52:00"><n>Rossini - La Cenerentola</n><t>M</t>    <k>This 2015 performance of La Cenerentola at the Opéra de Rennes is conducted by Darrell Ang and features the Symphonic Orchestra of Brittany and choir</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 03:52:00" d="2020-11-04 05:22:00"><n>Europakonzert 2010 - Oxford</n><t>M</t>    <k>For over 20 years, the Berliner Philharmoniker have celebrated their foundation on May 1st with the annual Europa Konzert - the 2010 concert takes place in Oxford</k>  </p>
</a>
