<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-10-28 03:53:34"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 05:22:00" d="2020-11-04 05:38:00"><n>Summertime at the Domaine Forget</n><t>M</t>    <k>The documentary Summertime at the Domaine Forget introduces internationally renowned treasure: Domaine Forget festival in Saint-Irénée, Québec</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 05:38:00" d="2020-11-04 07:00:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dina Ivanova (1994, Russia) performs La notte (S377a) and Hungarian Rhapsody No. 12, (S379a) during semi-final II (chamber music) of the 11th International</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 07:00:00" d="2020-11-04 08:38:00"><n>Buxtehude - Abendmusik</n><t>M</t>    <k>Enjoy the Masques ensemble and the Vox Luminis choir and discover 17th century baroque music and the composer Buxtehude through his vocal compositions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 08:38:00" d="2020-11-04 09:25:00"><n>The Violin in Naples - Fiorenza, Marchitelli, Leo</n><t>M</t>    <k>A hundred years of Neapolitan music for violin consort and basso continuo: this is the tasty menu Enrico Gatti and his Ensemble Aurora have prepared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 09:25:00" d="2020-11-04 11:01:00"><n>Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jenny Chen (1994, Taiwan) performs Tchaikovsky/Liszt - Polonaise aus der Oper Jewgeny Onegin, S429, Rubinstein/Liszt - Zwei Lieder, S554 und Rapsodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 11:01:00" d="2020-11-04 11:55:00"><n u="Rachmaninoff - Piano Concerto No. 3, Op">Rachmaninoff - Piano Concerto No. 3, Op 30</n><t>M</t>    <k>The legendary pianist Vladimir Horowitz (1903-1989) won his first glowing comment on his interpretation of Rachmaninoff's Third Piano Concerto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 11:55:00" d="2020-11-04 13:04:00"><n>The Red Priest and the Tanguero</n><t>M</t>    <k>The set YES Camerata (Young European String Camerata) and the violinist William Hagen interpret The four seasons of Antonio Vivaldi and Las quatros</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 13:04:00" d="2020-11-04 13:57:00"><n>Mozart on Tour - Episode 1: London</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journey of Mozart across Europe. In this episode, Vladimir Ashkenazy performs as a soloist and conductor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 13:57:00" d="2020-11-04 15:03:00"><n>Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alexander Ullman (1991, United Kingdom) performs Wagner/Liszt - Isoldens Liebestod: Schlußszene aus Tristan und Isolde, S447 and Beethoven/Liszt - Symphony No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 15:03:00" d="2020-11-04 16:37:00"><n>Europakonzert 2016 from R?ros</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sir Simon Rattle conducts the Berlin Philharmonic in the 2016 edition of the Europakonzert, in R?ros, Norway. On the program are Grieg's Lyrical Piece, Op</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 16:37:00" d="2020-11-04 17:23:00"><n u="Beethoven - Symphony No. 6 'Pastorale', Op.">Beethoven - Symphony No. 6 'Pastorale', Op. 68</n><t>M</t>    <k>Conrad van Alphen conducts the Sinfonia Rotterdam Orchestra in an interpretation of Beethoven's Symphony No. 6, Pastoral, at the St. Willibrord Basilica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 17:23:00" d="2020-11-04 17:49:00"><n>Rachmaninoff &amp; Dvořák Trios</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Valerius Ensemble, consisting of Eeva Koskinen (violin), René Geesing (cello) and Ingo Lulofs (piano) plays Rachmaninoff's Trio élégiaque Nr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 17:49:00" d="2020-11-04 18:49:00"><n>Couperin's Premier Livre, Masterly Mix</n><t>M</t>    <k>We have François Couperin to thank for some of the most stunning pages found in 18th-century harpsichord literature. Today, Aurélien Delage tackles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 18:49:00" d="2020-11-04 19:15:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Julien van Mellaerts</n><t>M</t>    <k>Joao Araújo accompanies baritone Julien van Mellaerts (New-Zealand/UK, 1988 during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 19:15:00" d="2020-11-04 20:59:00"><n>Concert Live from Geneva</n><t>M</t>    <k>Conducted by Daniel Barenboim, the West-Eastern Divan Orchestra performs Beethoven's Piano Concerto No. 3, Tchaikovsky's Symphony No. 5, Sibelius'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 20:59:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00"><n>Discovering Masterpieces - Brandenburg Concertos</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of Discovering Masterpieces presents the Brandenburg Concertos by Johann Sebastian Bach (1685-1750). Musical excerpts played by the Freiburger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 23:05:00"><n>Mosaique Project - Canadian Piano Quartets</n><t>M</t>    <k>This very special concert event celebrates the diversity and richness of Canada through the eyes and ears of its people. Ensemble Made in Canada's Mosaique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-04 23:05:00" d="2020-11-05 00:36:00"><n>Prosseda performs Mozart, Schubert &amp; Chopin</n><t>S</t>    <k>Roberto Prosseda (1975) performs Mozart's Piano Sonata No. 5 (KV. 283) and four Impromptus Op. 90 by Franz Schubert. The performance ends with Chopin's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 00:36:00" d="2020-11-05 01:00:00"><n>Solo Finals - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alexander Ullman (1991, United Kingdom) performs Liszt's Études d'exécution transcendante, No. 11 Harmonies du soir (S139/11), Nuages gris (S199)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 01:00:00" d="2020-11-05 03:48:00"><n>Haydn - Orlando Paladino</n><t>M</t>    <k>For more than 25 years, René Jacobs has dedicated his life to baroque operas and works with the best ensembles for early music. On occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 03:48:00" d="2020-11-05 05:07:00"><n>Barati &amp; Debargue perform Debussy, Brahms &amp; Franck</n><t>M</t>    <k>Violinist Kristof Barati and Pianist Lucas Debargue pair for the first time in a duo concert at the 25th anniversary edition of the Swiss Verbier Festival in 2018</k>  </p>
</a>
