<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-10-30 03:46:43"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 05:26:00" d="2020-11-06 07:00:00"><n>Haydn - String Quartet in G Major Op. 54 No.1</n><t>M</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 07:00:00" d="2020-11-06 08:31:00"><n>House of Dreams</n><t>M</t>    <k>House of Dreams is an imaginative concert designed by Alison Mackay. It is a magical journey to the meeting places of baroque art and music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 08:31:00" d="2020-11-06 09:22:00"><n>Naples, city of keyboards - Pier Domenico Paradisi</n><t>M</t>    <k>During the 18th century Neapolitan Pier Domenico Paradisi, also known as Paradies, tried, with varying success, to develop his operatic career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 09:22:00" d="2020-11-06 10:01:00"><n>Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Yonghwan Jeong (1991, South Korea) performs Harmonies poétiques et réligieuses, No. 7 Funérailles, S173/7 and Grandes Études de Paganini, S141 during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 10:01:00" d="2020-11-06 11:02:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 9, Op. 14, No.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 9, Op. 14, No. 1</n><t>M</t>    <k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986. One of his best known successes thus far, is the acclaimed concert cycle of Beethoven's 32 Sonatas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 11:02:00" d="2020-11-06 12:35:00"><n u="Mahler - Symphony No.">Mahler - Symphony No. 8</n><t>M</t>    <k>Fabio Luisi conducts the Danish National Symphony Orchestra in a performance of Mahler's Symphony No. 8. The work is one of the largest-scale choral works</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 12:35:00" d="2020-11-06 13:39:00"><n>Roberto Giordano plays Brahms and Beethoven</n><t>M</t>    <k>Roberto Giordano plays the Six Pieces for Piano, op. 118 of Brahms, as well as the famous Moonlight Sonata and Sonata No. 31, op. 110 of Beethoven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 13:39:00" d="2020-11-06 14:10:00"><n>Teatro Regio behind the scenes</n><t>M</t>    <k>This documentary portrays the Teatro Regio of Turin. Pillar of local life and symbol of excellence of the Italian operatic tradition, the Teatro Regio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 14:10:00" d="2020-11-06 15:02:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 54 No.">Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 54 No. 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 15:02:00" d="2020-11-06 16:14:00"><n>The Morricone Duel</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Wild West meets the soulful sound of Italy. Fearless New York gangsters meet cowboys from the dusty prairie. And the magic of cinema meets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 16:14:00" d="2020-11-06 17:30:00"><n u="Bruckner - Symphony No.">Bruckner - Symphony No. 5</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bruckner's Fifth Symphony has been called the &quot;Medieval&quot; because of its multi-layered, Baroque, contrapuntal tonal textures and the &quot;Catholic&quot; because</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 17:30:00" d="2020-11-06 19:14:00"><n>Arvo Pärt - Kanon Pokajanen</n><t>M</t>    <k>Arvo Pärt based his 'Kanon Pokajanen' (from 'Canon of Repentance to Our Lord Jesus Christ', 1995-97) on the canon of repentance as handed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 19:14:00" d="2020-11-06 20:07:00"><n>The Good, the Bold and the Fearless</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Burgundian rulers attached great importance to a high-quality court chapel, but music could also be heard daily in their private apartments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 20:07:00" d="2020-11-06 22:00:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 18, Op. 31, No.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 18, Op. 31, No. 3</n><t>M</t>    <k>This performance is taken from Daniel Barenboim's highly esteemed complete rendition of Beethoven's 32 piano sonatas, recorded at the Palais Rasumofsky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 22:00:00" d="2020-11-07 00:24:00"><n>Boito - Mefistofele</n><t>M</t>    <k>Stefan Soltesz conducts the Münchner Philharmoniker in a performance of Arrigo Boito's Mefistofele, with Erwin Schrott singing the title role. Mefistofele</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-07 00:24:00" d="2020-11-07 01:00:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 13, Op. 27, No.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 13, Op. 27, No. 1</n><t>M</t>    <k>This performance is taken from Daniel Barenboim's highly esteemed complete rendition of Beethoven's 32 piano sonatas, recorded at the Palais Rasumofsky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-07 01:00:00" d="2020-11-07 03:55:00"><n>Mozart - Cosi fan tutte</n><t>M</t>    <k>Stefano Montanari conducts Mozart's opera Cosi fan tutte in a staging by Adrian Noble. The major roles are played by Lionel Lhote, Daniel Behle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-07 03:55:00" d="2020-11-07 05:41:00"><n>Pianomania - Menahem Pressler</n><t>M</t>    <k>Menahem Pressler is the soloist in Mozart's Piano Concerto, No. 23. The Gulbenkian Orchestra is conducted by Leo Hussain in a concert program which</k>  </p>
</a>
