<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-10-29 03:53:11"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 05:07:00" d="2020-11-05 06:00:00"><n>Going for the Impossible: Mirga Gražinyte-Tyla</n><t>M</t>    <k>Lithuanian conductor Mirga Gražinyte-Tyla is the current musical director of the City of Birmingham Symphony Orchestra (CBSO), succeeding both Andris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 06:00:00" d="2020-11-05 07:00:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 33 No.">Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 33 No. 3</n><t>M</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 07:00:00" d="2020-11-05 07:57:00"><n>Dufay - Missa Ave regina caelorum</n><t>M</t>    <k>Why make use of a brilliant idea only once. Guillaume Dufay upcycled his Marian antiphon Ave Regina Coeloruminto, a four-part mass, probably intended</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 07:57:00" d="2020-11-05 08:48:00"><n>Tinctoris' Secret Consolation</n><t>M</t>    <k>Johannes Tinctoris ranks as one of the most prominent music theorists of the 15th century. He wrote his most famous books in Naples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 08:48:00" d="2020-11-05 09:34:00"><n u="Tchaikovsky - Piano Trio, Op.">Tchaikovsky - Piano Trio, Op. 50</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Zadig Trio consists of the two French childhood friends Boris Borgolotto (violin), Marc Girard Garcia (cello) and the American pianist Ian Barber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 09:34:00" d="2020-11-05 11:01:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 31, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 31, Op. 110</n><t>M</t>    <k>This performance is taken from Daniel Barenboim's highly esteemed complete rendition of Beethoven's 32 piano sonatas, recorded at the Palais Rasumofsky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 11:01:00" d="2020-11-05 12:01:00"><n>Testing Mozart</n><t>M</t>    <k>Testing Mozart is a 60 minute film about the &quot;Mozart Effect&quot;, the power of Mozart's music to fight disease and increase the mental ability</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 12:01:00" d="2020-11-05 12:53:00"><n u="Schubert - Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100, D.">Schubert - Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100, D. 929</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ester Hoppe (violin), Christian Poltéra (cello) and Francesco Piemontesi (piano) perform Schubert's Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100 (D. 929) during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 12:53:00" d="2020-11-05 13:43:00"><n>Rachmaninov &amp; Gershwin: Rhapsodies</n><t>M</t>    <k>The National Philharmonic Orchestra of Russia and acclaimed Russian pianist Boris Berezovsky are conducted by Konstantin Khvatynets in an interpretation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 13:43:00" d="2020-11-05 15:02:00"><n u="Brahms - Symphony No. 2, Op.">Brahms - Symphony No. 2, Op. 73</n><t>M</t>    <k>Franz Welser-Möst conducts The Cleveland Orchestra in this performance of Brahms' Symphony No. 2. Considerably brighter than his First, Brahms' Second</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 15:02:00" d="2020-11-05 17:48:00"><n>Debussy - Pelléas et Melisande</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alain Altinoglu conducts a performance of Debussy's Pelléas et Mélisande at the Opernhaus Zürich in 2016. Main soloists are Brindley Sherratt (Arkel)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 17:48:00" d="2020-11-05 18:53:00"><n u="Beethoven - Last Sonatas, Op. 109, 110 &amp;">Beethoven - Last Sonatas, Op. 109, 110 &amp; 111</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianist Alexandre Tharaud's interpretation of Beethoven's last three sonatas - Opus 109, 110 and 111</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 18:53:00" d="2020-11-05 20:15:00"><n>A Russian in Paris</n><t>M</t>    <k>The renowned Russian conductor Yuri Temirkanov conducts the Orchestre de Paris in a program that includes works by Prokofiev, Tchaikovsky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 20:15:00" d="2020-11-05 20:34:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Leon Bernsdorf (1992, Germany) performs Epithalam zu Eduard Reményis Vermählungsfeier (S129) and Grand Duo concertant sur la Romance de 'Le Marin' (S128)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 20:34:00" d="2020-11-05 21:00:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in D Major Op.76 No.">Haydn - String Quartet in D Major Op.76 No. 5</n><t>M</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 21:00:00" d="2020-11-05 22:00:00"><n u="Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 3, op.">Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 3, op. 108</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-05 22:00:00" d="2020-11-06 00:04:00"><n>Tricentenary of the French Dance School</n><t>L</t>    <k>Created under the reign of Louis XIV (the Sun King and the dancing King) the École de danse de l'Opéra national de Paris celebrated its 300th birthday in 2013</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 00:04:00" d="2020-11-06 01:00:00"><n u="Sibelius – Symphony No.">Sibelius – Symphony No. 3</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hannu Lintu, Finnish Radio Symphony Orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 01:00:00" d="2020-11-06 03:33:00"><n>Verdi - Aida</n><t>M</t>    <k>Conductor Paolo Arrivabeni leads the Orchestre et Choeurs de l'Opéra Royal de Wallonie in this performance of Aida. Although Aida is considered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 03:33:00" d="2020-11-06 04:58:00"><n u="Mahler - Symphony No.">Mahler - Symphony No. 9</n><t>M</t>    <k>Gustav Mahler Youth Orchestra, Claudio Abbado</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-06 04:58:00" d="2020-11-06 05:26:00"><n u="Discovering Masterpieces – Beethoven No.">Discovering Masterpieces – Beethoven No. 5</n><t>S</t>    <k>In this documentary, Ludwig van Beethoven's 'Symphony No. 5' is discussed. The piece has the character of an appeal from the very start, when the four-note</k>  </p>
</a>
