<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="16" t="2020-10-25 03:47:20"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 06:00:00" d="2020-11-01 06:55:00"><n>Naples, City of Keyboards - Alessandro Scarlatti</n><t>M</t>    <k>At the age of 24, following his successes in Rome, Alessandro Scarlatti was appointed royal Kapellmeister in Naples, in 1684</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 06:55:00" d="2020-11-01 07:58:00"><n>The Argonauts - Quest for the Golden Fleece</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1419 Philip the Good inherits a realm stretching from Dijon to deep into the Netherlands. In 1430, he founds his Order of the Golden Fleece, which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 07:58:00" d="2020-11-01 08:35:00"><n>Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Wouter Bergenhuizen (1988, The Netherlands) performs Grandes Études de Paganini, S141 and Années de Pelerinage: Deuxieme Année (Italie), No. 1 Sposalizio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 08:35:00" d="2020-11-01 10:06:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 30, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 30, Op. 109</n><t>M</t>    <k>This performance is taken from Daniel Barenboim's highly esteemed complete rendition of Beethoven's 32 piano sonatas, recorded at the Palais Rasumofsky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 10:06:00" d="2020-11-01 11:03:00"><n>Gennaro Manna - Arias in World Premiere</n><t>M</t>    <k>As the son of one of Naples' most prominent musical families Gennaro Manna was blessed with a pen both versatile and skilled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 11:03:00" d="2020-11-01 12:35:00"><n>Legato - World of the Piano</n><t>S</t>    <k>Montréal native Marc-André Hamelin is internationally renowned for his musical virtuosity and refined pianism. He plays works by Haydn (Piano sonata</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 12:35:00" d="2020-11-01 13:03:00"><n u="Brahms - Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 1, Op.">Brahms - Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 1, Op. 78</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 13:03:00" d="2020-11-01 14:09:00"><n>Inside the Hearing Machine</n><t>M</t>    <k>Can we get into Beethoven's creative mind, especially in the last phase of his life when he was coping with severe hearing loss? Tom Beghin's new recording</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 14:09:00" d="2020-11-01 17:09:00"><n>Luigi Rossi - L'Orfeo</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Ensemble Pygmalion performs Luigi Rossi's (c. 1597-1653) l'Orfeo (1647), is an opera in three acts in a staging by Jetske Mijnssen. The Ensemble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 17:09:00" d="2020-11-01 18:59:00"><n>Pianomania - Daniil Trifonov</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hannu Lintu conducts the Gulbenkian Orchestra in a Finnish flavoured concert program, featuring Rautavaara's Cantus Articus and Sibelius' Symphony No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 18:59:00" d="2020-11-01 19:43:00"><n>Johan de Meij - Symphony No. 1 &quot;Lord of the Rings&quot;</n><t>M</t>    <k>Johan de Meij conducts Symphony No. 1 for woodwind and brass orchestra. The work is titled &quot;Lord of the Rings&quot; and is based on the trilogy by</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 19:43:00" d="2020-11-01 22:00:00"><n>Stravinsky - Symphony in Three Movements</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sir Simon Rattle conducts the Berliner Philharmonic and Vadim Repin during the Europakonzert of 2008 from the Tchaikovsky Conservatory. On the program</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-01 22:00:00" d="2020-11-02 00:38:00"><n>Tchaikovsky - Eugene Onegin</n><t>M</t>    <k>Based on one of the most iconic works of Russian literature, Tchaikovsky's adaptation of Alexander Pushkin's 'Eugene Onegin' is coloured by a broad range of emotions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 00:38:00" d="2020-11-02 01:00:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 28, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 28, Op. 101</n><t>M</t>    <k>This performance is taken from Daniel Barenboim's highly esteemed complete rendition of Beethoven's 32 piano sonatas, recorded at the Palais Rasumofsky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 01:00:00" d="2020-11-02 03:55:00"><n>Mozart - Cosi fan tutte</n><t>M</t>    <k>Stefano Montanari conducts Mozart's opera Cosi fan tutte in a staging by Adrian Noble. The major roles are played by Lionel Lhote, Daniel Behle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 03:55:00" d="2020-11-02 05:24:00"><n>Europakonzert 2012 - Vienna</n><t>M</t>    <k>Every year, the Berliner Philharmoniker commemorate their founding in 1883 with the Europa Konzert at a venue of cultural importance in a different European city</k>  </p>
</a>
