<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-10-26 03:46:29"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 05:24:00" d="2020-11-02 06:17:00"><n>Gruppo Appassionati Verdiani - We love Verdi!</n><t>M</t>    <k>In the &quot;country of melodrama&quot;- Italy - exists a very exclusive club consisting of only 27 persons, each of whom is named after one of Verdi's operas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 06:17:00" d="2020-11-02 07:00:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in D minor Op.">Haydn - String Quartet in D minor Op. 42</n><t>S</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 07:00:00" d="2020-11-02 08:18:00"><n>La Moresca - Addio, Daedalus</n><t>M</t>    <k>After more than thirty years at the top Ensemble Daedalus is saying goodbye to the concert stage. That demands a fitting farewell. Roberto Festa sought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 08:18:00" d="2020-11-02 09:13:00"><n>Celebrate Saint-Patrick 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>This program brings the viewers to places most associated with Saint-Patrick and brings highlights of the annual concert, held in the cathedral that bears his name</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 09:13:00" d="2020-11-02 09:44:00"><n>CMIM - Finals - Clara Osowski</n><t>M</t>    <k>Olivier Godin accompanies mezzo-soprano Clara Osowski (USA, 1986) during the finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 09:44:00" d="2020-11-02 11:02:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 27, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 27, Op. 90</n><t>M</t>    <k>Beethoven's 32 piano sonatas, recorded at the Palais Rasumofsky, Vienna, Austria, in 1983</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 11:02:00" d="2020-11-02 11:55:00"><n>The Violin's Voice</n><t>M</t>    <k>The tale of world-renowned violinist Frank Peter Zimmerman's separation and reunion with his beloved 1711 Stradivarius is intertwined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 11:55:00" d="2020-11-02 13:00:00"><n>Beauty is a Crime: Mendelssohn &amp; Brahms</n><t>L</t>    <k>Conductor Teodor Currentzis leads his ensemble MusicAeterna alongside violinist Patricia Kopatchinskaja in a performance of works by Brahms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 13:00:00" d="2020-11-02 13:41:00"><n u="Brahms - Symphony No. 4, Op.">Brahms - Symphony No. 4, Op. 98</n><t>M</t>    <k>Franz Welser-Möst conducts The Cleveland Orchestra in this performance of Brahms' Symphony No. 4. This is the final of the composer's short selection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 13:41:00" d="2020-11-02 15:02:00"><n u="Chopin - Preludes, Op.">Chopin - Preludes, Op. 28</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alessandra Amara performs Chopin's complete Preludes, Op. 28. Chopin wrote the 24 preludes between 1835 and 1839, partly at Valldemossa, Mallorca, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 15:02:00" d="2020-11-02 16:40:00"><n>Tales of Two Cities: Leipzig-Damascus Coffee House</n><t>M</t>    <k>In Tales of Two Cities, the Tafelmusik Baroque Orchestra celebrates the music and culture in eighteenth century coffee houses of Leipzig and Damascus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 16:40:00" d="2020-11-02 17:06:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 17, Op. 31, No.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 17, Op. 31, No. 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>This performance is taken from Daniel Barenboim's highly esteemed complete rendition of Beethoven's 32 piano sonatas, recorded at the Palais Rasumofsky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 17:06:00" d="2020-11-02 17:33:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Rihab Chaieb</n><t>M</t>    <k>Michel-Alexandre Broekaert accompanies mezzo-soprano Rihab Chaieb (Canada/Tunisia, 1987 during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 17:33:00" d="2020-11-02 18:33:00"><n>Ladies first, From Marian motet to love song</n><t>M</t>    <k>Despite his motto 'Aultre n'auray' ('I shall never have another'), Philip the Good was known for his passion for the fairer sex. Could this explain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 18:33:00" d="2020-11-02 18:58:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Wouter Bergenhuizen (1988, The Netherlands) performs Die drei Zigeuner (S383), Die Zelle in Nonnenwerth (S382bis) and La lugubre gondola (S134bis) during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 18:58:00" d="2020-11-02 20:35:00"><n>A Tango Night - Live from Buenos Aires</n><t>L</t>    <k>On December 31, 2006, Daniel Barenboim came to celebrate the New Year in the Argentinean capital of Buenos Aires. For the pianist and conductor the tango</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 20:35:00" d="2020-11-02 22:00:00"><n>Mozart on Tour - Episode 4: Mannheim</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journeys of Mozart across Europe. Soloist Christian Zacharias performs Mozart's Piano Concerto No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-02 22:00:00" d="2020-11-03 00:12:00"><n>Janáček - Jenůfa</n><t>M</t>    <k>In a 2013 production from the stage of the Théâtre Royal de la Monnaie in Brussels, the La Monnaie Symphony Orchestra &amp; Chorus present Leoš Janáček's Jenůfa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 00:12:00" d="2020-11-03 01:00:00"><n>Prokofiev - Peter and the Wolf</n><t>M</t>    <k>Marin Alsop narrates and conducts the world-famous symphonic fairy tale 'Peter and the Wolf' (1936), composed by Sergei Prokofiev (1891-1953). The musical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 01:00:00" d="2020-11-03 03:32:00"><n>Dvořák - Rusalka</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ádám Fischer conducts the orchestra and choir of La Monnaie in a performance of Dvořák's opera Rusalka. The work remains one of the cornerstones of Czech opera houses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 03:32:00" d="2020-11-03 04:52:00"><n>Glass - Double Concerto for Two Pianos</n><t>M</t>    <k>As part of a new collaboration with the famous composer Philip Glass, French pianists Katia and Marielle Labeque perform the European premiere of Glass's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-11-03 04:52:00" d="2020-11-03 07:00:00"><n>Mozart on Tour - Episode 10: Prague</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journey of Mozart across Europe. Soloist Zoltán Kocsis performs Mozart's Piano Concerto No</k>  </p>
</a>
