<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="76" t="2020-10-23 04:35:06"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 05:00:00" d="2020-10-30 05:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Gekko's powers are increased by Power Pondweeds. Owlette breaks the telescope and tries to blame Luna Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 05:25:00" d="2020-10-30 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks Music Video">PJ Masks Music Video I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s time for teamwork! Music accompanies clips from the popular show featuring pyjama-clad heroes Catboy, Gekko and Owlette, who have adventures, solve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 05:30:00" d="2020-10-30 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The Wolfies run amok. Gekko doubts if he can be good. The Wolfies get into the HQ and transform it into their den!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 05:55:00" d="2020-10-30 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At a Mexican fiesta, Minnie and Daisy enter the Hat Dance competition, but it’s Clarabelle who feels the groove and gets into the Moo-sic after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 06:00:00" d="2020-10-30 06:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% The Lion Guard and Kiara must appease a haughty zebra leader to gain access to a new watering hole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 06:30:00" d="2020-10-30 07:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse III (81)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Martian Mickey visits and brings his pet shapes - cone, cylinder, pyramid, cube and sphere. He loses them so everyone helps find them, hiding among similar Earth shapes. (S3 E16)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 07:00:00" d="2020-10-30 07:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s adventure on the high seas as Bluey and Bingo play Pirates on the hammock swing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 07:10:00" d="2020-10-30 07:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Chloe embark on a quest to save their playground kingdom from the Greedy Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 07:20:00" d="2020-10-30 07:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bingo's favourite toy goes missing, the girls must retrace their steps to find it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 07:30:00" d="2020-10-30 07:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Five minutes feels like an eternity as Dad and the kids wait for their takeaway order. (S1Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 07:40:00" d="2020-10-30 07:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mum takes a walk along the beach, Bluey follows behind on her first solo adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 07:50:00" d="2020-10-30 08:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing Shops is the best game ever for Bluey and her friends - if they can ever get started! With Bluey questioning the rules and changing who’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 08:00:00" d="2020-10-30 08:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Armadylan tries to prove he's a great leader by training the Wolfies into heroes. Can they be trained? After stealing Owlette's gadgets, the Wolfies go on a rampage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 08:30:00" d="2020-10-30 09:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena of Avalor has saved her enchanted kingdom from an evil sorceress, and now must learn to rule Avalor with the help of her family and friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 09:00:00" d="2020-10-30 09:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip the Penguin and Freddy the Flamingo are Junior Fliers at T.O.T.S., (the Tiny Ones Transport Service), where they’re tasked with delivering baby animals to their parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 09:30:00" d="2020-10-30 10:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip the Penguin and Freddy the Flamingo are Junior Fliers at T.O.T.S., (the Tiny Ones Transport Service), where they’re tasked with delivering baby animals to their parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 10:00:00" d="2020-10-30 10:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse III (67)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Daisy Duck brings a new friend to the Clubhouse, Wilbur the Grasshopper. He's very playful, and when he hops away, it’s up to us to help the Clubhouse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 10:30:00" d="2020-10-30 11:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pugs go shopping for each other's birthday presents. The pups learn to dance so they can teach Bob for a contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 11:00:00" d="2020-10-30 11:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Trying to help Bob meet an alien, the Pugs meet UFO fans. The pugs try to reunite a lost toy dog with its owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 11:30:00" d="2020-10-30 12:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% When the school instruments go missing, Owlette and Gekko are hot on the trail. Catboy and Gekko dream up an exciting new superhero move, but Owlette can’t get it right!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 12:00:00" d="2020-10-30 12:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Armadylan and CB compete over an exclusive Master Fang comic thinking it contains a hero secret. Armadylan loses the PJs’ special jet to Night Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 12:30:00" d="2020-10-30 13:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% When Romeo steals Owlette’s powers, he turns himself, Catboy, and Gekko into fliers. Night Ninja plans to turn Catboy's daytime parade into the Night Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 13:00:00" d="2020-10-30 13:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After the family goldfish dies, Nancy must confront her feelings of loss. When Nancy spies on her parents, she thinks she hears them plotting to give away the family dog!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 13:30:00" d="2020-10-30 14:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy is determined to save money to go to Paris, but is devastated when she discovers how long it will take. Nancy realizes she is more like her Mum than she realized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 14:00:00" d="2020-10-30 14:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While camping in the bush, Bluey makes a new friend who doesn't speak the same language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 14:10:00" d="2020-10-30 14:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo and Bluey can’t agree on one simple question: Can Grannies do the floss dance?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 14:20:00" d="2020-10-30 14:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A quick trip to the shops proves tricky for Dad, when Bluey decides she’s going to be Mum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 14:30:00" d="2020-10-30 14:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey sends a video to Bingo in hospital to show her that everyone gets sick sometimes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 14:40:00" d="2020-10-30 14:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s magic asparagus turns her family into wild animals with no manners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 14:50:00" d="2020-10-30 15:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey has to appease invisible mischief-making fairies, who have infested the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 15:00:00" d="2020-10-30 15:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First IV (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia and Crackle attend the annual Dragon Roast 'n’ Toast – a big, picnic-like gathering of dragons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 15:25:00" d="2020-10-30 15:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales">Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mickey and Pluto are having trouble coming up with Halloween costumes, Pluto inspires Mickey to create the most spook-tacular costumes in Hot Dog Hills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 15:30:00" d="2020-10-30 16:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When visiting dignitaries fall under a spell of magical masks, Elena must learn to work with the equally headstrong Dona Paloma in order to break the spell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 16:00:00" d="2020-10-30 16:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey misses Mum when she goes out for the night and leaves Dad in charge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 16:10:00" d="2020-10-30 16:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s lunchtime on Bluey's back deck! But every BBQ needs a side salad, so Bingo’s relaxing sit-down will have to wait until she finds every colour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 16:20:00" d="2020-10-30 16:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum get into a heated debate with Dad about whether he is a Big Teaser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 16:30:00" d="2020-10-30 17:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJM have to protect all the kids from Luna Girl, Night Ninja and the Wolfy Kids who have got together to steal their goody bags</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 17:00:00" d="2020-10-30 17:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy is jealous when Bree gets the part she was hoping to play. (S2 Ep2a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 17:15:00" d="2020-10-30 17:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy realizes she is more like her Mum than she thought. (S2 Ep1b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 17:30:00" d="2020-10-30 18:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When Remy says goodbye to the Hauntleys to chase his dream as a chef at a fancy restaurant, a spookghetti monster pops up! Oxana adds a spooky flair to the school fair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 18:00:00" d="2020-10-30 18:15:00"><n u="PJ Masks S4 Splits">PJ Masks S4 Splits IV (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Newton likes the PJ Masks but also likes his solitude</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 18:15:00" d="2020-10-30 18:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks S4 Splits">PJ Masks S4 Splits IV (91)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Owlette causes a freak asteroid accident. Gekko and Catboy try to help her put it right. But there is more to the accident than there seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 18:30:00" d="2020-10-30 19:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Kion warns Jasiri about Scar’s return and offers her protection in the Pride Lands. Jasiri declines and instead offers to help fight Scar and his minions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 19:00:00" d="2020-10-30 19:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% When Princess Zooey, a new student at Royal Prep, starts a Princess Adventure Club to make friends and invites all the princesses to join except Amber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 19:25:00" d="2020-10-30 19:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales">Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mickey and Pluto are having trouble coming up with Halloween costumes, Pluto inspires Mickey to create the most spook-tacular costumes in Hot Dog Hills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 19:30:00" d="2020-10-30 20:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Amber is jealous of the time Roland is spending with Sofia, so when she finds a wishing well, she wishes that Roland would become allergic to Sofia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 20:00:00" d="2020-10-30 20:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey misses Mum when she goes out for the night and leaves Dad in charge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 20:10:00" d="2020-10-30 20:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s lunchtime on Bluey's back deck! But every BBQ needs a side salad, so Bingo’s relaxing sit-down will have to wait until she finds every colour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 20:20:00" d="2020-10-30 20:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum get into a heated debate with Dad about whether he is a Big Teaser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 20:30:00" d="2020-10-30 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJM have to protect all the kids from Luna Girl, Night Ninja and the Wolfy Kids who have got together to steal their goody bags</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 21:00:00" d="2020-10-30 21:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy is jealous when Bree gets the part she was hoping to play. (S2 Ep2a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 21:15:00" d="2020-10-30 21:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy realizes she is more like her Mum than she thought. (S2 Ep1b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 21:30:00" d="2020-10-30 22:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When Remy says goodbye to the Hauntleys to chase his dream as a chef at a fancy restaurant, a spookghetti monster pops up! Oxana adds a spooky flair to the school fair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 22:00:00" d="2020-10-30 22:15:00"><n u="PJ Masks S4 Splits">PJ Masks S4 Splits IV (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Newton likes the PJ Masks but also likes his solitude</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 22:15:00" d="2020-10-30 22:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks S4 Splits">PJ Masks S4 Splits IV (91)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Owlette causes a freak asteroid accident. Gekko and Catboy try to help her put it right. But there is more to the accident than there seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 22:30:00" d="2020-10-30 23:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Kion warns Jasiri about Scar’s return and offers her protection in the Pride Lands. Jasiri declines and instead offers to help fight Scar and his minions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 23:00:00" d="2020-10-30 23:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% When Princess Zooey, a new student at Royal Prep, starts a Princess Adventure Club to make friends and invites all the princesses to join except Amber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 23:25:00" d="2020-10-30 23:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales">Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mickey and Pluto are having trouble coming up with Halloween costumes, Pluto inspires Mickey to create the most spook-tacular costumes in Hot Dog Hills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-30 23:30:00" d="2020-10-31 00:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky wants a tail as powerful as Giganto’s, but with great power comes great responsibility. Bill discovers that ‘crying wolf’ lets him avoid doing things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 00:00:00" d="2020-10-31 00:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Luna Girl creates a giant moon ball, and hides the toys she’s stolen inside: Romeo and Night Ninja try to shrink the PJ Masks with Romeo’s invention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 00:25:00" d="2020-10-31 00:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Luna blames her moths for defeats and steals butterflies to replace them. Luna Girl and Owlette compete to win the biggest, best toy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 00:50:00" d="2020-10-31 01:00:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins make up a lovely song for Podium, but they just can’t remember the words (S1 Ep1c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 01:00:00" d="2020-10-31 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After learning about the importance of saving water, Zou decides to carry water around in a bucket and make his family ask when they want</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 01:15:00" d="2020-10-31 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Grandma is helping Zou make a cherry pie for a bake-off. Meanwhile Grandpa has lost the garage key - and it eventually turns up in a very strange place!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 01:30:00" d="2020-10-31 01:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Talent contest The Grr Factor is in town. Henry wants Daddo to demonstrate his juggling. Momma and Daddo leave Cobby to babysit and the power goes to his head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 01:55:00" d="2020-10-31 02:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rain stops Henry going to the Monster Wave Park, so he comes up with a novel way to have a swim. Summer loses Momma’s necklace so she runs away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 02:20:00" d="2020-10-31 02:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia are eager to play with Bigfoot, but he’s moving very slowly because his tooth is loose. The twins have trouble adjusting to this pace. (S1 Ep12c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 02:30:00" d="2020-10-31 02:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins want to do a drawing but they run out of paper! (S1 Ep13a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 02:40:00" d="2020-10-31 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Zou and Zak hear strange noises in the house, they are convinced it is haunted. With a little help from Grandpa and Elzee, the &quot;ghosts&quot; are tracked down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 02:55:00" d="2020-10-31 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou must do a project on The Wind. But what should he make? In the end, he creates a bicycle powered fan, which everyone likes: it’s a very hot day!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 03:10:00" d="2020-10-31 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Grandpa is going to an army reunion but on the way he loses his precious medal. Luckily Zou made a brass-rubbing of it – will Zou be able to find the medal?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 03:25:00" d="2020-10-31 03:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia spend the day at Magma’s while their parents are away. They’ve got loads of fun activities planned, but Magma isn’t interested in any of them. (S1 Ep9a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 03:35:00" d="2020-10-31 03:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the twins find out that Podium dreams of being stronger than Magma, they tell a little lie to take advantage of his services. (S1 Ep9b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 03:45:00" d="2020-10-31 04:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry and Denzel overhear Denzel’s parents talk about going away. He thinks they are moving and is very sad but plans a going away party for his best friend.( S2 E206b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 04:00:00" d="2020-10-31 04:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny performs a triceratops rite of passage. Rocky sets out to prove that he's the ultimate tough guy, like Giganto, but discovers that everyone needs help sometimes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 04:30:00" d="2020-10-31 05:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu makes Archie a pair of wings to help him fly. Marsh copies Rocky's every move while Rocky copies Giganto</k>  </p>
</a>
