<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="61" t="2020-10-25 03:40:27"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 05:00:00" d="2020-11-01 05:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky gets jealous when Tiny suddenly becomes the go-to hero! Mazu may be a slow runner but is a quick thinker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 05:30:00" d="2020-11-01 06:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill accidentally changes Cretacia’s ecosystem when he eats too many rare swamp flowers. Dilo pulls pranks on the dinos!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 06:00:00" d="2020-11-01 06:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo turns Owlette's Flossy Flash toy into a device that transforms the PJ Masks into action toys! Night Ninja steals an ancient gong to awaken a Dragon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 06:25:00" d="2020-11-01 06:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks Music Video">PJ Masks Music Video I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Music accompanies clips from the popular show featuring pyjama-clad heroes Catboy, Gekko and Owlette, who have adventures and learn valuable lessons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 06:30:00" d="2020-11-01 06:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% An evil plan from Night Ninja divides the P J Masks. Our heroes team up with other villains to defeat Romeo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 06:55:00" d="2020-11-01 07:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While trying to fix their satellite TV Minnie and Daisy get stuck on the roof. They can’t find their way back down to watch their favourite TV show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 07:00:00" d="2020-11-01 07:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Fuli and Makini must escort one of the Pride Lands’ wisest animals: a slow and deliberate tortoise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 07:30:00" d="2020-11-01 08:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse III (85)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% On Story Day it's Pluto's turn to tell of a pup called Pluto who wins a golden ball. He's pursued iby Sneaky Pete and transformed into a brave prince</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 08:00:00" d="2020-11-01 08:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny throws a party but can she deliver on the outrageous promises she made? When Mazu wants to see a once-in-a-lifetime comet, everyone else's needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 08:30:00" d="2020-11-01 09:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy teach a lion cub the difference between his &quot;indoor&quot; and &quot;outdoor&quot; roar. When a porcupine is scared of the delivery tube, K.C</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 09:00:00" d="2020-11-01 09:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Honey’s trip to see Dr. Bingo keeps getting interrupted by other, more exciting patients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 09:10:00" d="2020-11-01 09:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad create their own Magic Claw machine at home, but can Bluey win the big prize?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 09:20:00" d="2020-11-01 09:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Bluey is needed when Dad gets a very curious x-ray from Nurse Bingo. It seems he has a cat in his tummy, leaving Bluey no choice but to operate immediately!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 09:30:00" d="2020-11-01 09:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo’s plans to stay up late are derailed when Muffin misses her nap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 09:40:00" d="2020-11-01 09:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With five bucks from the tooth fairy, Bluey is overwhelmed with possibilities at the markets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 09:50:00" d="2020-11-01 10:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A trip to the pool’s great fun, until Dad forgets the towels, lunch and everything else!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 10:00:00" d="2020-11-01 10:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey must turn lemons into lemonade when he's having 'one of those days!' Cuckoo Loca's cousins visit from Paris!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 10:30:00" d="2020-11-01 11:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena of Avalor has saved her enchanted kingdom from an evil sorceress, and now must learn to rule Avalor with the help of her family and friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 11:00:00" d="2020-11-01 11:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy accidentally becomes Freddy’s new best friend when JoJo ditches him for her imaginary friend. Nancy decides to live on her own in the playhouse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 11:30:00" d="2020-11-01 12:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (81)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The moths infiltrate HQ, and Gekko won’t admit that he let them in until it is too late. Catboy realizes that a true Cat Explorer puts his team before the discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 12:00:00" d="2020-11-01 13:00:00"><n>PJ Masks: Heroes of The Sky</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 13:00:00" d="2020-11-01 13:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bob's lucky baseball bat breaks, the pups go on a mission to find a new one in time for the championship game. The pugs help a group of lost moles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 13:30:00" d="2020-11-01 14:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals III (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Chloe's dad's flight gets cancelled, so Keia and the pugs go on an urgent mission to bring him home. When Dash and Duke's favorite toy goes missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 14:00:00" d="2020-11-01 14:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bob wants to wake up on his dream vacation, so the pugs try to get him to Tahiti while he sleeps. Bingo and Rolly search all around the golf course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 14:30:00" d="2020-11-01 15:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bob signs up for a game show with Bingo and Rolly. When Bob's trip to the Empire State Building is cancelled the Pugs and ARF head to NYC to bring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 15:00:00" d="2020-11-01 15:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pups lose an important part of Bob's presentation during Take Your Dog to Work Day. Bob, the pugs and Keia run out of popcorn at their first slumber party!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 15:30:00" d="2020-11-01 16:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Cupcake hurts Rufus' feelings, Bingo and Rolly reunite the best friends. Bob forgets his camera on the trolley before his photography class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 16:00:00" d="2020-11-01 16:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When Remy says goodbye to the Hauntleys to chase his dream as a chef at a fancy restaurant, a spookghetti monster pops up! Oxana adds a spooky flair to the school fair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 16:30:00" d="2020-11-01 17:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When Edgar crashes the annual Ghoul Guides Extravaganza vamping trip in Transylvania, Vee and the girls must come clean about Vee's family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 17:00:00" d="2020-11-01 17:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When horsing around with Dad goes too far, Bingo learns about finding her big girl voice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 17:10:00" d="2020-11-01 17:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey needs to stay focused and not get distracted, during a family game of hide and seek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 17:20:00" d="2020-11-01 17:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s Bingo’s turn with Kindy’s Bob Bilby puppet and she’s going to show him a good time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 17:30:00" d="2020-11-01 18:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bob stays late at work to do a presentation and forgets his dinner, the pugs decide to bring it to him. Keia’s new caterpillar friend goes missing!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 18:00:00" d="2020-11-01 18:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy is determined to save money to go to Paris, but is devastated when she discovers how long it will take. Nancy realizes she is more like her Mom than she realized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 18:30:00" d="2020-11-01 19:30:00"><n u="Night Ninja">Night Ninja I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>This extra-long adventure features four tales about Night Ninja’s nefarious schemes, in which he involves henchmen the ninjalinos in executing his plots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 19:30:00" d="2020-11-01 20:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% A gorilla ally seems to cause the Pride Lands more harm than good</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 20:00:00" d="2020-11-01 20:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% When Sofia invites Princess Kari to perform ballet at Royal Prep's Open House, she struggles to learn the steps and Sofia must help Kari realize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 20:30:00" d="2020-11-01 21:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia encourages kitchen maid Gwen to pursue her dream of being an inventor. Together they invent a contraption that will automatically paint bowls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 21:00:00" d="2020-11-01 21:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (83)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks are enticed by a fake An Yu to break all the rules, and have a party on Mystery Mountain. An Yu tries to domesticate the wild Wolfies!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 21:30:00" d="2020-11-01 22:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (84)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Armadylan and Catboy compete over an exclusive Master Fang comic, thinking it contains a hero secret. Armadylan loses the PJs’ special jet to Night Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 22:00:00" d="2020-11-01 22:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (85)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Owlette causes an asteroid accident. While trying to make it right, the PJ Masks meet another night-time hero, Newton! Newton likes the PJ Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 22:30:00" d="2020-11-01 23:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky wants a tail as powerful as Giganto’s, but with great power comes great responsibility. Bill discovers that ‘crying wolf’ lets him avoid doing things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 23:00:00" d="2020-11-01 23:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The dinos have a falling out. After Archie saves Tiny, the little dino must repay the favour and honour the Triceratops Code</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 23:30:00" d="2020-11-02 00:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Rugo tries to collect all of the coconuts in Cretacia, Bill sets out to get them back! Tiny and Totor discover they have a lot in common</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 00:00:00" d="2020-11-02 00:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu and Rocky must work together to save Tiny and Bill from Terminonator. Bill and Marsh are separated from their friends in a storm and must face their fears to get home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 00:30:00" d="2020-11-02 01:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Armadylan saves the city. Romeo tries to use Armadylan's powers to improve his lab</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 01:00:00" d="2020-11-02 01:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Night Ninja steals everything from Gekko's party. Luna Girl turns a sleep-walking Cameron into her puppet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 01:25:00" d="2020-11-02 01:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Night Ninja steals the school bus and converts it into his very own super-vehicle! The PJ Masks discover a super teeny Ninjalino at HQ</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 01:50:00" d="2020-11-02 02:00:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia decide to clean up their room, but they need to come up with a method that works. (S1 Ep2b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 02:00:00" d="2020-11-02 02:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and Elzee see a rainbow and Grandpa tells them about the legendary pot of gold at the end. They decide to make one and Grandpa puts some &quot;treasure&quot; at its end</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 02:15:00" d="2020-11-02 02:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou sees an illusionist and decides he’d like to be a magician. When a magic prop malfunctions and his assistant disappears, Zou wonders if he really has magical powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 02:30:00" d="2020-11-02 02:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s Hugglemas. Henry’s excited as it’s his turn to switch on the family’s lights. But he gets trapped in the Enormomonsters’ house - can he escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 02:55:00" d="2020-11-02 03:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Will unforeseen events make Henry late for his first day at Monsterschool? Summer delivers singing Summergrams around Roarsville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 03:20:00" d="2020-11-02 03:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia feel great, and they want to share their good mood with everyone else. But Podium is so grumpy - even the twins can’t do anything about it! (S1 Ep14a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 03:30:00" d="2020-11-02 03:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia want everyone to think they’re cute. (S1 Ep14b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 03:40:00" d="2020-11-02 03:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and his friends are to play an important football match but their kit is locked in the sports hall, including Zou’s lucky shirt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 03:55:00" d="2020-11-02 04:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While litter-picking, Zou finds a lucky wrapper that gets Zinnia a great prize. Zou’s consolation is being on the winning team for the Tidiest Town competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 04:10:00" d="2020-11-02 04:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou plays Footprints in the snow with Grandpa, They must follow a trail of footprints left in the snow. But has Zou been too sneaky? Has he lost Elzee and Zena forever?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 04:25:00" d="2020-11-02 04:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins have to make a choice between two friends. (S1 Ep11a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 04:35:00" d="2020-11-02 04:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magma’s garden is a real labyrinth. Stan takes on the challenge of getting through it alone, while Olivia teams up with their friends. (S1 Ep11b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 04:45:00" d="2020-11-02 05:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry's excited because it's Spring Cleaning Day and there are lots of bubbles about! (S2 Ep21b)</k>  </p>
</a>
