<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="76" t="2020-10-26 03:40:04"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 05:00:00" d="2020-11-02 05:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu and her three besties map the stars. Tiny’s artistic skills are put to use when the dinos are lost in the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 05:30:00" d="2020-11-02 06:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny and Mazu treat Giganto's toothache. Every dino in Cretacia tries to claim a beautiful pebble!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 06:00:00" d="2020-11-02 06:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo creates a space laser to carve his face on the moon. Romeo plans to use a device to make everyone so clumsy that they can’t stop him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 06:25:00" d="2020-11-02 06:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks Music Videos">PJ Masks Music Videos II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The leader of the PJ Masks, Catboy is incredibly fast – an almost invisible blur as he covers huge distances in the blink of an eye at Super Cat Speed!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 06:30:00" d="2020-11-02 06:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo’s new robot, Robette, decides to take over the world. Owlette wants to be a pet owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 06:55:00" d="2020-11-02 07:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Pet Salon transforms into a three-ring circus as Minnie and Daisy do their best to bathe Ellie, an adorable, and muddy, baby elephant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 07:00:00" d="2020-11-02 07:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% When the hyenas and jackals launch simultaneous attacks, Kion uses Tamaa the Drongo to help the Guard be in two places at once</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 07:30:00" d="2020-11-02 08:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse III (87)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% It’s the grand opening of Minnie’s Bow-tique, a store packed with bows and bowties. Mickey and friends do their best to make sure all the store’s customers are happy. (S3 Ep 22)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 08:00:00" d="2020-11-02 08:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Bluey and Bingo squabble over their magic xylophone (that has the power to freeze Dad in space and time) Dad seizes control and freezes Bluey, leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 08:10:00" d="2020-11-02 08:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Bluey is needed when Dad gets a very curious x-ray from Nurse Bingo. It seems he has a cat in his tummy, leaving Bluey no choice but to operate immediately!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 08:20:00" d="2020-11-02 08:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum are enjoying playing Keepy Uppy around the house with their last balloon, when Dad joins in and the game becomes the ultimate test of skill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 08:30:00" d="2020-11-02 08:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo don't want to tidy the playroom, so they get Daddy Robot to do it for them. But when Bluey takes things too far, Daddy Robot malfunctions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 08:40:00" d="2020-11-02 08:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the weekend, Bluey and Bingo are playing in the garden with Dad. But Bingo gets upset, when she discovers a walking leaf insect and Dad is too caught</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 08:50:00" d="2020-11-02 09:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s lunchtime on Bluey's back deck! But every BBQ needs a side salad, so Bingo’s relaxing sit-down will have to wait until she finds every colour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 09:00:00" d="2020-11-02 09:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% When the new Fairground Flyer Train goes missing, Owlette is determined to get it back. Catboy must save the summer from Luna Girl, but to do so he’ll</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 09:30:00" d="2020-11-02 10:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena officially becomes crown princess and rescues her sister, Isabel, from Noblins, elf-like shapeshifting creatures based on a Chilean peuchen myth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 10:00:00" d="2020-11-02 10:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy teach a lion cub the difference between his &quot;indoor&quot; and &quot;outdoor&quot; roar. When a porcupine is scared of the delivery tube, K.C</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 10:30:00" d="2020-11-02 11:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy deliver a monkey who loves to play pretend so much, it gets in the way of his delivery! When a baby hippo refuses to eat his food, K.C</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 11:00:00" d="2020-11-02 11:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bob loses his shirt and leaves the pups with his mom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 11:30:00" d="2020-11-02 12:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pugs go to Australia. The pups get a fishy friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 12:00:00" d="2020-11-02 12:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Can the pups find Chloe's lost puppy before she returns? Chloe wishes for a unicorn. The pups set out to find one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 12:30:00" d="2020-11-02 13:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo erases stories from books, so Owlette enlists the help of Flossy Flash. Romeo uses boxing gloves to steal a jetpack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 13:00:00" d="2020-11-02 13:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Night Ninja steals sports equipment for his Ninjalinos. Romeo takes a pterodactyl model and turns it into a flying robot!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 13:30:00" d="2020-11-02 14:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Luna Girl creates a giant moon ball, and hides the toys she’s stolen inside: Romeo and Night Ninja try to shrink the PJ Masks with Romeo’s invention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 14:00:00" d="2020-11-02 14:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy learns covering up an accident makes it worse. When Nancy finds a butterfly, she wants to keep it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 14:30:00" d="2020-11-02 15:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy’s horrified when Dad builds a non-fancy playhouse! Nancy starts a charm school to teach friends to be fancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 15:00:00" d="2020-11-02 15:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Not wanting to go to bed, Bluey tries to dream about being a nocturnal fruit bat so she can stay up all night long and soon finds herself flying through the night sky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 15:10:00" d="2020-11-02 15:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and their cousins make Dad and Uncle Stripe play a game of Horsey Ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 15:20:00" d="2020-11-02 15:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad gets embroiled in a game of Hotel, where Bluey and Bingo run a crazy hotel and Dad is the beleaguered guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 15:30:00" d="2020-11-02 15:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s struggling to ride her bike. But inspired by her friends, she refuses to give up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 15:40:00" d="2020-11-02 15:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s Bingo’s turn with Kindy’s Bob Bilby puppet and she’s going to show him a good time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 15:50:00" d="2020-11-02 16:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When horsing around with Dad goes too far, Bingo learns about finding her big girl voice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 16:00:00" d="2020-11-02 16:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First IV (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% While travelling to the Mystic Isles on a quest, Minimus and Skye compete for Sofia's attention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 16:25:00" d="2020-11-02 16:30:00"><n u="Fancy It Yourself Shorts">Fancy It Yourself Shorts I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy and Bree teach us how to host an exquisite tea party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 16:30:00" d="2020-11-02 17:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When Elena and her friends are stranded at sea, an enchanted ship rescues them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 17:00:00" d="2020-11-02 17:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Honey’s trip to see Dr. Bingo keeps getting interrupted by other, more exciting patients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 17:10:00" d="2020-11-02 17:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad create their own Magic Claw machine at home, but can Bluey win the big prize?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 17:20:00" d="2020-11-02 17:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A trip to the pool’s great fun, until Dad forgets the towels, lunch and everything else!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 17:30:00" d="2020-11-02 17:45:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (88)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hot Dog! Get mixed-up with Mickey and all of his pals in his new house in Hot Dog Hills! Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie, Daisy, Pluto and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 17:45:00" d="2020-11-02 18:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (70)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's Mini-Mechanics Day and Mickey's number one fan can't wait to get to work! (S3 Ep10a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 18:00:00" d="2020-11-02 18:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Marabelle gets injured, Nancy must stay calm under pressure as the doll surgeon on call. (S2 Ep2b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 18:15:00" d="2020-11-02 18:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy is jealous when Bree gets the part she was hoping to play. (S2 Ep2a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 18:30:00" d="2020-11-02 19:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When Edgar crashes the annual Ghoul Guides Extravaganza vamping trip in Transylvania, Vee and the girls must come clean about Vee's family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 19:00:00" d="2020-11-02 19:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (81)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The moths infiltrate HQ, and Gekko won’t admit that he let them in until it is too late. Catboy realizes that a true Cat Explorer puts his team before the discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 19:30:00" d="2020-11-02 20:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Kion finds getting Pride Landers to work together difficult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 20:00:00" d="2020-11-02 20:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia’s pet rabbit Clover is acting spoilt. But when another bunny is mistaken for him and he is left in the forest, Clover must give up his spoiled ways to survive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 20:25:00" d="2020-11-02 20:30:00"><n u="Fancy It Yourself Shorts">Fancy It Yourself Shorts I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy and Bree teach us how to host an exquisite tea party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 20:30:00" d="2020-11-02 21:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% It's the day of the dance, but Sofia's friend arrives early, and she promised to show her around. Sofia discovers a way she can be in two places at once</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 21:00:00" d="2020-11-02 21:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey loses patience when Dad keeps stopping to chat with grown-ups on the way to the park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 21:10:00" d="2020-11-02 21:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With Bluey as his taxi driver, Dad’s got no chance of making it the airport on time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 21:20:00" d="2020-11-02 21:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mum takes a walk along the beach, Bluey follows behind on her first solo adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 21:30:00" d="2020-11-02 21:45:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (88)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hot Dog! Get mixed-up with Mickey and all of his pals in his new house in Hot Dog Hills! Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie, Daisy, Pluto and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 21:45:00" d="2020-11-02 22:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (70)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's Mini-Mechanics Day and Mickey's number one fan can't wait to get to work! (S3 Ep10a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 22:00:00" d="2020-11-02 22:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Marabelle gets injured, Nancy must stay calm under pressure as the doll surgeon on call. (S2 Ep2b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 22:15:00" d="2020-11-02 22:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy is jealous when Bree gets the part she was hoping to play. (S2 Ep2a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 22:30:00" d="2020-11-02 23:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When Edgar crashes the annual Ghoul Guides Extravaganza vamping trip in Transylvania, Vee and the girls must come clean about Vee's family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 23:00:00" d="2020-11-02 23:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (81)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The moths infiltrate HQ, and Gekko won’t admit that he let them in until it is too late. Catboy realizes that a true Cat Explorer puts his team before the discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-02 23:30:00" d="2020-11-03 00:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Kion finds getting Pride Landers to work together difficult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 00:00:00" d="2020-11-03 00:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia’s pet rabbit Clover is acting spoilt. But when another bunny is mistaken for him and he is left in the forest, Clover must give up his spoiled ways to survive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 00:25:00" d="2020-11-03 00:30:00"><n u="Fancy It Yourself Shorts">Fancy It Yourself Shorts I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy and Bree teach us how to host an exquisite tea party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 00:30:00" d="2020-11-03 01:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The dinos have a falling out. After Archie saves Tiny, the little dino must repay the favour and honour the Triceratops Code</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 01:00:00" d="2020-11-03 01:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy has two concert tickets and must decide which friend to take. Gekko loses the Gekko-Mobile when they need it the most!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 01:25:00" d="2020-11-03 01:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Something is fishy when Catboy gets a gift of a scooter from an unknown aunt. Gekko’s got the sneezes and his friends want him to rest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 01:50:00" d="2020-11-03 02:00:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Time for Puff’s nap: the twins offer help her get to sleep, instead of Sheriff Pearl. It’s harder than they expect! (S1 Ep2c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 02:00:00" d="2020-11-03 02:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Grandma has been telling Zou about the Easter Bunny and how he leaves eggs out for children. Zou decides to leave eggs out for the Bunny as well</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 02:15:00" d="2020-11-03 02:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou builds a model dinosaur from bits of furniture, etc. but there’s nothing to resemble a dinosaur hide - until Grandma’s washing blows off the line!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 02:30:00" d="2020-11-03 02:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While delivering people’s seed orders Daddo accidentally mixes them up. Henry’s scared of meeting the legendary Sno-Grrr, but gets a surprise when he does</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 02:55:00" d="2020-11-03 03:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry encourages his friends to draw their own comic. Henry invites neighbour Roddy to play with him, but Roddy misbehaves. Can Henry change him?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 03:20:00" d="2020-11-03 03:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan wants to win the soap bubble competition. He teams up with Bigfoot but realizes his friend is kind of hopeless. He does everything he can to change partners. (S1 Ep14c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 03:30:00" d="2020-11-03 03:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins want to keep playing King with Bigfoot. (S1 Ep15a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 03:40:00" d="2020-11-03 03:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s Zak’s birthday and his dad has bought him tickets for a basketball match. But both teams have come down with flu. Zou organises a much more exciting match instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 03:55:00" d="2020-11-03 04:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Elzee misses out on a place in a gymnastics competition she’s disappointed. Then Zou suggests they enter as a team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 04:10:00" d="2020-11-03 04:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou decides Zigmund and Zoroaster need to get fit and appoints himself their personal trainer. But he makes it too hard and finds he is training all by himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 04:25:00" d="2020-11-03 04:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan wants to give Bigfoot a present, but the twins can’t help doing everything together. How can he find a way to make his present by himself? (S1 Ep12a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 04:35:00" d="2020-11-03 04:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Captain Stan has to come up with an idea in order to get Olivia free. (S1 Ep12b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 04:45:00" d="2020-11-03 05:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry is the new voice of the local radio station. But he starts upsetting people when he tells their secrets to the whole of Roarsville! ( S2 Ep22a)</k>  </p>
</a>
