<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="76" t="2020-10-27 03:59:33"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 05:00:00" d="2020-11-03 05:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill wishes Giganto would go away forever after his coconut lunch is disrupted. Ayati sends the four friends off on a quest to find a legendary land call Dinosia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 05:30:00" d="2020-11-03 06:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill’s friends pretend he is invisible so he can win at hide-and-seek. Mazu invents eyeglasses to help near-sighted Patchy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 06:00:00" d="2020-11-03 06:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo uses his newest device to make the PJ Masks and their HQ float away! When Romeo steals the PJ Masks’ super vehicles, they have to use their bicycles to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 06:25:00" d="2020-11-03 06:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks Music Videos">PJ Masks Music Videos II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Gekko’s lizard pajamas give him the superpower of strength. No obstacle is too big or heavy for him as he flexes his Super Gekko Muscles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 06:30:00" d="2020-11-03 06:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% When the school instruments go missing, Owlette and Gekko are hot on the trail. Catboy and Gekko dream up an exciting new superhero move, but Owlette can’t get it right!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 06:55:00" d="2020-11-03 07:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It is Pet Adoption day, and lots of pets need a home, especially Gilbert, a guinea Pig who wants to impress Minnie’s pet salon customers. Will he find a new family?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 07:00:00" d="2020-11-03 07:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% When Scar’s minions take over the Kilio Valley, the Pride Lands must adjust to an influx of elephants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 07:30:00" d="2020-11-03 08:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse III (89)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Goofy has gone missing and his friends are worried he may have been abducted by a monster. So they use their special spy and superhero powers to find him. (S3 Ep 24)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 08:00:00" d="2020-11-03 08:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo and Bluey can’t agree on one simple question: Can Grannies do the floss dance?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 08:10:00" d="2020-11-03 08:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In a game of Work, Bluey and Bingo are the latest hires at Dad’s drainpipe factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 08:20:00" d="2020-11-03 08:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad can’t go to work until he has played all of Bluey and Bingo’s trampoline games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 08:30:00" d="2020-11-03 08:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo causes chaos at Bluey’s backyard zoo, when she sneaks into Daddy Gorilla’s cage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 08:40:00" d="2020-11-03 08:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad are going on an adventure with Bluey and Bingo as their backpacks!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 08:50:00" d="2020-11-03 09:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo’s plans to stay up late are derailed when Muffin misses her nap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 09:00:00" d="2020-11-03 09:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Luna blames her moths for defeats and steals butterflies to replace them. Luna Girl and Owlette compete to win the biggest, best toy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 09:30:00" d="2020-11-03 10:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena is torn between a promise she made to help Isabel and fulfilling her royal duties as crown princess. George Takei (Star Trek) guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 10:00:00" d="2020-11-03 10:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On Pip and Freddy’s first day, they deliver a kitten who mistakes them as her parents. When there is a two-ton baby whale delivery, the fliers compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 10:30:00" d="2020-11-03 11:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy must deliver a baby panda that is so cute, that it makes it hard to say goodbye. The Junior Fliers have trouble delivering a baby skunk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 11:00:00" d="2020-11-03 11:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pugs encourage Keia to host a puppy housewarming party. Rolly loses a first puppy tooth. Will the Fang Fairy visit?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 11:30:00" d="2020-11-03 12:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Snow monkeys help the pups to save Bob's ski trip. A.R.F. gets a robo-cold before an important demonstration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 12:00:00" d="2020-11-03 12:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pups return Chloe's lost toy to her at Space Camp. Bob throws a ball too hard. The pugs follow clues to find it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 12:30:00" d="2020-11-03 13:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo steals Gekko’s voice, but Gekko’s not sure he wants it back before his poetry presentation. Night Ninja has stolen Master Fang’s prized sword!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 13:00:00" d="2020-11-03 13:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy has to get Amaya’s and Greg’s stolen superhero pyjamas back from Romeo! Owlette’s prized Giving Owl statue is stolen by Luna Girl to decorate her new headquarters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 13:30:00" d="2020-11-03 14:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Night Ninja steals everything from Gekko's party. Luna Girl turns a sleep-walking Cameron into her puppet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 14:00:00" d="2020-11-03 14:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy's attempts to give Mom a perfect spa day go wrong. Nancy becomes Dad's assistant and causes an office disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 14:30:00" d="2020-11-03 15:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jo Jo has an imaginary friend. Can Nancy make perfect handprints in a newly cemented path?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 15:00:00" d="2020-11-03 15:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey needs to stay focused and not get distracted, during a family game of hide and seek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 15:10:00" d="2020-11-03 15:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey needs Mum's advice when her couch-cushion playhouse has noisy neighbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 15:20:00" d="2020-11-03 15:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s magic asparagus turns her family into wild animals with no manners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 15:30:00" d="2020-11-03 15:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey struggles to train her new pet Shaun, an unruly and troublesome emu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 15:40:00" d="2020-11-03 15:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Bluey and Bingo squabble over their magic xylophone (that has the power to freeze Dad in space and time) Dad seizes control and freezes Bluey, leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 15:50:00" d="2020-11-03 16:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Bluey is needed when Dad gets a very curious x-ray from Nurse Bingo. It seems he has a cat in his tummy, leaving Bluey no choice but to operate immediately!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 16:00:00" d="2020-11-03 16:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First IV (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% After spending time learning to be royal, Sofia’s ready to discover some of Enchancia’s secrets as she releases a genie, finds a secret library and learns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 16:25:00" d="2020-11-03 16:30:00"><n u="Fancy It Yourself Shorts">Fancy It Yourself Shorts I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy fancies up her beloved dog, Frenchy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 16:30:00" d="2020-11-03 17:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When a mysterious spell turns Elena and her friends into moving Maruvian sculptures, Elena must rely on her little sister to help undo the spell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 17:00:00" d="2020-11-03 17:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum are enjoying playing Keepy Uppy around the house with their last balloon, when Dad joins in and the game becomes the ultimate test of skill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 17:10:00" d="2020-11-03 17:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo don't want to tidy the playroom, so they get Daddy Robot to do it for them. But when Bluey takes things too far, Daddy Robot malfunctions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 17:20:00" d="2020-11-03 17:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the weekend, Bluey and Bingo are playing in the garden with Dad. But Bingo gets upset, when she discovers a walking leaf insect and Dad is too caught</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 17:30:00" d="2020-11-03 17:45:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (89)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hot Dog! Get mixed-up with Mickey and all of his pals in his new house in Hot Dog Hills! Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie, Daisy, Pluto and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 17:45:00" d="2020-11-03 18:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (88)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hot Dog! Get mixed-up with Mickey and all of his pals in his new house in Hot Dog Hills! Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie, Daisy, Pluto and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 18:00:00" d="2020-11-03 18:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fancy Nancy Clancy has adventures with family and friends, as she finds the extraordinary in the ordinary, and – with a little imagination- transforms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 18:15:00" d="2020-11-03 18:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Marabelle gets injured, Nancy must stay calm under pressure as the doll surgeon on call. (S2 Ep2b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 18:30:00" d="2020-11-03 19:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Vee has the most important job at Frankenstein and the Bride of Frankenstein's wedding! Gregoria sculpts the family for an art show, but Vee's not ready</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 19:00:00" d="2020-11-03 19:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (82)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJs offer to help Motsuki find Luna, but miss plot by Night Ninja in the process. When the Ninjalinos lose their ninja powers, the PJ Masks teach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 19:30:00" d="2020-11-03 20:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Dhahabu the golden zebra makes Fuli, Tiifu and Zuri her personal guard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 20:00:00" d="2020-11-03 20:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia discovers that her friend, Princess Lani, has the power to alter the weather according to her moods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 20:25:00" d="2020-11-03 20:30:00"><n u="Fancy It Yourself Shorts">Fancy It Yourself Shorts I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy fancies up her beloved dog, Frenchy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 20:30:00" d="2020-11-03 21:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Disney princess Mulan arrives to help Sofia, Amber and Princess Jun work together to rescue their fathers and brothers who are trapped in a jaguar's den</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 21:00:00" d="2020-11-03 21:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s lunchtime on Bluey's back deck! But every BBQ needs a side salad, so Bingo’s relaxing sit-down will have to wait until she finds every colour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 21:10:00" d="2020-11-03 21:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Not wanting to go to bed, Bluey tries to dream about being a nocturnal fruit bat so she can stay up all night long and soon finds herself flying through the night sky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 21:20:00" d="2020-11-03 21:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and their cousins make Dad and Uncle Stripe play a game of Horsey Ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 21:30:00" d="2020-11-03 21:45:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (89)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hot Dog! Get mixed-up with Mickey and all of his pals in his new house in Hot Dog Hills! Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie, Daisy, Pluto and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 21:45:00" d="2020-11-03 22:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (88)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hot Dog! Get mixed-up with Mickey and all of his pals in his new house in Hot Dog Hills! Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie, Daisy, Pluto and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 22:00:00" d="2020-11-03 22:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fancy Nancy Clancy has adventures with family and friends, as she finds the extraordinary in the ordinary, and – with a little imagination- transforms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 22:15:00" d="2020-11-03 22:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Marabelle gets injured, Nancy must stay calm under pressure as the doll surgeon on call. (S2 Ep2b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 22:30:00" d="2020-11-03 23:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Vee has the most important job at Frankenstein and the Bride of Frankenstein's wedding! Gregoria sculpts the family for an art show, but Vee's not ready</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 23:00:00" d="2020-11-03 23:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (82)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJs offer to help Motsuki find Luna, but miss plot by Night Ninja in the process. When the Ninjalinos lose their ninja powers, the PJ Masks teach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-03 23:30:00" d="2020-11-04 00:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Dhahabu the golden zebra makes Fuli, Tiifu and Zuri her personal guard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 00:00:00" d="2020-11-04 00:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia discovers that her friend, Princess Lani, has the power to alter the weather according to her moods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 00:25:00" d="2020-11-04 00:30:00"><n u="Fancy It Yourself Shorts">Fancy It Yourself Shorts I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy fancies up her beloved dog, Frenchy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 00:30:00" d="2020-11-04 01:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Rugo tries to collect all of the coconuts in Cretacia, Bill sets out to get them back! Tiny and Totor discover they have a lot in common</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 01:00:00" d="2020-11-04 01:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Night Ninja creates a fortress of his own to take down the PJ Masks. When Romeo unleashes his Big Box of Bad, Gekko fails to stop him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 01:25:00" d="2020-11-04 01:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo‘s remote controls the PJ Masks! Night Ninja breaks Owlette’s statue, who gets revenge by destroying Night Ninja’s masterpiece!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 01:50:00" d="2020-11-04 02:00:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia are fascinated by Sheriff Pearl, and decide to become sheriffs themselves. Well, it’s not that simple! Both Olivia and Stan realize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 02:00:00" d="2020-11-04 02:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou discovers Grandpa’s old walkie talkie and is allowed to play with it. He finds it very useful when he runs errands for Nanna</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 02:15:00" d="2020-11-04 02:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou doesn’t stick to the rules when playing football with Elzee, and upsets Zak and Poc. He realises it’s better to enjoy yourself rather than being too strict</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 02:30:00" d="2020-11-04 02:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Momma reads Henry the story of a magical bird who loses a special feather. Henry and Momma undertake a quest to return the feather, but is their adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 02:55:00" d="2020-11-04 03:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry helps Estelle stop being jealous of her baby brother. Henry turns the house into a romantic restaurant for Momma and Daddo’s anniversary dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 03:20:00" d="2020-11-04 03:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Olivia forgot to prepare her bag. (S1 Ep15b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 03:30:00" d="2020-11-04 03:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan doesn’t like his piggy laugh and decides to stop laughing for good. (S1 Ep15c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 03:40:00" d="2020-11-04 03:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zowie and Zinnia are taking a cycling proficiency course. Zinnia is over-enthusiastic so Zou must show her where she’s going wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 03:55:00" d="2020-11-04 04:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou is looking after Elzee’s fern while she’s away. It seems to have died and she’s upset, but is it really dead?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 04:10:00" d="2020-11-04 04:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s been snowing and as Zou is on his way to Mr. Zoey’s he thinks he hears strange noises. It turns out Zigmund and Zoroaster are snowed in at Uncle Zavier’s shop!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 04:25:00" d="2020-11-04 04:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins want to do a drawing but they run out of paper! (S1 Ep13a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 04:35:00" d="2020-11-04 04:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia are playing with a mermaid. (S1 Ep13b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 04:45:00" d="2020-11-04 05:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s upset when little brother Ivor starts day care and can’t play with him. So he tries to break into day care and rescue Ivor! ( S2 Ep22b)</k>  </p>
</a>
