<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="76" t="2020-10-30 03:36:31"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 05:00:00" d="2020-11-06 05:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu invents the world's first go-carts to beat Giganto in a race. When Bill's food stash is raided, he makes it his mission to find the culprit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 05:30:00" d="2020-11-06 06:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When everyone blames Giganto for damaging the lake, the Dinos try to prove his innocence. Rocky wants to roar like Giganto, so he sets out to capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 06:00:00" d="2020-11-06 06:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo turns people into babies. Gekko babysits his mates. Owlette must get back Luna Girl’s board and magnet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 06:25:00" d="2020-11-06 06:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks Music Videos">PJ Masks Music Videos II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A splat-sticking, back flipping ninja, Night Ninja thinks he’s the best ninja (and best at everything for that matter) that ever lived!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 06:30:00" d="2020-11-06 06:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy hears of a way to increase his cat power. A Romeo remote makes Catboy's night last forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 06:55:00" d="2020-11-06 07:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie and Daisy throw a slumber party for their best friends. Clumsy Clarabelle feels like she keeps messing things up. In the end she makes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 07:00:00" d="2020-11-06 07:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% The Lion Guard and Makini discover a mysterious cave that may hold the key to defeating Scar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 07:30:00" d="2020-11-06 08:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse III (95)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% It’s the first day of Spring. Mickey and friends celebrate by looking for decorated eggs. That leads them to an &quot;eggs-cellent&quot; Springtime Surprise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 08:00:00" d="2020-11-06 08:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With Bluey as his taxi driver, Dad’s got no chance of making it the airport on time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 08:10:00" d="2020-11-06 08:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mum takes a walk along the beach, Bluey follows behind on her first solo adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 08:20:00" d="2020-11-06 08:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo and Bluey can’t agree on one simple question: Can Grannies do the floss dance?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 08:30:00" d="2020-11-06 08:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In a game of Work, Bluey and Bingo are the latest hires at Dad’s drainpipe factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 08:40:00" d="2020-11-06 08:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad can’t go to work until he has played all of Bluey and Bingo’s trampoline games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 08:50:00" d="2020-11-06 09:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo causes chaos at Bluey’s backyard zoo, when she sneaks into Daddy Gorilla’s cage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 09:00:00" d="2020-11-06 09:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% When the school instruments go missing, Owlette and Gekko are hot on the trail. Catboy and Gekko dream up an exciting new superhero move, but Owlette can’t get it right!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 09:30:00" d="2020-11-06 10:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When a wicked wizard named Fiero turns Elena's family to stone, Elena enlists the help of Mateo, her newly appointed Royal Wizard, to undo the spell and save her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 10:00:00" d="2020-11-06 10:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freddy must face his fear of the dark when he and Pip are assigned a nighttime delivery. Pip hopes to speed through the next delivery, but they are tasked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 10:30:00" d="2020-11-06 11:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip’s hiccups threaten their delivery so he asks Freddy to do the impossible, scare them out of him. Pip and Freddy have to prove that delivery birds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 11:00:00" d="2020-11-06 11:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pups search to find the perfect Valentine's Day gifts for Bob and Chloe. Bob is sad when the Symphony of Lights is canceled, so the pups</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 11:30:00" d="2020-11-06 12:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bob wishes he could run fast, the pugs find cheetahs to learn the secret of their speed. The pugs go on a journey to find the perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 12:00:00" d="2020-11-06 12:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pugs help their nervous puppy cousin, Cody, feel comfortable in a new place. When Hissy’s favorite toy goes missing, the pups go on a mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 12:30:00" d="2020-11-06 13:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo discovers P. J. Masks’ HQ’s secret rocket ship ability. Catboy learns appearances don’t matter as long as you save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 13:00:00" d="2020-11-06 13:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% When Romeo steals Owlette’s powers, he turns himself, Catboy, and Gekko into fliers. Night Ninja plans to turn Catboy's daytime parade into the Night Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 13:30:00" d="2020-11-06 14:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo’s multiplying machine accidentally makes Catboy copies. Night Ninja challenges the PJ Masks to a game of Capture the Flag with the PJ Mask headquarters as the prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 14:00:00" d="2020-11-06 14:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy must improvise when a storm ruins the family campout. Nancy wants Grandma's vanity, but it holds special memories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 14:30:00" d="2020-11-06 15:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy tries to prevent her old toy from being sold at the family yard sale without revealing that she still loves it. When Nancy produces Lionel’s first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 15:00:00" d="2020-11-06 15:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad are going on an adventure with Bluey and Bingo as their backpacks!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 15:10:00" d="2020-11-06 15:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo’s plans to stay up late are derailed when Muffin misses her nap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 15:20:00" d="2020-11-06 15:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey needs to stay focused and not get distracted, during a family game of hide and seek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 15:30:00" d="2020-11-06 15:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey needs Mum's advice when her couch-cushion playhouse has noisy neighbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 15:40:00" d="2020-11-06 15:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s magic asparagus turns her family into wild animals with no manners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 15:50:00" d="2020-11-06 16:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey struggles to train her new pet Shaun, an unruly and troublesome emu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 16:00:00" d="2020-11-06 16:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia discovers twins Amber and James’s don’t like sharing a birthday so she tries to solve the problem with Cedric the Magician’s help. Unfortunately</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 16:25:00" d="2020-11-06 16:30:00"><n u="Fancy It Yourself Shorts">Fancy It Yourself Shorts I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy and Bree show us how to make hair fancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 16:30:00" d="2020-11-06 17:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena of Avalor has saved her enchanted kingdom from an evil sorceress, and now must learn to rule Avalor with the help of her family and friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 17:00:00" d="2020-11-06 17:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Bluey and Bingo squabble over their magic xylophone (that has the power to freeze Dad in space and time) Dad seizes control and freezes Bluey, leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 17:10:00" d="2020-11-06 17:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Bluey is needed when Dad gets a very curious x-ray from Nurse Bingo. It seems he has a cat in his tummy, leaving Bluey no choice but to operate immediately!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 17:20:00" d="2020-11-06 17:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum are enjoying playing Keepy Uppy around the house with their last balloon, when Dad joins in and the game becomes the ultimate test of skill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 17:30:00" d="2020-11-06 17:45:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang plans to surprise Donald with a waffle breakfast for his birthday. (S3 Ep4a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 17:45:00" d="2020-11-06 18:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (91)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hot Dog! Get mixed-up with Mickey and all of his pals in his new house in Hot Dog Hills! Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie, Daisy, Pluto and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 18:00:00" d="2020-11-06 18:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On Valentine’s Day, Nancy helps Lionel say what’s in his heart. (S2 Ep9b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 18:15:00" d="2020-11-06 18:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fancy Nancy Clancy has adventures as she finds the extraordinary in the ordinary, and transforms the plain into the exquisite. (S2 Ep9a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 18:30:00" d="2020-11-06 19:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The baby dragon, Puffers, comes to visit the Hauntleys. The Hauntley house is infested with Charmer bugs!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 19:00:00" d="2020-11-06 19:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (85)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Owlette causes an asteroid accident. While trying to make it right, the PJ Masks meet another night-time hero, Newton! Newton likes the PJ Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 19:30:00" d="2020-11-06 20:00:00"><n u="Lion Guard S3, The">Lion Guard S3, The III (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Lion Guard roars again to defend the Pride Lands!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 20:00:00" d="2020-11-06 20:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% After Sofia and Vivian find an adorable baby dragon in the woods, they soon discover he’s not as innocent as he first appears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 20:25:00" d="2020-11-06 20:30:00"><n u="Fancy It Yourself Shorts">Fancy It Yourself Shorts I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy and Bree show us how to make hair fancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 20:30:00" d="2020-11-06 21:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% When an emerald key from the kingdom of Hakalo washes up on the shore, two girls claim to be the princess and rightful owners. Sofia must work out who is the imposter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 21:00:00" d="2020-11-06 21:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo don't want to tidy the playroom, so they get Daddy Robot to do it for them. But when Bluey takes things too far, Daddy Robot malfunctions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 21:10:00" d="2020-11-06 21:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the weekend, Bluey and Bingo are playing in the garden with Dad. But Bingo gets upset, when she discovers a walking leaf insect and Dad is too caught</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 21:20:00" d="2020-11-06 21:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s lunchtime on Bluey's back deck! But every BBQ needs a side salad, so Bingo’s relaxing sit-down will have to wait until she finds every colour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 21:30:00" d="2020-11-06 21:45:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang plans to surprise Donald with a waffle breakfast for his birthday. (S3 Ep4a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 21:45:00" d="2020-11-06 22:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (91)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hot Dog! Get mixed-up with Mickey and all of his pals in his new house in Hot Dog Hills! Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie, Daisy, Pluto and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 22:00:00" d="2020-11-06 22:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On Valentine’s Day, Nancy helps Lionel say what’s in his heart. (S2 Ep9b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 22:15:00" d="2020-11-06 22:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fancy Nancy Clancy has adventures as she finds the extraordinary in the ordinary, and transforms the plain into the exquisite. (S2 Ep9a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 22:30:00" d="2020-11-06 23:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The baby dragon, Puffers, comes to visit the Hauntleys. The Hauntley house is infested with Charmer bugs!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 23:00:00" d="2020-11-06 23:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (85)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Owlette causes an asteroid accident. While trying to make it right, the PJ Masks meet another night-time hero, Newton! Newton likes the PJ Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-06 23:30:00" d="2020-11-07 00:00:00"><n u="Lion Guard S3, The">Lion Guard S3, The III (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Lion Guard roars again to defend the Pride Lands!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 00:00:00" d="2020-11-07 00:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% After Sofia and Vivian find an adorable baby dragon in the woods, they soon discover he’s not as innocent as he first appears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 00:25:00" d="2020-11-07 00:30:00"><n u="Fancy It Yourself Shorts">Fancy It Yourself Shorts I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy and Bree show us how to make hair fancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 00:30:00" d="2020-11-07 01:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A falling meteorite forces the herd to move, leaving Giganto behind!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 01:00:00" d="2020-11-07 01:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy works too fast to kick back moonfizzle balls. Owlette must coach Catboy and Gekko to defeat Night Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 01:25:00" d="2020-11-07 01:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Gekko’s pet, Lionel, becomes a monster, wreaking havoc. Catboy confesses he has a cuddly toy to Owlette and Gekko</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 01:50:00" d="2020-11-07 02:00:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia play choo-choo train with Bigfoot, but they can’t settle on the right place, and the train takes a while to leave. (S1 Ep4a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 02:00:00" d="2020-11-07 02:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou is disappointed when the local pantomime is cancelled, so decides to stage his own. On the day of the performance Zou gets stage fright</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 02:15:00" d="2020-11-07 02:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Zou accidentally knocks over a pile of apples in Mr Zooey's shop, his attempts to rescue them remind Mr Zoey of a clown - and Zou decides he'd like to be a clown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 02:30:00" d="2020-11-07 02:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s upset he’s not invited to Summer’s sleepover so holds his own. Henry’s in charge while the mayor’s away and soon learns why rules exist. ( S2 Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 02:55:00" d="2020-11-07 03:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s organising Roarsville’s big wedding and asks Summer to be the flower monster. Henry and Denzel decide to start a boy band</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 03:20:00" d="2020-11-07 03:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia break a toy: it's time to play Toy Hospital! When there aren’t any broken toys to mend, it’s tempting to break other ones on purpose. (S1 Ep17c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 03:30:00" d="2020-11-07 03:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia make Bigfoot angry without meaning to. But Bigfoot has never been angry before, and doesn’t understand what’s happening to him. The twins try to help him. (S1 Ep18a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 03:40:00" d="2020-11-07 03:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou helps Zinnia make her mother a birthday present by finding out her favourite colour, flower and scent and incorporating them into a wonderful gift</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 03:55:00" d="2020-11-07 04:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The snow has cut off all communication. Nanna tells Zou that in earlier days, pigeons were used to carry messages, and he wonders if Poc could act as a messenger bird?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 04:10:00" d="2020-11-07 04:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Nanna gently bemoans the fact that in her young days, things were all so much slower; and everyone was more polite, Zou tries to recreate those days for her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 04:25:00" d="2020-11-07 04:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan has promised to help his friends but gets stuck in a traffic jam with his pedal car. Olivia says she can replace him, and do everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 04:35:00" d="2020-11-07 04:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia invite Bigfoot to sleep over. But Stan is terrified of Bigfoot’s clown cuddly toy! Bigfoot won’t sleep without it, so the evening could be cancelled. (S1 Ep16c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-07 04:45:00" d="2020-11-07 05:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry and his family work together to help get sunlight to the special Huggleflower. (S1 Ep1a)</k>  </p>
</a>
