<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="76" t="2020-10-28 03:43:57"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 05:00:00" d="2020-11-04 05:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a runaway boulder ruins Mazu’s invention, she sets out to find what set it in motion. Bill is tired of being a little brachiosaurus, so he looks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 05:30:00" d="2020-11-04 06:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky decides not to practice for a talent show but his partner in the show is Giganto. Marsh is tricked by raptors to play a game, but they’re really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 06:00:00" d="2020-11-04 06:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo’s multiplying machine accidentally makes Catboy copies. Night Ninja challenges the PJ Masks to a game of Capture the Flag with the PJ Mask headquarters as the prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 06:25:00" d="2020-11-04 06:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks Music Videos">PJ Masks Music Videos II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Owlette’s owl pajamas mean she can do something truly amazing – she can soar high in the sky with her Super Owl Wings!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 06:30:00" d="2020-11-04 06:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% When Night Ninja pushes the Ninjalinos too far, they become Owlette’s new sidekicks. When Greg doesn’t take care of Cameron's mini-car, it goes missing!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 06:55:00" d="2020-11-04 07:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Minnie and Daisy take twins Millie and Melody on a camping adventure, everything goes wrong and the trip is ruined – until Minnie discovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 07:00:00" d="2020-11-04 07:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Scar sets a plan in motion to destroy Simba and the Lion Guard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 07:30:00" d="2020-11-04 08:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse III (91)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Prof von Drake is working on his time machine. Pluto’s ball bounces in and travels to the time of dinosaurs. The Prof manages to retrieve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 08:00:00" d="2020-11-04 08:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad gets embroiled in a game of Hotel, where Bluey and Bingo run a crazy hotel and Dad is the beleaguered guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 08:10:00" d="2020-11-04 08:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s struggling to ride her bike. But inspired by her friends, she refuses to give up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 08:20:00" d="2020-11-04 08:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s Bingo’s turn with Kindy’s Bob Bilby puppet and she’s going to show him a good time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 08:30:00" d="2020-11-04 08:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When horsing around with Dad goes too far, Bingo learns about finding her big girl voice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 08:40:00" d="2020-11-04 08:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Honey’s trip to see Dr. Bingo keeps getting interrupted by other, more exciting patients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 08:50:00" d="2020-11-04 09:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad create their own Magic Claw machine at home, but can Bluey win the big prize?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 09:00:00" d="2020-11-04 09:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Night Ninja steals the school bus and converts it into his very own super-vehicle! The PJ Masks discover a super teeny Ninjalino at HQ</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 09:30:00" d="2020-11-04 10:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena finds herself at odds with the Grand Council when dealing with a magical rock whose anger can trigger a monfuego eruption!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 10:00:00" d="2020-11-04 10:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a cheetah is set loose at T.O.T.S., Pip and Freddy must play a game of tag to catch it! The Junior Fliers lead a class trip of storks and teach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 10:30:00" d="2020-11-04 11:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After KC gets sick, Pip and Freddy try to watch the babies in the Nursery for her. When delivery batches of bunnies get mixed up, the Junior Fliers figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 11:00:00" d="2020-11-04 11:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bob is learning to yodel, The Pugs go to the Alps for tips. It’s Bob’s birthday and his sister Bonnie is acting sneaky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 11:30:00" d="2020-11-04 12:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bob stays late at work to do a presentation and forgets his dinner, the pugs decide to bring it to him. Keia’s new caterpillar friend goes missing!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 12:00:00" d="2020-11-04 12:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After meeting a duckling that thinks he's a puppy, the pugs must teach him to be a duck. Bob and the pups head to Washington to compete in an environmental</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 12:30:00" d="2020-11-04 13:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy has two concert tickets and must decide which friend to take. Gekko loses the Gekko-Mobile when they need it the most!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 13:00:00" d="2020-11-04 13:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Something is fishy when Catboy gets a gift of a scooter from an unknown aunt. Gekko’s got the sneezes and his friends want him to rest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 13:30:00" d="2020-11-04 14:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo creates a space laser to carve his face on the moon. Romeo plans to use a device to make everyone so clumsy that they can’t stop him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 14:00:00" d="2020-11-04 14:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy learns she must practise to be a great ice skater. Nancy makes a mess painting a portrait. Jo Jo is blamed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 14:30:00" d="2020-11-04 15:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy has a sleepover at Mrs. Devine's. Nancy feels threatened when her boy cousin is fancier than she is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 15:00:00" d="2020-11-04 15:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A trip to the pool’s great fun, until Dad forgets the towels, lunch and everything else!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 15:10:00" d="2020-11-04 15:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey loses patience when Dad keeps stopping to chat with grown-ups on the way to the park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 15:20:00" d="2020-11-04 15:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With Bluey as his taxi driver, Dad’s got no chance of making it the airport on time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 15:30:00" d="2020-11-04 15:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mum takes a walk along the beach, Bluey follows behind on her first solo adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 15:40:00" d="2020-11-04 15:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo and Bluey can’t agree on one simple question: Can Grannies do the floss dance?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 15:50:00" d="2020-11-04 16:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In a game of Work, Bluey and Bingo are the latest hires at Dad’s drainpipe factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 16:00:00" d="2020-11-04 16:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia is upset when her mum invites Amber and James to their Mother’s Day picnic. She learns a valuable lesson when little witch Lucinda grants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 16:25:00" d="2020-11-04 16:30:00"><n u="Fancy It Yourself Shorts">Fancy It Yourself Shorts I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy teaches her Dad how to wear a boa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 16:30:00" d="2020-11-04 17:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena of Avalor has saved her enchanted kingdom from an evil sorceress, and now must learn to rule Avalor with the help of her family and friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 17:00:00" d="2020-11-04 17:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad can’t go to work until he has played all of Bluey and Bingo’s trampoline games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 17:10:00" d="2020-11-04 17:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo causes chaos at Bluey’s backyard zoo, when she sneaks into Daddy Gorilla’s cage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 17:20:00" d="2020-11-04 17:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad are going on an adventure with Bluey and Bingo as their backpacks!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 17:30:00" d="2020-11-04 17:45:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (90)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hot Dog! Get mixed-up with Mickey and all of his pals in his new house in Hot Dog Hills! Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie, Daisy, Pluto and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 17:45:00" d="2020-11-04 18:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (89)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hot Dog! Get mixed-up with Mickey and all of his pals in his new house in Hot Dog Hills! Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie, Daisy, Pluto and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 18:00:00" d="2020-11-04 18:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fancy Nancy Clancy has adventures as she finds the extraordinary in the ordinary, and transforms the plain into the exquisite. (S2 Ep6b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 18:15:00" d="2020-11-04 18:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fancy Nancy Clancy has adventures with family and friends, as she finds the extraordinary in the ordinary, and – with a little imagination- transforms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 18:30:00" d="2020-11-04 19:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Vampirina decides to run for class president. Poppy wants a pet bunny, but first she has to show her mum she's ready to have a pet by looking after Wolfie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 19:00:00" d="2020-11-04 19:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (83)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks are enticed by a fake An Yu to break all the rules, and have a party on Mystery Mountain. An Yu tries to domesticate the wild Wolfies!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 19:30:00" d="2020-11-04 20:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% The Pride Landers panic when Scar appears in the flames that destroy Mizimu Grove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 20:00:00" d="2020-11-04 20:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% During a visit to Merlin the Magician's tower, Cedric’s no-boundaries niece makes off with Merlin's magical staff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 20:25:00" d="2020-11-04 20:30:00"><n u="Fancy It Yourself Shorts">Fancy It Yourself Shorts I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy teaches her Dad how to wear a boa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 20:30:00" d="2020-11-04 21:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia visits Mystic Meadows, a retirement home for sorcerers. Can she help Cedric reconcile with his father so the old wizard will hand down the powerful family wand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 21:00:00" d="2020-11-04 21:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo’s plans to stay up late are derailed when Muffin misses her nap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 21:10:00" d="2020-11-04 21:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey needs to stay focused and not get distracted, during a family game of hide and seek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 21:20:00" d="2020-11-04 21:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey needs Mum's advice when her couch-cushion playhouse has noisy neighbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 21:30:00" d="2020-11-04 21:45:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (90)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hot Dog! Get mixed-up with Mickey and all of his pals in his new house in Hot Dog Hills! Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie, Daisy, Pluto and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 21:45:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (89)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hot Dog! Get mixed-up with Mickey and all of his pals in his new house in Hot Dog Hills! Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie, Daisy, Pluto and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 22:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fancy Nancy Clancy has adventures as she finds the extraordinary in the ordinary, and transforms the plain into the exquisite. (S2 Ep6b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 22:15:00" d="2020-11-04 22:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fancy Nancy Clancy has adventures with family and friends, as she finds the extraordinary in the ordinary, and – with a little imagination- transforms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 22:30:00" d="2020-11-04 23:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Vampirina decides to run for class president. Poppy wants a pet bunny, but first she has to show her mum she's ready to have a pet by looking after Wolfie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 23:00:00" d="2020-11-04 23:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (83)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks are enticed by a fake An Yu to break all the rules, and have a party on Mystery Mountain. An Yu tries to domesticate the wild Wolfies!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-04 23:30:00" d="2020-11-05 00:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% The Pride Landers panic when Scar appears in the flames that destroy Mizimu Grove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 00:00:00" d="2020-11-05 00:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% During a visit to Merlin the Magician's tower, Cedric’s no-boundaries niece makes off with Merlin's magical staff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 00:25:00" d="2020-11-05 00:30:00"><n u="Fancy It Yourself Shorts">Fancy It Yourself Shorts I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy teaches her Dad how to wear a boa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 00:30:00" d="2020-11-05 01:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu and Rocky must work together to save Tiny and Bill from Terminonator. Bill and Marsh are separated from their friends in a storm and must face their fears to get home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 01:00:00" d="2020-11-05 01:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo discovers P. J. Masks’ HQ’s secret rocket ship ability. Catboy learns appearances don’t matter as long as you save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 01:25:00" d="2020-11-05 01:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% When Romeo steals Owlette’s powers, he turns himself, Catboy, and Gekko into fliers. Night Ninja plans to turn Catboy's daytime parade into the Night Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 01:50:00" d="2020-11-05 02:00:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Both Olivia and Stan realize that Stan can’t keep a secret. Olivia offers to help her brother, and gives him advice. (S1 Ep3b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 02:00:00" d="2020-11-05 02:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou learns about making promises, and makes them to anyone who asks. He promises more than he can deliver, and ends up having to make a list of what he’s promised to do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 02:15:00" d="2020-11-05 02:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zinnia finds a caterpillar and mistakes it for a worm. She’s scared but Zou explains what it is and that it will turn into a beautiful butterfly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 02:30:00" d="2020-11-05 02:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry chases Daddo's birthday cake that’s caught on a balloon. Henry must save the monsterpets when they are swept into an airship on a windy day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 02:55:00" d="2020-11-05 03:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry searches Roarsville for Beckett when he runs off to play with Meg's monsterpet Shakey. Henry tries to teach his friends Gertie and Denzel to fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 03:20:00" d="2020-11-05 03:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan has promised to help his friends but gets stuck in a traffic jam with his pedal car. Olivia says she can replace him, and do everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 03:30:00" d="2020-11-05 03:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia invite Bigfoot to sleep over. But Stan is terrified of Bigfoot’s clown cuddly toy! Bigfoot won’t sleep without it, so the evening could be cancelled. (S1 Ep16c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 03:40:00" d="2020-11-05 03:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou’s team must have a mascot for an important football match but theirs becomes unusable. They think they won’t be able to compete until Poc comes to the rescue!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 03:55:00" d="2020-11-05 04:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and Grandpa have entered an orienteering competition but find they need to help Uncle Zavier and Zinnia, who win with their help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 04:10:00" d="2020-11-05 04:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou has to write an essay about My Ideal Day. He tries unsuccessfully to recreate it, but realises it’s his family who make it ideal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 04:25:00" d="2020-11-05 04:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia feel great, and they want to share their good mood with everyone else. But Podium is so grumpy - even the twins can’t do anything about it! (S1 Ep14a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 04:35:00" d="2020-11-05 04:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia want everyone to think they’re cute. (S1 Ep14b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-05 04:45:00" d="2020-11-05 05:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Hugglemonsters are having a roar-mazing snow day with the Enormomonsters. But things get competitive as the families start to compare sleds and cocoa recipes. ( S2 E23a)</k>  </p>
</a>
