<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="59" t="2020-10-24 04:33:14"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 05:00:00" d="2020-10-31 05:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Rip tries to gather feathers from Owlette's wings to let the Wolfies fly. Skeletons are stolen from the museum!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 05:25:00" d="2020-10-31 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks Music Video">PJ Masks Music Video I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The PJ Masks are on their way to save the day! Music accompanies clips from the popular show featuring pyjama-clad heroes Catboy, Gekko and Owlette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 05:30:00" d="2020-10-31 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Armadylan saves the city. Romeo tries to use Armadylan's powers to improve his lab</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 05:55:00" d="2020-10-31 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons III (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A cow that clucks and a chicken that moos? Something is obviously wrong. Minnie must find a way to switch their personalities back. Nobody wants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 06:00:00" d="2020-10-31 06:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Beshte befriends a gecko who wants to be a crocodile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 06:30:00" d="2020-10-31 07:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse III (83)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The friends board the Choo Choo and ride around collecting friends to play in the snow. They must pick up a mystery guest, and find it’s no other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 07:00:00" d="2020-10-31 07:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu and Rocky must work together to save Tiny and Bill from Terminonator. Bill and Marsh are separated from their friends in a storm and must face their fears to get home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 07:30:00" d="2020-10-31 08:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip the Penguin and Freddy the Flamingo are Junior Fliers at T.O.T.S., (the Tiny Ones Transport Service), where they’re tasked with delivering baby animals to their parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 08:00:00" d="2020-10-31 08:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Not wanting to go to bed, Bluey tries to dream about being a nocturnal fruit bat so she can stay up all night long and soon finds herself flying through the night sky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 08:10:00" d="2020-10-31 08:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad are going on an adventure with Bluey and Bingo as their backpacks!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 08:20:00" d="2020-10-31 08:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and their cousins make Dad and Uncle Stripe play a game of Horsey Ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 08:30:00" d="2020-10-31 08:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad gets embroiled in a game of Hotel, where Bluey and Bingo run a crazy hotel and Dad is the beleaguered guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 08:40:00" d="2020-10-31 08:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing Butterflies in the backyard is great fun, until Bluey runs away with Judo leaving Bingo all alone. Now poor Bingo’s heartbroken and Bluey needs to make amends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 08:50:00" d="2020-10-31 09:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With Bluey as his taxi driver, Dad’s got no chance of making it the airport on time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 09:00:00" d="2020-10-31 09:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's Mini-Mechanics Day and Mickey's number one fan can't wait to get to work! The Happy Helpers are busy pet-sitting while everyone heads to the Fancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 09:30:00" d="2020-10-31 10:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena of Avalor has saved her enchanted kingdom from an evil sorceress, and now must learn to rule Avalor with the help of her family and friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 10:00:00" d="2020-10-31 10:30:00"><n u="Rocketeer S1, The">Rocketeer S1, The I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Kit becomes a rocket-pack wearing superhero!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 10:30:00" d="2020-10-31 11:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJM have to protect all the kids from Luna Girl, Night Ninja and the Wolfy Kids who have got together to steal their goody bags</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 11:00:00" d="2020-10-31 12:00:00"><n>Mickey's Monster Musical</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey and pals are stranded near a spooky castle. They meet Count Mikula who looks like Mickey - except for his fangs and the fact that he can fly! He has a problem too. Can they help each other?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 12:00:00" d="2020-10-31 12:30:00"><n u="Rocketeer S1, The">Rocketeer S1, The I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Kit becomes a rocket-pack wearing superhero!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 12:30:00" d="2020-10-31 13:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Roadster Racers">Mickey Mouse Roadster Racers I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On Halloween Mickey meets the legendary Haunted Hot Rod. Can he beat him? Three real ghosts sabotage Pete’s Haunted House party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 13:00:00" d="2020-10-31 13:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Will a Halloween competition jeopardise the family's secret? Vee invents something which brings dead flowers to life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 13:30:00" d="2020-10-31 14:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pugs learn the pumpkin patch is a scary place at night. The pugs hunt for a local kid's lost Halloween costume</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 14:00:00" d="2020-10-31 14:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% The toys learn to be safe on Halloween and not wander off alone. Gustav’s head is stuck in the fence. Doc uses one of mum’s remedies to free him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 14:30:00" d="2020-10-31 15:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia must stop Lucinda’s good and evil friends from ruining her special witch ceremony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 15:00:00" d="2020-10-31 15:30:00"><n u="Muppet Babies">Muppet Babies I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>75% During Halloween, Fozzie can't help but be funny when he's supposed to be spooky! When Kermit won't try Miss Nanny's boo-berry pancakes, Summer tells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 15:30:00" d="2020-10-31 16:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% When tales of a mysterious creature plague the Pride Lands, the Guard must conquer their fears and track down the beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 16:00:00" d="2020-10-31 16:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At school, Bluey and her friends throw themselves into various games. Teacher Calypso keeps her charges on track with a wise word and a song - all except</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 16:10:00" d="2020-10-31 16:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo causes chaos at Bluey’s backyard zoo, when she sneaks into Daddy Gorilla’s cage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 16:20:00" d="2020-10-31 16:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In a game of Work, Bluey and Bingo are the latest hires at Dad’s drainpipe factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 16:30:00" d="2020-10-31 17:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bob is learning to yodel, The Pugs go to the Alps for tips. It’s Bob’s birthday and his sister Bonnie is acting sneaky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 17:00:00" d="2020-10-31 17:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy accidentally becomes Freddy’s new best friend when JoJo ditches him for her imaginary friend. Nancy decides to live on her own in the playhouse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 17:30:00" d="2020-10-31 18:30:00"><n>Mickey's Monster Musical</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey and pals are stranded near a spooky castle. They meet Count Mikula who looks like Mickey - except for his fangs and the fact that he can fly! He has a problem too. Can they help each other?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 18:30:00" d="2020-10-31 19:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% To escape a fire, Kiara, Tiifu, Zuri, Kion, and Bunga end up on an underground adventure through aardvark tunnels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 19:00:00" d="2020-10-31 19:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia and Clover stumble through a portal at the bottom of a silver tree and enter the magical, enchanted world of Elvenmoor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 19:30:00" d="2020-10-31 20:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% James is made King for the Day but gets carried away and ends up waking a sleeping baby giant. It teaches him that being in charge can be fun, but is a big responsibility</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 20:00:00" d="2020-10-31 20:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJM have to protect all the kids from Luna Girl, Night Ninja and the Wolfy Kids who have got together to steal their goody bags</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 20:30:00" d="2020-10-31 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The moths infiltrate HQ and Gekko won’t admit he let them in. Catboy wants to prove himself to be a brave Cat Explorer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 21:00:00" d="2020-10-31 21:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJs help Motsuki find Luna but miss a Night Ninja plot. The PJ Masks teach the Ninjalinos alternative skills when they lose their powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 21:30:00" d="2020-10-31 22:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu and her three besties map the stars. Tiny’s artistic skills are put to use when the dinos are lost in the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 22:00:00" d="2020-10-31 22:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny and Mazu treat Giganto's toothache. Every dino in Cretacia tries to claim a beautiful pebble!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 22:30:00" d="2020-10-31 23:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill wishes Giganto would go away forever after his coconut lunch is disrupted. Ayati sends the four friends off on a quest to find a legendary land call Dinosia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 23:00:00" d="2020-10-31 23:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill’s friends pretend he is invisible so he can win at hide-and-seek. Mazu invents eyeglasses to help near-sighted Patchy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-10-31 23:30:00" d="2020-11-01 00:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Rip tries to gather feathers from Owlette's wings to let the Wolfies fly. Skeletons are stolen from the museum!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 00:00:00" d="2020-11-01 00:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo steals Gekko’s voice, but Gekko’s not sure he wants it back before his poetry presentation. Night Ninja has stolen Master Fang’s prized sword!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 00:25:00" d="2020-11-01 00:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy has to get Amaya’s and Greg’s stolen superhero pyjamas back from Romeo! Owlette’s prized Giving Owl statue is stolen by Luna Girl to decorate her new headquarters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 00:50:00" d="2020-11-01 01:00:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia try to take good care of Puff’s silly hat, but they end up losing it. They realize that taking care of things isn’t always easy. (S1 Ep2a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 01:00:00" d="2020-11-01 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou wants to enter the art competition but can't decide what to do. Zak has made a sculpture, Zinnia a painting and Elzee a mosaic. In the end he combines all three!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 01:15:00" d="2020-11-01 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou’s family is planning a trip to the seaside - but it’s raining. So Zou decides to have the fun they might have had at the beach in the house instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 01:30:00" d="2020-11-01 01:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Instead of getting cross with young cousin Harry, Henry lets him help put on a Huggsgiving show. Summer loses the bow she wears when she dances. Can Henry find it?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 01:55:00" d="2020-11-01 02:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry is determined to win the Monsterpet Pageant, but things don’t quite work out that way. The family can’t wait for baby Ivor to take his first stomp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 02:20:00" d="2020-11-01 02:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>No hurdle’s too high for the Paprika twins Olivia and Stan as they turn everyday life into wonderful, colourful adventures!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 02:30:00" d="2020-11-01 02:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Olivia and Stan have an argument. (S1 Ep13c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 02:40:00" d="2020-11-01 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the sound system fails and it looks like the disco will have to be cancelled, Zou moves Nanna’s piano into the hall and the disco is a big success</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 02:55:00" d="2020-11-01 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and Zak help the family with chores which prove surprisingly helpful as training for a forthcoming beach volleyball game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 03:10:00" d="2020-11-01 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum has lost a beautiful powder compact Zou gave her. So he borrows a metal detector to see if he can find it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 03:25:00" d="2020-11-01 03:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins play &quot;Treasure Hunters&quot;, but it’s no fun without a baddy guarding the treasure. The problem is, no one wants to play the baddy (S1 Ep10a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 03:35:00" d="2020-11-01 03:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins can’t enter the park without a triple-scoop ice cream. The only place to find ice cream is Bigfoot’s, but Bigfoot needs everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-11-01 03:45:00" d="2020-11-01 05:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's Ivor's first birthday. Henry thinks they should have a huge party, then realises he is being selfish and doing what he wants, not what Ivor will like.(S2 E21a)</k>  </p>
</a>
