<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="124" t="2020-10-26 03:37:46"><p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 05:00:00" d="2020-11-02 05:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Thirst Quencher
Another heat wave: even the riverbed is dried up. One very thirsty Grizzy discovers that the Lemmings have used the last remaining bottles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 05:05:00" d="2020-11-02 05:15:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Spider Lemmings
The Lemmings have caught a little spider. Her sticky, elastic threads are absolutely perfect for bungee jumping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 05:15:00" d="2020-11-02 05:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Random Bear
Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over chocolate-spread jar lids, which they use as chips in a competition to win goodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 05:20:00" d="2020-11-02 05:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Lemming Interference
Grizzy has prepared himself a TV dinner to eat in front of his favorite series. But his moment of pleasure is abruptly interrupted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 05:25:00" d="2020-11-02 05:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% High Voltage Bear Attack
The Lemmings are having a rave party. When Grizzy throws their stereo into the river he sparks a general power outage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 05:35:00" d="2020-11-02 05:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Bear Scents
When he realises his beloved she-bear adores the smell of flowers, Grizzy decides to offer her the geraniums that decorate the window ledges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 05:40:00" d="2020-11-02 05:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Bear Luck
Decidedly, this is not Grizzy's day: after making a fool of himself in front of the she-bear he's in love with, he is ousted from the log cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 05:45:00" d="2020-11-02 05:50:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Magnetic Bear
Grizzy can't believe his eyes when he sees objects moving all by themselves. When he realises it's the Lemmings who are playing around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 05:50:00" d="2020-11-02 06:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Bear Charm
Further to a misunderstanding, Grizzy is persuaded that the she-bear he's in love with has been turned into a frog. While he looks through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 06:00:00" d="2020-11-02 06:20:00"><n u="Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?">Scooby-Doo and Guess Who? II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% A Fashion Nightmare!
When Scooby Doo and the gang are investigating a mysterious ghost at the Dergfall Boldman Department Store (a historic mecca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 06:20:00" d="2020-11-02 07:00:00"><n u="Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?">Scooby-Doo and Guess Who? I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Ollie Ollie In-Come Free!
When our mystery solving gang agrees to help Ricky Gervais with a haunted antique Egyptian statue of a cat they find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 07:00:00" d="2020-11-02 07:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>69% What a Pain
After a particularly destructive chase Tom and Spike have to go to the vet and Ginger hires an exterminator to take care of Jerry and Tuffy once and for all</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 07:10:00" d="2020-11-02 07:20:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>69% Hop to It!
Tom and Jerry have to go retrieve an ingredient for the witches' spell before sundown. Tom sees Princess Toodles and quickly forgets the mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 07:20:00" d="2020-11-02 07:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>69% For the Love of Ruggles
Tom impulsively kicks Spike's beloved chew toy Ruggles over the fence and has to go get it back when he sees how heartbroken Spike becomes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 07:30:00" d="2020-11-02 08:00:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>69% Sleuth or Consequences
Butch and a squirrel detective have set up shop across the street from Tom and Jerry and are stealing all their customers by using</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 08:00:00" d="2020-11-02 08:05:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Special Delivery
Mrs. Wicket demands that Bean stay in to take delivery of a new lounge chair. He is forced to dress up as Mrs. Wicket when Brian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 08:05:00" d="2020-11-02 08:15:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% A Dog's Life
Mr Bean dog-sits for Irma and while in the park comes across a professional dog-walker. This guy's making a fortune while Bean is doing it for free! That evening posters go up and the next morning Bean has four dogs to look after. But who is going to walk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 08:15:00" d="2020-11-02 08:35:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Big Stink
Mr Bean ends up in a farm slurry pit after racing a tractor. The car smells, Teddy smells, Bean smells … bad. He comes home, determined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 08:35:00" d="2020-11-02 08:41:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Birthday Bother
It's Irma's birthday. Bean buys a bargain-bin load of cards, and writes out two - one nice, one silly. He gets his envelopes mixed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 08:41:00" d="2020-11-02 08:42:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Meet the Shrink
The Docs are so obsessed with catching Lamput that even in their dreams, the chase goes on. It’s really not a restful sleep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 08:42:00" d="2020-11-02 09:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Invisible Necklace
You never can tell when inspiration’s gonna strike. Specs and Skinny are having a nice evening at the theatre, enjoying a magic show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 09:00:00" d="2020-11-02 09:10:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% There's Nothing Like a Good Book
Before they became big Looney Tunes stars they were the Baby Looney Tunes! Half the size and twice the amount of trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 09:10:00" d="2020-11-02 09:20:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% The Dolly Vanishes
On an overnight train trip to visit Floyd at college Lola's doll vanishes. Baby Bugs acts as a detective as he tries to solve the missing Edna mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 09:20:00" d="2020-11-02 09:25:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Without a Sound
Lola needs a good night’s sleep to be in shape for her class presentation the next day. Pat must make sure that nothing disturbs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 09:25:00" d="2020-11-02 09:35:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Voodoo
The Guanos discover a doll that looks like Pat and decide to turn it into a voodoo doll! They are going to order it to capture Hoodie while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 09:35:00" d="2020-11-02 10:00:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sit, Stand, Heel
For a pet talent contest, Victor shows off Tank’s talents as a dancer using a beat box. The Guanos, who realize that Hoodie is drawn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 10:00:00" d="2020-11-02 10:15:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Runaway Train
Kingdom Force must rescue Hoover and Professor Dunbit from a speeding train before it crashes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 10:15:00" d="2020-11-02 10:20:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Forecast: Chaos
Jabari accidentally sends a weather drone into overdrive, causing extreme weather shifts to endanger the Five Kingdoms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 10:20:00" d="2020-11-02 10:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>That Magnificent Mike!
It's Iris's birthday and Mike wants to surprise her with a special party. Balloons, gifts, Pinata - the works! Everything has been perfectly planned but the relentless raccoons decide to crash the party and steal all the candy. The racoons discover the h</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 10:25:00" d="2020-11-02 10:35:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mikeyzushi
While Mike prepares a special sushi dinner to win Iris's heart, the racoons break into the garage intent on creating some mischief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 10:35:00" d="2020-11-02 11:00:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sneezed To Meet You!
Mike has the perfect gift idea for Iris, flowers! The only snag is that Mike discovers he's horribly allergic and the raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 11:00:00" d="2020-11-02 11:10:00"><n u="PURST: Agent Binky">PURST: Agent Binky I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Snack Attack!
When Binky witnesses some aliens (ants) making off with fruit in the yard that belongs to Small Human, he leaps to his human’s aid, wrestles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 11:10:00" d="2020-11-02 11:20:00"><n u="PURST: Agent Binky">PURST: Agent Binky I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hit the Road, Roach!
When Captain Gracie’s PURST issue training whistle goes missing, Binky thinks he knows where it is. Unfortunately, it’s in Small</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 11:20:00" d="2020-11-02 12:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog: Santa Pat</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Guanos hijack Santa Claus’s sleigh and all the presents (including Lola’s) and let the reindeer escape. While Pat will do everything he can to recover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 12:00:00" d="2020-11-02 12:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 II (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Double Hex
While bird watching at Pinnacles National Park, Gwen and Ben get into a competition of who can spot more birds first, but once a forrest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 12:10:00" d="2020-11-02 12:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 II (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ye Olde Laser Duel
As Team Tennyson admires the efficiency of a super modern train station, Ben is quick to sniff out one of Steam Smythe's robots holding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 12:20:00" d="2020-11-02 12:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 II (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben Again and Again
After Billy Billions' efforts to carve his face onto Mount Rushmore with a laser are thwarted by Ben, the billionaire brat turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 12:30:00" d="2020-11-02 13:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 II (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>All Koiled Up
When Ben grows impatient with the snail-like pace of gardening, he goes O-E Overflow to pick up the pace and accidentally floods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 13:00:00" d="2020-11-02 13:20:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Trading Chases
Fred switches places with Jeff the tour guide at a history museum to give him a chance to lead the Gang in solving a mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 13:20:00" d="2020-11-02 14:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Kitchen Frightmare
Shaggy and Scooby's favourite chef is finally opening his own restaurant but a monstrous Yeti threatens the opening night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 14:00:00" d="2020-11-02 14:20:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Area 51 Adjacent
Daphne always dreamed of meeting extra-terrestrial life but that dream becomes a nightmare when the gang gets caught up in the mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 14:20:00" d="2020-11-02 15:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Grand Scam
Shaggy takes the gang to the Minor League Baseball stadium of his youth only to learn that it's about to be shut down because a Ghostly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 15:00:00" d="2020-11-02 15:20:00"><n u="Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?">Scooby-Doo and Guess Who? II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Scooby On Ice!
When Scooby Doo and the gang are in Austria for the International Ice Games they meet up with none other than famous Olympic Gold Medalist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 15:20:00" d="2020-11-02 16:00:00"><n u="Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?">Scooby-Doo and Guess Who? I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Cursed Cabinet of Professor Madds Markson!
When our mystery solving gang accepts the invitation to spend one night in the haunted Savannah Hotel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 16:00:00" d="2020-11-02 16:20:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Renn Scare
The gang heads to the Velma’s beloved authentic Renaissance Fair where they must find a way to infiltrate the royal feast in order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 16:20:00" d="2020-11-02 17:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% How to Train Your Coward
Shaggy and Scooby decide to leave the gang! But before that they insist on training the new recruits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 17:00:00" d="2020-11-02 17:10:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Looney Tunes Zoo (song)
Before they became big Looney Tunes stars they were the Baby Looney Tunes! Half the size and twice the amount of trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 17:10:00" d="2020-11-02 17:20:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Flush Hour
The babies learn the purpose of toilets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 17:20:00" d="2020-11-02 17:28:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Kung-fu Hamster
Inspired by a comic book he has seen, Pompom becomes a Kung-Fu master. Pat has to stop him before he destroys everything in sight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 17:28:00" d="2020-11-02 17:35:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Flying Page
While Lola is trying to get a peek at the last page of her father’s new comic book, it goes flying out the window. Pat tries everything to rescue it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 17:35:00" d="2020-11-02 18:00:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Ferret Sitter
So that he can steal Lola’s piggy bank, Marcus asks her if she can look after his ferret, who is actually Squizel in disguise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 18:00:00" d="2020-11-02 18:10:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fire on Wolf Mountain
While the Wolf and Bear communities argue over ownership of the new bridge that connects their two villages, Kingdom Force</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 18:10:00" d="2020-11-02 18:20:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Go with the Floe
Kingdom Force must save a family of bears from going Titanic after Jalopi sets them adrift on an ice floe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 18:20:00" d="2020-11-02 18:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>That Magnificent Mike!
It's Iris's birthday and Mike wants to surprise her with a special party. Balloons, gifts, Pinata - the works! Everything has been perfectly planned but the relentless raccoons decide to crash the party and steal all the candy. The racoons discover the h</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 18:25:00" d="2020-11-02 18:35:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mikeyzushi
While Mike prepares a special sushi dinner to win Iris's heart, the racoons break into the garage intent on creating some mischief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 18:35:00" d="2020-11-02 19:00:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sneezed To Meet You!
Mike has the perfect gift idea for Iris, flowers! The only snag is that Mike discovers he's horribly allergic and the raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 19:00:00" d="2020-11-02 19:10:00"><n u="PURST: Agent Binky">PURST: Agent Binky I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Moussie Mischief
When Ted lands in the laundry bin, with an alien (code name: fly) circling it, the team assume the alien’s evil plan is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 19:10:00" d="2020-11-02 19:20:00"><n u="PURST: Agent Binky">PURST: Agent Binky I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Who's the Wurst?
When Small Human rescues a Budgie Bird he thinks he's found a great new pet and the PURST Team think they've found a great new member</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 19:20:00" d="2020-11-02 20:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog: Santa Pat</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Guanos hijack Santa Claus’s sleigh and all the presents (including Lola’s) and let the reindeer escape. While Pat will do everything he can to recover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 20:00:00" d="2020-11-02 20:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bed Bean
Mr. Bean breaks his bed using it as a trampoline. He tries to fix it, but he can't. Next morning, and after an awful night's sleep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 20:10:00" d="2020-11-02 20:20:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Spa Day
Mrs. Wicket demands that Bean drives her and Miss Wince to their booked spa retreat; and wait outside in the car until they're done</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 20:20:00" d="2020-11-02 20:30:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Charity Bean
Bean is both cajoled by Irma and spurred by his own jealousy of the fund-raising super-star Declan into raising money for the local donkey sanctuary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 20:30:00" d="2020-11-02 21:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bean Encore
The Great Eduardo, violinist supreme, is in town and Irma wants to go to the concert. But Bean won't pay for the tickets. More than that</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 21:00:00" d="2020-11-02 21:05:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Cold Medal Wabbit
Cal attempts to win gold in every Winter Olympic event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 21:05:00" d="2020-11-02 21:10:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% No Duck is an Island
Tad Tucker is filming the last stages of his reality show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 21:10:00" d="2020-11-02 21:15:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% My Kingdom for a Duck
Egotistical actor Elmer Fudd is doing his one man show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 21:15:00" d="2020-11-02 21:20:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Finders Keepers Losers Sweepers
Bugs accidentally buys an enchanted broom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 21:20:00" d="2020-11-02 21:25:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Daffy Crockpot
Daffy Duck tries to help Settler Porky Pig fight Sam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 21:25:00" d="2020-11-02 21:30:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Fashion Viktor
Bugs seeks revenge on Viktor the male model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 21:30:00" d="2020-11-02 21:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Sam the Roughrider
Roughrider Yosemite Sam seeks glory in battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 21:35:00" d="2020-11-02 21:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Fool's Gold
Daffy Ducks decides to help out Red Omaha mine for gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 21:40:00" d="2020-11-02 22:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Bonjour DarkBat
Darkbat seeks vengeance against Blacque Jacque Shellacque</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 22:00:00" d="2020-11-02 22:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Super Grizzy Bros
By chance, Grizzy discovers the pleasures of video games on the ranger's console. The Lemmings want to try their hand at the joystick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 22:05:00" d="2020-11-02 22:15:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Fake Brother
Grizzy builds a look-alike robot to keep the Lemmings away while he prepares a popcorn party for his beloved she-bear. But his double's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 22:15:00" d="2020-11-02 22:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Mind in a Whirl
When she is accidentally hit over the head, Grizzy's beloved she-bear thinks she's a Lemming. Grizzy thinks that another little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 22:20:00" d="2020-11-02 22:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% A Sizeable Problem
When a meteorite falls not far from the log cabin, strange berries start to grow. One of their properties is that they make any animal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 22:25:00" d="2020-11-02 22:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Treasure Bear
Under the wood floor of the log cabin, Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the entrance to an underground gallery with an old treasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 22:35:00" d="2020-11-02 22:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% In the Service of His Majesty
When he brandishes an enchanted sceptre that the Lemmings brought home with other antique objects, Grizzy sees the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 22:40:00" d="2020-11-02 23:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Bear Art
Grizzy tries to impress the she-bear that he's in love with by making a sculpture of her from a piece of wood. But as soon as the artist's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 23:00:00" d="2020-11-02 23:10:00"><n u="My Knight and Me">My Knight and Me I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Fashion Victims
When the entire realm is blindly selling out and wearing Wilfried’s BWK (“Bright White Knight”) line of clothing Jimmy refuses determined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 23:10:00" d="2020-11-02 23:20:00"><n u="My Knight and Me">My Knight and Me I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Attack Of The 50ft Squire
When Jimmy finds he’s too small to complete a squire competition in gym class he sneaks a swig of Perlin's magic growing potion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 23:20:00" d="2020-11-02 23:30:00"><n u="My Knight and Me">My Knight and Me I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% The Helmet Of Epic
Jimmy gets a helmet that will make him a fearless super-warrior (and impress his dad) but the gear turns out to be a cursed “baddie magnet”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-02 23:30:00" d="2020-11-03 00:00:00"><n u="My Knight and Me">My Knight and Me I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% The Challenge
After a foolhardy challenge causes Jimmy and Lance to be captured by Bad Jack Henri and Wilfried must team up to save their squires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 00:00:00" d="2020-11-03 00:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Flea Party
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 00:05:00" d="2020-11-03 00:15:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Guard Dog
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing – unlike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 00:15:00" d="2020-11-03 00:20:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Cat's Pajamas
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 00:20:00" d="2020-11-03 00:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Happy Home
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing – unlike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 00:25:00" d="2020-11-03 00:35:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Buried Treasure
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 00:35:00" d="2020-11-03 00:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fortune 500
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 00:40:00" d="2020-11-03 00:50:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jitter Fever
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing – unlike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 00:50:00" d="2020-11-03 00:55:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Recall
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing – unlike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 00:55:00" d="2020-11-03 01:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>New Leaf Taffy
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 01:00:00" d="2020-11-03 01:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Bear's Best Friend
Grizzy discovers a baby raccoon not far from the log cabin. When he sees its big, moist eyes, Grizzy melts and adopts the creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 01:05:00" d="2020-11-03 01:15:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Super Grizzy Bros
By chance, Grizzy discovers the pleasures of video games on the ranger's console. The Lemmings want to try their hand at the joystick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 01:15:00" d="2020-11-03 01:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Fake Brother
Grizzy builds a look-alike robot to keep the Lemmings away while he prepares a popcorn party for his beloved she-bear. But his double's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 01:20:00" d="2020-11-03 01:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Mind in a Whirl
When she is accidentally hit over the head, Grizzy's beloved she-bear thinks she's a Lemming. Grizzy thinks that another little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 01:25:00" d="2020-11-03 01:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% A Sizeable Problem
When a meteorite falls not far from the log cabin, strange berries start to grow. One of their properties is that they make any animal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 01:35:00" d="2020-11-03 01:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Treasure Bear
Under the wood floor of the log cabin, Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the entrance to an underground gallery with an old treasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 01:40:00" d="2020-11-03 01:50:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% In the Service of His Majesty
When he brandishes an enchanted sceptre that the Lemmings brought home with other antique objects, Grizzy sees the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 01:50:00" d="2020-11-03 01:55:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Bear Art
Grizzy tries to impress the she-bear that he's in love with by making a sculpture of her from a piece of wood. But as soon as the artist's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 01:55:00" d="2020-11-03 02:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Happy Birthday Lemmings!
The Lemmings throw a surprise birthday party for one of the clan. When &quot;Happy Birthday&quot; rings out, the &quot;surpriiiiiise&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 02:00:00" d="2020-11-03 02:05:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sit, Stand, Heel
For a pet talent contest, Victor shows off Tank’s talents as a dancer using a beat box. The Guanos, who realize that Hoodie is drawn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 02:05:00" d="2020-11-03 02:15:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Kung-fu Hamster
Inspired by a comic book he has seen, Pompom becomes a Kung-Fu master. Pat has to stop him before he destroys everything in sight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 02:15:00" d="2020-11-03 02:20:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Flying Page
While Lola is trying to get a peek at the last page of her father’s new comic book, it goes flying out the window. Pat tries everything to rescue it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 02:20:00" d="2020-11-03 02:25:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Ferret Sitter
So that he can steal Lola’s piggy bank, Marcus asks her if she can look after his ferret, who is actually Squizel in disguise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 02:25:00" d="2020-11-03 02:35:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Automated House
The Guanos steal the TV remote control, thus locking Lola and Pat outside (where they ran to get it). Coast is clear to kidnap Hoodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 02:35:00" d="2020-11-03 02:40:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tank Gets Amnesia
Victor asks Lola to look after Tank for the day. Because of the Guanos, Tank runs headfirst into a cabinet and the impact totally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 02:40:00" d="2020-11-03 02:45:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Guano Scooter
Lola helps Hugo learn how to ride a scooter. But the Guanos, drawn to the horn in the shape of a pigeon, and that they think is real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 02:45:00" d="2020-11-03 02:55:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Reducing Your Pawprint
Lola is going to be interviewed following a class presentation she did on recycling. While she is getting ready for it, the Guanos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 02:55:00" d="2020-11-03 03:00:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Frienship Letter
The friendly letter from Lucie addressed to Lola gets carried away in the wind. Pat will bend over backwards to get</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 03:00:00" d="2020-11-03 03:10:00"><n u="My Knight and Me">My Knight and Me I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% The Stinky Swamp Witch
When Jimmy and Cat find a witch’s broom they can’t resist taking it for a spin for fun. But the fun quickly ends when their joyride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 03:10:00" d="2020-11-03 03:20:00"><n u="My Knight and Me">My Knight and Me I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% The Harvest Festival
Epic the Queen asks Henri to compose a song to lift the spirits of her beloved subjects for this year’s Harvest Festival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 03:20:00" d="2020-11-03 03:30:00"><n u="My Knight and Me">My Knight and Me I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Treasure Trap
As Henri and Bad Jack go head-to-head in a race to find an extremely rare treasure Jimmy lies to Bjorn and then has to try to repair their friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 03:30:00" d="2020-11-03 03:45:00"><n u="My Knight and Me">My Knight and Me I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Guess Who's Coming For Dinner
Heart of gold Henri and Jimmy host the bad Witch who has been kicked out of her house by her sister Stinky Swamp Witch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 03:45:00" d="2020-11-03 04:00:00"><n u="My Knight and Me">My Knight and Me I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Fearless Colbert
When Jimmy and Cat discover Colbert never completed his officiant exam he has to go on a field mission with Henri to keep his job while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 04:00:00" d="2020-11-03 04:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Flea Party
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 04:05:00" d="2020-11-03 04:15:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Guard Dog
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing – unlike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 04:15:00" d="2020-11-03 04:20:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Cat's Pajamas
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 04:20:00" d="2020-11-03 04:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Happy Home
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing – unlike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 04:25:00" d="2020-11-03 04:35:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Buried Treasure
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 04:35:00" d="2020-11-03 04:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fortune 500
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 04:40:00" d="2020-11-03 04:50:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jitter Fever
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing – unlike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 04:50:00" d="2020-11-03 04:55:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Recall
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing – unlike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-11-03 04:55:00" d="2020-11-03 05:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>New Leaf Taffy
Welcome to Muchmore Manor, home of uber-rich senior Mrs Muchmore and her beloved dog with a red bow, Bentley. They want for nothing</k>  </p>
</a>
