<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2020-10-26 03:40:24"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 05:00:00" d="2020-11-02 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - AUSTRALIA: A THIRSTY CONTINENT</n><t>D</t>    <k>Climate change is no longer a theory. The effects of global warming on the earth are now clearly visible. Over the last few years, they have been having</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 06:00:00" d="2020-11-02 07:00:00"><n>SEYCHELLES - TRIP TO PARADISE</n><t>D</t>    <k>White beaches, blue water and wonderful silence, the Seychelles are the garden eden. Consisting out of more than 100 isles, &quot;Seychelles - Trip to Paradise&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 07:00:00" d="2020-11-02 08:00:00"><n>LET'S ALL GO TO THE SEA - OKINAWA ISLAND, JAPAN, CENTENARIANS’ ISLAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>Coastlines and seafronts are the gateways to the oceans, a source of many and varied natural resources. It’s easy to understand why half of the world’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 08:00:00" d="2020-11-02 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - HADZA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra and his team embark on a journey through the forests of Tanzania in search of one of the last wild tribes that inhabit the world:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 09:00:00" d="2020-11-02 10:00:00"><n>VACACIONES CON FIDEL</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tristan is a journalist with deep political convictions who worked for years doing journalistic research. Once married and with three children, he accepts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 10:00:00" d="2020-11-02 11:00:00"><n>NOMADS - WHITEWATER KAYAKING IN NEW ZEALAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>An international team kayaks the classic runs of New Zealand’s south island and in turn they find a new adventure around every bend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 11:00:00" d="2020-11-02 11:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Our sim series continues as we meet Jessica Cox, a pilot born without arms, to see if she can land an airliner with her feet! ENGINE FAILURE: Anthony tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 11:30:00" d="2020-11-02 12:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>L-39 ALBATROSS: Fasten your seat belts as we go flying in the most prolific fighter jet trainer of the Soviet era. UPSET RECOVERY: In the most extreme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 12:00:00" d="2020-11-02 12:30:00"><n u="GARONGA SAFARI -">GARONGA SAFARI - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this chapter René will visit with his teammates the &quot;Center of Reptiles&quot;. One of the instructors will tell us a terrible experience of a student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 12:30:00" d="2020-11-02 13:00:00"><n u="GARONGA SAFARI -">GARONGA SAFARI - (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Garonga Safari is a fun and educational show that showcases the African wilderness and the efforts to preserve it. Learn about the importance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 13:00:00" d="2020-11-02 14:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF THE SEA - MARES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Power of the Sea is a documentary series that reveals the special features of each one of the wonderful seas of Chile, generating conscience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 14:00:00" d="2020-11-02 15:00:00"><n>POSTCARD PERFECT - NEW CALEDONIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The island has numerous attributes, but it also possesses one of the most important nickel deposits in the world, which creates significant environmental problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 15:00:00" d="2020-11-02 16:00:00"><n u="RACE TO MARS -">RACE TO MARS - (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Based on contemporary, international research being done at space agencies and in laboratories. Race To Mars imagines the first human voyage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 16:00:00" d="2020-11-02 17:00:00"><n>TRIBES OF THE HIMALAYAS - HIMALAYAS, THE LOST VALLEYS OF PALDAR</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Himalayas are more than a playground for trekkers or the landmark of the most memorable climbing achievements. Hard to reach valleys, such as Ladakh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 17:00:00" d="2020-11-02 18:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 18:00:00" d="2020-11-02 19:00:00"><n u="MISSION EXPLORATION: MEGALOPOLIS -">MISSION EXPLORATION: MEGALOPOLIS - (14)</n><t>D</t>    <k>As millions more people join the exodus from the countryside seeking a living in the big city, Alexandra Leroux, host of the series, investigates how these</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 19:00:00" d="2020-11-02 20:00:00"><n u="THE SPECIES RETURN -">THE SPECIES RETURN - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>With a little helping hand, Mother Nature possesses magnificent vital energy. It is up to us to understand that energy. This series examine various species</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 20:00:00" d="2020-11-02 22:00:00"><n>EMPIRE OF THE MID-SOUTH</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Empire of mid-South&quot; is a remarkable film with rare archive footage of the first steps of the colonisation of French Indochina to the fall of Saigon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 22:00:00" d="2020-11-02 22:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF MEXICO - THE NORTH</n><t>D</t>    <k>Charlie journeys to the borderlands of Baja California where he visits the oldest winery in Mexico, swims with sea lions in the Gulf of Cortez</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 22:30:00" d="2020-11-02 23:00:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - IN THE KINGDOM OF SHARKS - PART">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - IN THE KINGDOM OF SHARKS - PART 2 (CUBA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this incredible eco-system of mangroves, reefs and sandy sea beds of the labyrinth of small islands and channels that make up the archipelago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-02 23:00:00" d="2020-11-03 00:00:00"><n>BEAUTIFUL MINDS - NIBALDO INESTROSA PHD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Albert Einstein said that the mind is like a parachute: it only works if we have it opened. Beautiful Minds is a documentary series that summarizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-03 00:00:00" d="2020-11-03 00:30:00"><n>KITCHEN RUSH - SWITZERLAND - RESTAURANTS WOODS INTERCONTINENTAL &amp; LE LEXIQUE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A journey to some of the best restaurants around the globe. We're going to try everything from sushi to steak tartare. Surprise some of the great Chefs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-03 00:30:00" d="2020-11-03 01:00:00"><n>KITCHEN RUSH - SWITZERLAND - ZURICH</n><t>D</t>    <k>A journey to some of the best restaurants around the globe. We're going to try everything from sushi to steak tartare. Surprise some of the great Chefs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-03 01:00:00" d="2020-11-03 02:00:00"><n>CAMEROON, ON THE WAY TO SCHOOL</n><t>D</t>    <k>More than 66 million school-aged girls do not attend primary nor secondary school worldwide. In the Briqueterie, a disadvantaged district of Cameroon's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-03 02:00:00" d="2020-11-03 03:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE - CIUDAD VARANASI</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-03 03:00:00" d="2020-11-03 03:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - IV (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Float Planes: An introduction to the world of seaplanes. Buying an Aircraft: Ever wondered how to actually buy an airplane? Aircraft Boneyard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-03 03:30:00" d="2020-11-03 04:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - IV (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Civil Air Patrol: We participate in a search and rescue exercise with the CAP members and cadets. AWACS: We take an exclusive inside look at the eye’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-03 04:00:00" d="2020-11-03 04:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - NEW YORK</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-11-03 04:30:00" d="2020-11-03 05:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - NICE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
</a>
