<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="51" t="2020-10-28 03:54:15"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 05:23:00" d="2020-11-04 05:40:00"><n>Connections: Leah &amp; Mal</n>    <k>Connections, celebrates all that?s great about porn for women: passion, laughter, teasing, giving, receiving, &amp; experiencing real pleasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 05:40:00" d="2020-11-04 06:06:00"><n>Making Ends Meet: Mercedes Carrera &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>A suburbian family is in destress over money, but sex seems to really heal the wounds. Scorching hot sex and sharp comedy blend perfectly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 06:06:00" d="2020-11-04 06:19:00"><n>Power Pussy</n><t>S</t>    <k>Two Power Pussies take on and dominate the burly Dean Van Damme, all in From Dawn Til Dawn style. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 06:19:00" d="2020-11-04 06:40:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Marc Rose &amp; Sicilia</n>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. A naughty female friendly porn scene by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 06:40:00" d="2020-11-04 07:08:00"><n>Tenderness: Ria Sunn &amp; Jayden Cox</n>    <k>A erotic massage scene by Dusk TV's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Romantic porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 07:08:00" d="2020-11-04 07:40:00"><n>Home Coming: Home for Diner</n>    <k>Oh, home sweet home. These couples experience that there's no place like home to come back to, especially since orgasms are awaiting them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 07:40:00" d="2020-11-04 08:17:00"><n>The Stepmother 8: Kendra Lust &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Billy and Julia are getting close to marriage, but each have a single parent who?s loneliness is ruining their peace. But the real problem arises when Billy can?t stop thinking about Julia?s gorgeous mother, Theresa. Will Theresa settle for quiet companionship, or will she succumb to lust for the vibrant young man. A Sweet Sinner?s daring look into forbidden passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 08:17:00" d="2020-11-04 08:49:00"><n>Love is in the Air: Chanel Preston &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>When her fiance gets sucked into never-ending conversation at a friend's party, a woman lures him to the bedroom for a passionate sexual encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 08:49:00" d="2020-11-04 09:25:00"><n>In The Limelight 1: Rita &amp; Leony April</n><t>L</t>    <k>Daring! Pure?s film ?In the Limelight? shows a romantic lesbian sex scene. The most beautiful women surpass your wildest dreams to fulfill their sexual desires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 09:25:00" d="2020-11-04 09:49:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: India Summer &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 09:49:00" d="2020-11-04 10:10:00"><n>Ball Control: Sienna Day &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one woman on this pitch with all the power. Physio Eva puts her massage skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 10:10:00" d="2020-11-04 10:29:00"><n>If the Apocalypse Comes, Fuck Me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maria Riot is lost and thirsty in an apocalyptical world. Luke seems to be the only man alive. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 10:29:00" d="2020-11-04 10:59:00"><n>Hot Water: Francys Belle &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>Licking, sucking, kissing, thrusting, touching, stroking, becoming one with each other in hot water. A sexual and visual delight by Studio Sinfull</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 10:59:00" d="2020-11-04 11:19:00"><n>Corporate Bonding: Tamara Grace &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>Good teamwork can lead to surprising situations. Rookie lawyer Leyla organises a team-building weekend by the beach for her and her firm of London lawyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 11:19:00" d="2020-11-04 11:47:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Anabelle &amp; Adam Black</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it take to have that fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media show you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 11:47:00" d="2020-11-04 12:07:00"><n u="Ages of Sex: Sex at">Ages of Sex: Sex at (40)</n>    <k>The Ages of Sex is a porn for women film by Thagson. 4 Well known directors will direct a short which represents a woman?s sexual reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 12:07:00" d="2020-11-04 12:22:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Ella Nova &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 12:22:00" d="2020-11-04 12:47:00"><n>Very Beautiful Lips</n><t>L</t>    <k>Starting with a shower, performers Apolonia Lapiedra and Alberto Blanco waste no time in exploring their lust for one another. As they move</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 12:47:00" d="2020-11-04 13:04:00"><n>Exposure: Security Measures</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 13:04:00" d="2020-11-04 13:45:00"><n>Hot Water: Vanessa Decker &amp; Ricky Rascal</n>    <k>Licking, sucking, kissing, thrusting, touching, stroking, becoming one with each other in hot water. A sexual and visual delight by Studio Sinfull</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 13:45:00" d="2020-11-04 14:37:00"><n>An Arabian Night</n><t>L</t>    <k>Always wanted to know about anal sex, but never tried? This porn for women film shows how nice anal massage can be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 14:37:00" d="2020-11-04 14:54:00"><n>I found your mother on tinder</n><t>S</t>    <k>The legendary Mrs. Robinson brought to life by the most modern of dating apps. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 14:54:00" d="2020-11-04 15:18:00"><n>Girl Next Door Likes It Dirty: Dillion Harper &amp; Ryan McClane</n>    <k>All of these next door girls are young, free, and secretly wild who love it dirty! They all get their pussies passionately pulverized over the course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 15:18:00" d="2020-11-04 15:38:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Ana Marco &amp; Fenix Santos</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first porn for women film as director for Thagson with a vibrant story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 15:38:00" d="2020-11-04 15:59:00"><n>Passion Noir: Lexi &amp; Jason</n>    <k>A fantastic new female friendly porn film from Roma Amor for Sinful XXX. The naked body as an art form and sex as a masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 15:59:00" d="2020-11-04 16:17:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Jess West &amp; Danielle Ashlea Maye</n><t>L</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She shows a pretty young teacher how to get closer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 16:17:00" d="2020-11-04 16:42:00"><n>Beautiful Young Couples: Jessica Malone &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A erotic scene from Beautiful Young</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 16:42:00" d="2020-11-04 17:15:00"><n>Silver Shoes: Undressed</n>    <k>This award-winning explicit erotic trilogy from Jennifer Lyon Bell intertwines three short female friendly porn stories about the carnal power of what we wear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 17:15:00" d="2020-11-04 17:39:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: Aaliyah Love &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 17:39:00" d="2020-11-04 18:07:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 8: Karla Kush &amp; Daniel Hunter</n>    <k>When she gets caught in a compromising position with her professor, Sandi escapes with her boyfriend to her artistic free-spirit mother, Moon-Rose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 18:07:00" d="2020-11-04 18:23:00"><n>Memory Files of You</n><t>S</t>    <k>A deeply moving ode to loves lost, and irrevocable, unobtainable desires through Virtual Reality. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 18:23:00" d="2020-11-04 18:56:00"><n>Remy's Angels: Lexi Belle, Remy LaCroix &amp; Dani Daniels</n>    <k>Watch the beautiful brunette Remy Lacroix explore her inner desires with some of her closest girlfriends in this all girl sexual adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 18:56:00" d="2020-11-04 19:18:00"><n>Inside: Kali Sudhra &amp; Miguel Zayas</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 19:18:00" d="2020-11-04 19:51:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Bella Jordan &amp; Fernando</n>    <k>A scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 19:51:00" d="2020-11-04 20:13:00"><n>Make Me Sweat: Matt &amp; Blanche</n>    <k>Matt &amp; Blanche's beautiful bodies are the centerpiece of this incredibly hot erotic scene by Sinful XXX. Super sexy female friendly porn with super sexy performers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 20:13:00" d="2020-11-04 20:32:00"><n>Heavy Contact</n>    <k>That feeling when you have a lot of contact with someone and the connection gets even heavier when you meet in real life? Yes, that's passion to the max</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 20:32:00" d="2020-11-04 20:44:00"><n>A Feminist Man</n><t>S</t>    <k>Is there anything sexier than a man who can give perfect cunnilingus and have a conversation about Judith Butler? From the XConfessions series by Erika</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 20:44:00" d="2020-11-04 21:14:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies: Dolce Vita &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. A romantic porn video from Favorite Fantasies by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 21:14:00" d="2020-11-04 21:40:00"><n>Sex in white: Erica Fontes &amp; Miquel Zayas</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us with her ?Sex In White? productions, where sexual encounters take place in a pure and white scenery, so the main focus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 21:40:00" d="2020-11-04 22:05:00"><n>Obedience</n>    <k>On a beautiful day a Spanish beauty gets a surprise phone call from a stranger. A man tells her exactly what to do to pleasure herself sexually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 22:05:00" d="2020-11-04 23:51:00"><n u="Trouble">Trouble X (2)</n>    <k>On his first day back in the dating game, Nick meets not one but TWO beautiful women. Olivia (Abigail Mac) is hot, sexy, and confident. Jenny (Cherie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 23:51:00" d="2020-11-05 01:46:00"><n>The Thief of Hearts</n>    <k>Three days. A lemonade stand. Angry, sexy roommates and a cheating girlfriend. All totally manageable for millennial Katie. When she steals a truck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 01:46:00" d="2020-11-05 02:08:00"><n>Elevator Dreams</n>    <k>When a guy meets an attractive girl in an elevator, she ignores him. But in his dreams all she want to do is having kinky, rough sex. A female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 02:08:00" d="2020-11-05 02:30:00"><n>Tease: Tyler Nixon &amp; Stella Cox</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Naught porn for women by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 02:30:00" d="2020-11-05 02:57:00"><n>I Love You: Blanche Bradburry &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A erotic porn film by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 02:57:00" d="2020-11-05 03:20:00"><n>Facade: Layla Price &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 03:20:00" d="2020-11-05 03:51:00"><n>Surreal Encounters: Aaron Rock &amp; Stacy Cruz</n>    <k>All Space &amp;Time Is Lost When Mysterious Lovers Meet. First there seems to be someone behind the mirror, then he's gone. Stacy looks closer and steps into an erotic dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 03:51:00" d="2020-11-05 04:23:00"><n>Swing with me: Ava dalush, Logan Pierce &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Four segments on the sexual fantasies of husbands and wives. Siri let's her husband listen to her sexual exploits at work, Romi has sex with her co-worker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 04:23:00" d="2020-11-05 04:40:00"><n>Momentum 1: Backseat lovers</n>    <k>Australian film maker Michelle Flynn has the most distinctive style within the alternative porn genre. Her debut film Momentum is a cinematic intimacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 04:40:00" d="2020-11-05 04:56:00" c="1"><n>The Possession Of Mrs Hyde: Avi Love &amp; Ramon Nomar</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Possession of Mrs. Hyde is Axel Braun's first non-parody feature in 15 years and his most ambitious movie to date. Shot entirely in Black and White</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 04:56:00" d="2020-11-05 05:25:00"><n>I'm Obsessed with Owen Gray</n><t>S</t>    <k>What would happen if your first time having sex on screen was with a pornstar you were totally obsessed with? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
</a>
