<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="62" t="2020-10-23 04:51:38"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 05:40:00" d="2020-10-30 06:02:00"><n>Upon Further Reflection: Avi Love &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>Fiction writer, James Wharton (Ryan Mclane), is suffering from writers block and a drinking problem. His ex-wife is making his life a living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 06:02:00" d="2020-10-30 06:14:00"><n>Obsessed</n>    <k>A scene from Xconfessions by Erika Lust. In this porn for women movie she films the 'sneaky' fantasies of her fans. Have you ever fantasized about a former lover?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 06:14:00" d="2020-10-30 06:37:00"><n>Positions: Second</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 06:37:00" d="2020-10-30 07:02:00"><n>Love Me Forever: Lily Cat &amp; Vega</n><t>L</t>    <k>Romantic, passionate love. These couples show each other how much they enjoy each others company. A romantic porn video by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 07:02:00" d="2020-10-30 07:25:00"><n>While You're Sleeping</n><t>L</t>    <k>A man secretly watches porn when he thinks his wife is asleep. But she know?s what he is doing and shows him that he doesn?t have to watch tv when he wants good porn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 07:25:00" d="2020-10-30 07:38:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Bianca Breeze &amp; Jake Jace</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 07:38:00" d="2020-10-30 07:50:00"><n>Madmen Porn</n><t>S</t>    <k>Have you ever wondered what Don Draper's cock might be like? Find out in this fan fiction inspired short! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 07:50:00" d="2020-10-30 08:10:00"><n>The Temptation Of Eve: Remy Lacroix &amp; Xander Corvus</n>    <k>Thrust into an uncomfortable circumstance, Eve (Remy LaCroix) finds herself living under the same roof as Brandon (the man she shared the most intense</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 08:10:00" d="2020-10-30 08:31:00"><n>Perfect &amp; Pure 2: Katty West &amp; Joe T</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive, four sultry sirens kiss their lovers whilst soft hands caress strong backs, firm gluts and erect manhoods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 08:31:00" d="2020-10-30 08:51:00"><n>Fit: Samantha Bentley &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 08:51:00" d="2020-10-30 09:14:00"><n>Sex is for Lovers: Denise &amp; Renato</n>    <k>Indulge yourself in female friendly porn with an emphasis on passion, lovers, and true romance. Their inspiration is not found in anonymous encounters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 09:14:00" d="2020-10-30 09:34:00"><n>Stair Love</n>    <k>Yet another cinematic Spanish female friendly porn scene from Verso Cinema featuring the super popular and multiply awarded Carolina Abril. Don't miss this encounter!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 09:34:00" d="2020-10-30 09:48:00"><n>The Fantasy Project: Kara &amp; Devon</n>    <k>Massage is the ultimate sensation of touch and the complete focus on you, your body and your pleasure. Your pleasure only. A true female friendly porn video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 09:48:00" d="2020-10-30 10:03:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Charlotte Cross &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 10:03:00" d="2020-10-30 10:30:00"><n>Multiorgasmic Brunch</n><t>S</t>    <k>An explosive exploration of the possibilities for female pleasure; where the orgasms just never end. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 10:30:00" d="2020-10-30 10:55:00"><n>Inside: Julia Roca &amp; Anneke Necro</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 10:55:00" d="2020-10-30 11:22:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: Sweet</n>    <k>How sweet is your partner? A romantic sex film by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV's own porn for women label: &quot;Ooh la la&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 11:22:00" d="2020-10-30 11:52:00"><n>Sex Sinners and Saints: Jan Seidl &amp; Michaela Mangova</n>    <k>Not only is the church the perfect place to confess your sins, it's also the perfect location to have sensational sex. These couples sin in church, moaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 11:52:00" d="2020-10-30 12:21:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 6: Chloe Foster &amp; Steven St. Croix</n>    <k>Robbie dreaded meeting his girlfriend's mother, but when he finally does, he's taken back as how friendly, alluring and sensual she really is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 12:21:00" d="2020-10-30 12:45:00"><n>A Lesbian Romance: Shyla Jennings &amp; Mia Malkova</n>    <k>When feelings develop after a one-night-stand, Kenna puts her heart on the line and fights for the woman she wants. Penny's secret attraction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 12:45:00" d="2020-10-30 13:07:00"><n>First Summer Love 2: Sweet Cat &amp; Mark Archer</n><t>L</t>    <k>The temperature is not the only thing that rises. Love is in the air. The passion these couples show you is as warm as the sun - it's their &quot;first summer love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 13:07:00" d="2020-10-30 13:30:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: Karlee Grey &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 13:30:00" d="2020-10-30 13:52:00"><n>Housemates 3: Good Company</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 13:52:00" d="2020-10-30 14:06:00"><n>Latex Sessions</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parker Marx and Amarna Miller feature in this steamy homage to latex and the psychology of fetishism. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 14:06:00" d="2020-10-30 14:40:00"><n>Suspicious Minds: Steve Q &amp; Katy Rose</n>    <k>Max Deeds Is A Private Detective Caught In A World Of Suspicious Minds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 14:40:00" d="2020-10-30 15:00:00"><n>Tease: Ella Hughes &amp; Carly Rae</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. A lesbian porn scene by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 15:00:00" d="2020-10-30 15:26:00"><n>Intimate Moments: Leona &amp; Peter</n>    <k>Intimate moments for beautiful couples while exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Intimate Moments by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 15:26:00" d="2020-10-30 15:44:00"><n>Bad Sometimes: Erica Fontes, Angelo Ferro &amp; Emilio Ardana</n><t>L</t>    <k>After the acclaimed success of his first film, Lara Tinelli surprises us with a completely different and transgressive film while staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 15:44:00" d="2020-10-30 16:09:00"><n>Sex and Lies: Avi Love &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>In the world of the ultra-rich, sex and lies reign supreme. Alisa (Avi Love)is a personal assistant who craves nothing more than order; difficult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 16:09:00" d="2020-10-30 16:34:00"><n>Summer</n>    <k>What a better refreshment in the middle of a hot hazy and sticky summer day than playing with some ice in front of a breezy fan and having loads of good sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 16:34:00" d="2020-10-30 16:55:00"><n>Quartet: Tenderley</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 16:55:00" d="2020-10-30 17:25:00"><n>Blind Date Swingers Club: Ricky Raskal &amp; Nikky Dream</n>    <k>Everyone is getting their fuck on! Swinging couples going wild!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 17:25:00" d="2020-10-30 17:45:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 3: She</n>    <k>Apolonia Lapiedra is a beautiful Spanish pornstar who is a classic example of good girl gone bad. In this scene, a gorgeous Threesome, Apolonia, Emilio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 17:45:00" d="2020-10-30 18:04:00"><n>We Know You Are Watching</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: A sexy young couple in Brazil notice how interested their neighbor is in observing their naturist habits at home. In XConfessions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 18:04:00" d="2020-10-30 18:24:00"><n>Pure Milf 5: Johnny Castle &amp; Capri Cavanni</n><t>L</t>    <k>These pure MILFs always get what they want as you will see in these five tantalizing scenes. These sexy ladies show you the true meaning of seduction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 18:24:00" d="2020-10-30 18:34:00"><n>Diet Of Sex: The Beach</n>    <k>Diet of Sex is an experience, is a love story between Ágata and Marc told through sex. A culinary, sexual adventure through a variety of flavours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 18:34:00" d="2020-10-30 19:14:00"><n>Light my Fire: Daphne Klyde &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 19:14:00" d="2020-10-30 19:34:00"><n>Housemates 2: Luke Hotrod &amp; Samantha Bentley</n>    <k>New house. New rules. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 19:34:00" d="2020-10-30 19:59:00"><n>Cum Inside Me: Rebeccca &amp; Andrew</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 19:59:00" d="2020-10-30 20:24:00"><n>Momentum 1: Before dinner</n>    <k>Australian film maker Michelle Flynn has the most distinctive style within the alternative porn genre. Her debut film Momentum is a cinematic intimacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 20:24:00" d="2020-10-30 20:36:00"><n>Unbridled: Lyra Law &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>To save her family’s ranch, city girl Avery has to return to Texas and face her demons and her old flame horse trainer Grant. Stormy Daniels stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 20:36:00" d="2020-10-30 21:04:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 8: Ariana Grand &amp; Mark Davis</n>    <k>When she gets caught in a compromising position with her professor, Sandi escapes with her boyfriend to her artistic free-spirit mother, Moon-Rose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 21:04:00" d="2020-10-30 21:15:00"><n>Wine Is The Best Lubricant</n><t>S</t>    <k>A french wine lover walks into a wine shop looking for something to taste. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 21:15:00" d="2020-10-30 21:48:00"><n>Restraint 2: Ryan Driller &amp; Valentina Nappi</n>    <k>After placing an ad in search of a dominant man, Valentina finds herself blindfolded and restrained in the home of a mysterious stranger. Although Aria?s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 21:48:00" d="2020-10-30 22:11:00"><n>Pleasure Fix: Kali Sudhra, Bishop Black &amp; Nat Portnoy</n>    <k>Sex can be hard to talk about. Pleasure Fix is an app designed to help couples explore their sexuality by trying new things. Sexy porn for women by Joybear pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 22:11:00" d="2020-10-30 22:33:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: Feeling Hot</n>    <k>A porn for women scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit female friendly porn , sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 22:33:00" d="2020-10-30 23:07:00"><n>The Artist: Max Deeds, Anna Rose &amp; Cherry Kiss</n>    <k>Another beautiful production by Studio Sinful, containing lots of close-ups, artistic lighting and delicious performers. In The Artist a man is sensually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 23:07:00" d="2020-10-30 23:22:00"><n u="Kara And Devon">Kara And Devon (2)</n>    <k>A sunny afternoon, a sofa and a madly in love couple. The perfect ingredients for hot sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 23:22:00" d="2020-10-30 23:35:00"><n>My first time eating oysters and pussy</n>    <k>A scene from Xconfessions by Erika Lust. In this female porn for women movie she films the 'sneaky' fantasies of her fans. In this scene we a young woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 23:35:00" d="2020-10-30 23:59:00"><n>Educating Reeves: Danny D &amp; Lou Charmelle</n>    <k>Motor racing champion Reeves wants to buy a piece of land in the countryside and build a race track. That is easier said than done? A romantic porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-30 23:59:00" d="2020-10-31 00:20:00"><n>Racetrack</n>    <k>Helena and Thomas are in the middle of a fierce video game battle, but when his car begins to pull away from the pack and her chances of victory dwindle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-31 00:20:00" d="2020-10-31 00:33:00"><n u="OOOOOH!: Phil Holliday &amp; Nikita Bellucci">OOOOOH!: Phil Holliday &amp; Nikita Bellucci (4)</n>    <k>Smart women don't wait around for pleasure to find them - they go and get it! Florence is a modern woman who is anxious to understand and experience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-31 00:33:00" d="2020-10-31 01:07:00"><n>Guide To Kinky Sex For Couples: Asa Akira &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>Kink expert Tristan Taormino gives sexlessons to discuss, explore and finally act out your wildest fantasies, with your partner! 4 Hot couples demonstrate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-31 01:07:00" d="2020-10-31 01:32:00"><n>Blindfolded Passion</n>    <k>When Uma steps through the gate at Nick's home he's waiting for her with a plan in mind and a blindfold in hand. A bathtub, kisses, teasing and lovemaking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-31 01:32:00" d="2020-10-31 01:58:00"><n>Sexology: Nick Lange &amp; Kathia Knobili</n>    <k>For her graduation project, sexology student Tess researches how the female orgasm works. Do women really like anal? Porn ofr women by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-31 01:58:00" d="2020-10-31 02:20:00"><n>In the limelight 2: Abigaile &amp; Denis Reed</n>    <k>You can taste the love in the air. This beautiful sex scene of a young couple, is full of romance, passion and lust. A porn for women scene by Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-31 02:20:00" d="2020-10-31 02:48:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: In the Evening</n>    <k>A scene from a romantic sex film by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-31 02:48:00" d="2020-10-31 03:10:00"><n>Housemates 3: Morning Sex</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-31 03:10:00" d="2020-10-31 03:36:00"><n>Anal Lovers: Esparansa &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A romantic sex scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-31 03:36:00" d="2020-10-31 04:02:00"><n>Making Ends Meet: Cheri Deville &amp; Jay Smooth</n>    <k>A suburbian family is in destress over money, but sex seems to really heal the wounds. Scorching hot sex and sharp comedy blend perfectly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-31 04:02:00" d="2020-10-31 04:35:00"><n>Girls Crush: Ildiko Sarang &amp; Simona Opavova</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-10-31 04:35:00" d="2020-10-31 05:02:00"><n>Love is in the Air: Jodi Taylor &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>When her fiance gets sucked into never-ending conversation at a friend's party, a woman lures him to the bedroom for a passionate sexual encounter</k>  </p>
</a>
