<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="64" t="2020-10-27 04:15:30"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 05:14:00" d="2020-11-03 05:30:00"><n>Going Bananas</n>    <k>Stand up and pick up a banana, read the instructions carefully, follow the rules. Wait for me lying on our big white bed, I?ll come</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 05:30:00" d="2020-11-03 05:49:00"><n>Sex in white: Amirah Adara &amp; Adrian Yuyu</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us with her female friendly porn production: ?Sex In White?, where sexual encounters take place in a pure and white scenery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 05:49:00" d="2020-11-03 06:05:00"><n>Unbridled: Stormy Daniels &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>To save her family’s ranch, city girl Avery has to return to Texas and face her demons and her old flame horse trainer Grant. Stormy Daniels stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 06:05:00" d="2020-11-03 06:28:00"><n>Horngry</n><t>S</t>    <k>Food and sex combine in a delicious foursome from Erika Lust's XConfessions series! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 06:28:00" d="2020-11-03 06:47:00"><n>Fit: Luke Hardy &amp; Jasmine Jae</n>    <k>What could be better than unwinding after a good workout. A super sexy scene from Fit by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 06:47:00" d="2020-11-03 07:13:00"><n>My Love For you: Chrissy Fox &amp; Nic Vargas</n>    <k>Roma Woodcock for Dusk's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. A pleasure to all the senses representing real-life romantic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 07:13:00" d="2020-11-03 07:42:00"><n>Sexy And She Knows It: Lutro, Dorian Del Isla &amp; Anna Polina</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 07:42:00" d="2020-11-03 08:20:00"><n>The Stepmother 8: Cameron Canada &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Billy and Julia are getting close to marriage, but each have a single parent who?s loneliness is ruining their peace. But the real problem arises when Billy can?t stop thinking about Julia?s gorgeous mother, Theresa. Will Theresa settle for quiet companionship, or will she succumb to lust for the vibrant young man. A Sweet Sinner?s daring look into forbidden passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 08:20:00" d="2020-11-03 08:40:00"><n u="Don't Tell Daddy: Carter Cruise &amp; August Ames">Don't Tell Daddy: Carter Cruise &amp; August Ames (2)</n><t>L</t>    <k>Remember being young and doing naughty things that under certain circumstances could get you grounded for a month? Weekend house parties</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 08:40:00" d="2020-11-03 09:07:00"><n>First Summer Love 2: Radek Chigsantor &amp; Samantha Joons</n><t>L</t>    <k>The temperature is not the only thing that rises. Love is in the air. The passion these couples show you is as warm as the sun - it's their &quot;first summer love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 09:07:00" d="2020-11-03 09:25:00"><n>Unbridled: Rachel Starr &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>To save her family’s ranch, city girl Avery has to return to Texas and face her demons and her old flame horse trainer Grant. Stormy Daniels stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 09:25:00" d="2020-11-03 09:48:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Touchy-Feeley</n>    <k>Alone in her bedroom, Nora hears her neighbours fucking next door - and it's seriously hot. Pressing her ear to the wall, she begins to touch herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 09:48:00" d="2020-11-03 10:02:00"><n>Some never awaken</n><t>S</t>    <k>Experience a sexual awakening through dance, movement, and passionate sex. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 10:02:00" d="2020-11-03 10:34:00"><n>Colors Of Eden: Lady Dee &amp; Thomas</n><t>L</t>    <k>A gorgeous couple having breathtakingly hot sex, in colorful surroundings, showing both intimacy and sexual fulfilment in every little detail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 10:34:00" d="2020-11-03 10:56:00"><n>Positions: Fifth</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 10:56:00" d="2020-11-03 11:24:00"><n>I Love You: Sarah Kay &amp; Angelo Godshack</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A romatic sex scene by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 11:24:00" d="2020-11-03 11:38:00"><n>Till Sex Do Us Part: Lady May &amp; Lesly Kiss</n>    <k>Helen is a young actress at the best of her life, she's got the job she likes, good friends and a well positioned boyfriend. However Helen's life changes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 11:38:00" d="2020-11-03 12:06:00"><n>Sure Feels Right: Bunny Colby &amp; Jake Adams</n>    <k>Sometimes love is found in the most unlikely places and maybe the one that you're with isn't necessarily the one that you were destined for. Four sensual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 12:06:00" d="2020-11-03 12:28:00"><n>Hugman</n>    <k>My girlfriend and I are not serious people, we like to have fun in our lives and we are always playing tricks and games to spice up our life. Playful porn by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 12:28:00" d="2020-11-03 12:46:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Julia De Lucia &amp; Miguel Zayas</n>    <k>Porn for women by Joybear. Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 12:46:00" d="2020-11-03 13:18:00"><n>The Passionate Three: Evelyn Dellai, Jean, Angel Piaff</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 13:18:00" d="2020-11-03 13:27:00"><n>Momentum 4: Sun on our skin</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 13:27:00" d="2020-11-03 13:38:00"><n>Eat with me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Be fed all your deepest and most delicious desires by a gorgeous celeb chef. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 13:38:00" d="2020-11-03 13:56:00"><n u="Horizont">Horizont (2)</n>    <k>Horizont II is less a story than it is an evocation of atmosphere and emotion. With the wind blowing, waves crashing, and the sun shining, Miller and Sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 13:56:00" d="2020-11-03 14:02:00"><n>Bad Sometimes: Didac Duran</n><t>L</t>    <k>After the acclaimed success of his first film, Lara Tinelli surprises us with a completely different and transgressive film while staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 14:02:00" d="2020-11-03 14:31:00"><n>Our Summer of Love: Sienna Day &amp; Mugur</n>    <k>A hot couple travels abroad and adores the new country, but they enjoy each other even more and especially the new sexy people they meet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 14:31:00" d="2020-11-03 14:55:00"><n>Sun stroke: Stephanie</n>    <k>When international DJ Cosmo needs a secluded escape, his boss? sun-kissed Spanish villa is the perfect location. The unannounced arrival of Chloe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 14:55:00" d="2020-11-03 15:21:00"><n>Cum Inside Me 2: Emily Red &amp; Joe T</n><t>L</t>    <k>Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you how to have a strong, respectful and happy sex life with your loved one. Porn for couples by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 15:21:00" d="2020-11-03 15:39:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 5: The Biker</n>    <k>Apolonia Lapiedra is a beautiful Spanish pornstar who is a classic example of good girl gone bad. In this scene, a gorgeous couple, Apolonia and Emilio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 15:39:00" d="2020-11-03 16:05:00"><n>Sexual Situations: Friends with Benefits Sex</n>    <k>&quot;Wanna have sex?&quot; Gorgeous Gina Valentina takes the viewer through 5 sexy scenarios illustrating the various ways that people hook up -- Casual sex, kinky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 16:05:00" d="2020-11-03 16:29:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 7: Dana deArmond &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>An ambitious young man, with a nave mother and a philandering father, returns home from college to discover that the girl next door has grown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 16:29:00" d="2020-11-03 16:45:00"><n>Hello Pool Boy</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: “I clean your pool. Easy going, good hearted, always horny.” In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 16:45:00" d="2020-11-03 17:23:00"><n>Trying New Things: Casey Calvert &amp; Anthony Rosano</n>    <k>Passions explode when a sexually frustrated Alison asks her fiancé to take her virginity two weeks before their wedding day. Sara discovers that adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 17:23:00" d="2020-11-03 17:44:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Clea Gaultier &amp; Anthony Gaultier</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 17:44:00" d="2020-11-03 18:09:00"><n>Come Closer: Summer Love</n>    <k>Feeling the summer? This couple is going outdoors to enjoy each other and make their time together worthwhile. A real couple having natural sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 18:09:00" d="2020-11-03 18:39:00"><n>So Wet Beside Her: Tina Kay &amp; Timea Bella</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 18:39:00" d="2020-11-03 18:57:00"><n>Strip Chess</n>    <k>Are you up for a chess game? Join Silvia Rubi and Gabe Romero in this intimate scene full of chemistry, where the game (and the increasing lack of clothes)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 18:57:00" d="2020-11-03 19:08:00"><n>Make some time for us</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: Samantha Bentley and Franck Franco make a gorgeous couple in this confession about sex when you're a parent. In XConfessions, people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 19:08:00" d="2020-11-03 19:45:00"><n>Couples Massage: Antonia Sainz &amp; Adam Black</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too. A beautiful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 19:45:00" d="2020-11-03 20:06:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 1: Girlfriends</n>    <k>Apolonia Lapiedra is a beautiful Spanish spinner who is a classic example of good girl gone bad. In this scene, two gorgeous girls, Apolonia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 20:06:00" d="2020-11-03 20:32:00"><n>Special Moments: The Second Date</n>    <k>What happens after the second date? Find out in this new romantic sex scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label: Ooh la la</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 20:32:00" d="2020-11-03 21:02:00"><n>Wet!: A Wet Suprise</n>    <k>Sinful couples enjoy having seks when it pours? What's on your bucket list? A SinfulXXX film by Roma Amor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 21:02:00" d="2020-11-03 21:09:00"><n>Before The Guests Arrive</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: Against the clock, this couple engage in a hot quickie before their dinner guests arrive! In XConfessions, people from all around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 21:09:00" d="2020-11-03 21:29:00"><n>Housemates 2: Satine Spark &amp; Seth Strong</n>    <k>New house. New rules. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 21:29:00" d="2020-11-03 21:48:00"><n>Trouble X 2: Cherie Deville &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>On his first day back in the dating game, Nick meets not one but TWO beautiful women. Olivia (Abigail Mac) is hot, sexy, and confident. Jenny (Cherie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 21:48:00" d="2020-11-03 22:06:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: First Time</n>    <k>Dusk-tv presents: explicit porn for women and couples by Lara Tinelli. A pleasure to all the senses representing real-life sex full of intimacy, laughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 22:06:00" d="2020-11-03 22:24:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Lynna Nilsson &amp; Clarke Kent</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She whips two city workers into a frenzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 22:24:00" d="2020-11-03 22:57:00"><n>Sexy and Sensual: Mary Dee &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A romantic sex scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 22:57:00" d="2020-11-03 23:22:00"><n>Love Lust Longing: Jessica Drake &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Love Lust &amp; Longing takes place in a seemingly innocent Bed &amp; Breakfast. Rachel a prostitute who has set up shop in the master bedroom falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 23:22:00" d="2020-11-03 23:54:00"><n>Girls Crush: Constanze Berankova &amp; Nicole Dandova</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-03 23:54:00" d="2020-11-04 00:28:00"><n>My Hotwife's Lover: The Freedom of Being Tied Down</n>    <k>Kristin's (Karla Kush) forbidden attraction to her husband's best friend reaches a breaking point when he arranges a private get-together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 00:28:00" d="2020-11-04 01:00:00"><n>Momentum 4: Go for a walk</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 01:00:00" d="2020-11-04 01:22:00"><n>Facade: Cassidy Klein &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students, who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 01:22:00" d="2020-11-04 01:33:00"><n>Parallel Universe</n><t>S</t>    <k>There is another world out there, a world where you can exist purely as a piece of furniture. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 01:33:00" d="2020-11-04 01:55:00"><n>Ball Control: Rebecca More &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one Milf on this pitch with all the power. Physio Eva puts her massage skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 01:55:00" d="2020-11-04 02:16:00"><n>Sexy And Sensual 2: Sonia Sweet &amp; Vincent</n>    <k>Sensual but kind of naughty. These beautiful and sexy couples take you on a journey to their romantic escapades. Loving porn for couples by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 02:16:00" d="2020-11-04 02:35:00"><n>Room 208: Pamela Sanchez &amp; Sasha blonnde</n>    <k>An explicit porn for women video by Dusk TV's female friendly porn label &quot;Oh la la&quot;. Romantic sex films depicting real excitement and passion. A realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 02:35:00" d="2020-11-04 03:03:00"><n>The Escort 2: Lola Foxx &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>When a beautiful young woman enters the escorting profession, she's put off by her first client. But under the tutelage of a smart and capable madam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 03:03:00" d="2020-11-04 03:22:00"><n>I wish I was a lesbian</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maria's deepest fantasies come true when she finds herself being hosted by a hot and sweet lesbian couple. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 03:22:00" d="2020-11-04 03:54:00"><n>Hair Down There: Nadine Sage &amp; Bruce Venture</n><t>L</t>    <k>She's got hair down there, and yes, we love that natural look! Let Mia Malkova, Nadine Sage, Tracey Sweet, and Anastasia Morna show you how their naturally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 03:54:00" d="2020-11-04 04:17:00"><n>Cum Inside Me 2: Katty West &amp; Joe T</n><t>L</t>    <k>Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you how to have a strong, respectful and happy sex life with your loved one. Porn for couples by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 04:17:00" d="2020-11-04 04:38:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Julia Roca &amp; Julia De Lucia</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 04:38:00" d="2020-11-04 04:58:00"><n>Que Es La Pasion</n>    <k>A couple, clearly in love, kissing and indulging in a brief bit of spontaneous sex. While there is affection and romance in the air, there's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-04 04:58:00" d="2020-11-04 05:23:00"><n>Two Girls Sofa</n>    <k>Two girls on a sofa, what else is there to do on a Sunday when you have nothing planned? These girls decide to explore each other's bodies</k>  </p>
</a>
