<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="63" t="2020-10-29 03:53:50"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 05:25:00" d="2020-11-05 05:46:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Three Wishes</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 05:46:00" d="2020-11-05 06:09:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Miranda &amp; Joe T</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 06:09:00" d="2020-11-05 06:30:00"><n>Special Moments: The Shower</n><t>L</t>    <k>Watch how this couple shares a steamy shower. A romantic sex scene by Dusk TV's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women, sensuous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 06:30:00" d="2020-11-05 06:45:00"><n>From Beyond: Aaliyah Love &amp; Jay Smooth</n><t>L</t>    <k>Romantic porn scene with a young couple fully in love. Let the beautiful Aaliyah Love &amp; Jay Smooth show you how they take care of eachothers needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 06:45:00" d="2020-11-05 06:58:00"><n>Late night out</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: When that little bit too much makes you uncontrollably horny! In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 06:58:00" d="2020-11-05 07:27:00"><n>Brave Hearts: Abigaile Johnson &amp; George Uhl</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sarah (Faye Regan), the most famous Romance Novelist in the world, is writing the final book in her series of best-selling love stories. Admired by women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 07:27:00" d="2020-11-05 07:55:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Cayla Lions &amp; Nick Larsen</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it take to have fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 07:55:00" d="2020-11-05 08:14:00"><n>The Invitation: Lola Gatsby &amp; Dean Van Damme</n>    <k>Jane and Tom's car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves knocking on a stranger?s door only to be presented with an invitation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 08:14:00" d="2020-11-05 08:37:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction 2: Lilly Love &amp; Danny Mountain</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 08:37:00" d="2020-11-05 08:55:00"><n>Arousal</n>    <k>If you ever wondered why everybody wants to make threesomes with these two? Super sexy porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 08:55:00" d="2020-11-05 09:10:00"><n>Bad Sometimes: Didac Duran &amp; Erica Fontes</n><t>L</t>    <k>After the acclaimed success of his first film, Lara Tinelli surprises us with a completely different and transgressive film while staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 09:10:00" d="2020-11-05 09:35:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: Brandi Love &amp; Lucas Frost</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody! Cuckold porn for women by Wicked Pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 09:35:00" d="2020-11-05 09:47:00"><n>Titty Titty Bang Bang</n><t>S</t>    <k>Miriam Prado is feeling like dancing. Breasts will jiggle and sparks will fly. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 09:47:00" d="2020-11-05 10:05:00"><n>The Invitation: Sienna Day &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>Jane and Tom decide to pack the kids off and book a romantic weekend away. When their car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 10:05:00" d="2020-11-05 10:29:00"><n>Her Desire: The Couch</n>    <k>A great scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit erotic films for women and couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 10:29:00" d="2020-11-05 10:57:00"><n>Black Obsession</n>    <k>Sinful interracial couples enjoy colorful erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 10:57:00" d="2020-11-05 11:32:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 6: Chloe Foster &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Robbie dreaded meeting his girlfriend's mother, but when he finally does, he's taken back as how friendly, alluring and sensual she really is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 11:32:00" d="2020-11-05 11:56:00"><n>Afternoon Delight: April O'Neil &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>Attractive people that have sex on gorgeous locations. A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 11:56:00" d="2020-11-05 12:24:00"><n>A Sensual Touch: Tamara Grace &amp; Marc Rose</n>    <k>Intimate lovers escape the stresses of every day life and spend some relaxing time together. Couples pamper each other with erotic massage and intense sexual pleasure. From Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 12:24:00" d="2020-11-05 12:51:00"><n>Faithless: Aaliyah Love &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>&quot;Laura (Whitney Wright) is an aspiring actress from small town America who made her way to LA with stars in her eyes. Her boyfriend waits patiently</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 12:51:00" d="2020-11-05 13:09:00"><n>Quartet: Inspiration</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 13:09:00" d="2020-11-05 13:23:00"><n>Public Submission</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sometimes you find the most thrilling encounters where you least expect. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 13:23:00" d="2020-11-05 13:53:00"><n>Sexual Bliss: Keira &amp; Chriss</n>    <k>Four passionate couples in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 13:53:00" d="2020-11-05 14:13:00"><n>Housemates 2: Ava Dalush &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Romantic porn with pornstars: Ava Dalush &amp; Tyler Nixon. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 14:13:00" d="2020-11-05 14:36:00"><n>Our Sexual Secrets 2: Dolce Vita &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Our Sexual Secrets 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 14:36:00" d="2020-11-05 14:52:00"><n u="Ages of Sex: Sex at">Ages of Sex: Sex at (50)</n>    <k>The Ages of Sex is a porn for women film by Thagson. 4 Well known directors will direct a short which represents a woman?s sexual reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 14:52:00" d="2020-11-05 15:08:00"><n>From Beyond: Monka Mora &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>Sofia is mourning her beloved husband, but still feels him everywhere in their house. Is he haunting her for a reason? Her best friend helps Sofia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 15:08:00" d="2020-11-05 15:24:00"><n>Maquillaje</n>    <k>It is a statement that girls just want to have fun. But how they do it? In ?Maquillaje? two girl friends are spending a pleasant afternoon together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 15:24:00" d="2020-11-05 15:44:00"><n>Fit: Alexei Jackson &amp; Amarna Miller</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized - what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 15:44:00" d="2020-11-05 16:15:00"><n>Confessions Of A Sinner: Dorian Del Isla &amp; Simony Diamond</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic female friendly porn film by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 16:15:00" d="2020-11-05 16:43:00"><n>Anne And Ryan</n>    <k>A new film from Dusk!Academy in collaboration with director Michelle Flyn.In this scene, we</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 16:43:00" d="2020-11-05 16:55:00"><n>That Guy At The Nudist Beach</n><t>S</t>    <k>Julia Roca and Bel Gris play a gorgeous Spanish couple, seducing each other on a deserted beach. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 16:55:00" d="2020-11-05 17:18:00"><n>Girl Next Door Likes It Dirty: Alexis Adams &amp; Ryan McLane</n>    <k>All of these next door girls are young, free, and secretly wild who love it dirty! They all get their pussies passionately pulverized over the course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 17:18:00" d="2020-11-05 17:35:00"><n u="Ages of Sex: Sex at">Ages of Sex: Sex at (30)</n>    <k>The Ages of Sex is a porn for women film by Thagson. 4 Well known directors will direct a short which represents a woman?s sexual reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 17:35:00" d="2020-11-05 18:04:00"><n>Jungleicious: Stacy Cruz &amp; Mugur</n>    <k>In a dream, Antonia goes out in the woods. She finds her love, sleeping and waiting for her to touch him. First softly, then firm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 18:04:00" d="2020-11-05 18:27:00"><n>Housemates 3: Decoupled</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 18:27:00" d="2020-11-05 19:04:00"><n>Perfect And Pure: Mary Dee &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Romantic and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A romantic porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 19:04:00" d="2020-11-05 19:22:00"><n>Soulmates</n>    <k>Nothing more fun than watching beautiful people together with your partner. Especially if that ends in super nice sex with your 'Soulmate(s)'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 19:22:00" d="2020-11-05 19:48:00"><n>The Escort 2: Presley Hart &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>When a beautiful young woman enters the escorting profession, she's put off by her first client. But under the tutelage of a smart and capable madam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 19:48:00" d="2020-11-05 20:26:00"><n>A love triangle 2: Casey Calvert, Dana DeArmond &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>It?s time for yoga class! Sensuous Dana DeArmond leads the star studded class flaunting her sexual appetite for both men and women. A Mile High film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 20:26:00" d="2020-11-05 20:37:00"><n>Be A Hero</n><t>S</t>    <k>Anneke woke up horny and spotted her boyfriend's go pro lying around. What will she do with it? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 20:37:00" d="2020-11-05 21:03:00"><n>Trying New Things: Kasey Warner &amp; Richie Calhoun</n>    <k>Passions explode when a sexually frustrated Alison asks her fiancé to take her virginity two weeks before their wedding day. Sara discovers that adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 21:03:00" d="2020-11-05 21:22:00"><n>Quartet: The Teacher</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 21:22:00" d="2020-11-05 21:47:00"><n>Breakfast for Two</n>    <k>These girlfriends just wanna have fun. With each other. Especially while having a sleepover. A female friendly porn production by Dusk porn-TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 21:47:00" d="2020-11-05 22:18:00"><n>A Touch Of Lust: The Book of Love</n>    <k>In this scene an intimate dance ends up in sultry sex on the kitchen table. A cinematic feast for the eyes by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 22:18:00" d="2020-11-05 22:38:00"><n>Ouija</n>    <k>My girlfriend asked me to play with a Ouija board tonight. I?m dying to have some wild sex here on the floor. Let?s ask the ghosts what they think about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 22:38:00" d="2020-11-05 22:50:00"><n>Try My Boyfriend</n><t>S</t>    <k>Her boyfriend was so good at cunnilingus that she felt the need of sharing him. With the world! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 22:50:00" d="2020-11-05 23:20:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Eveline Dellai &amp; Nick Vargas</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it take to have fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 23:20:00" d="2020-11-05 23:40:00"><n>Sex in white: Amirah Adara &amp; Adrian Yuyu</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us with her female friendly porn production: ?Sex In White?, where sexual encounters take place in a pure and white scenery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-05 23:40:00" d="2020-11-06 00:09:00"><n>My Love For you: Vinna Reed &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>A sex film by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 00:09:00" d="2020-11-06 00:42:00"><n>Black Desire</n>    <k>Sinful interracial couples enjoy colorful erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 00:42:00" d="2020-11-06 00:55:00"><n>The Couchsurfer</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: Making the most of your house guests has never been so sexy. In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 00:55:00" d="2020-11-06 01:16:00"><n>Positions: Third</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 01:16:00" d="2020-11-06 01:41:00" c="1"><n>The Possession Of Mrs Hyde: Seth Gamble, Kenna James &amp; Victoria Voxxx</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Possession of Mrs. Hyde is Axel Braun's first non-parody feature in 15 years and his most ambitious movie to date. Shot entirely in Black and White</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 01:41:00" d="2020-11-06 02:04:00"><n>The Party</n>    <k>A breasty Spanish beauty can’t get any sleep because of the loud party next door. But when she sees her attractive neighbor her angry feelings fade away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 02:04:00" d="2020-11-06 02:25:00"><n>The Invitation: Amber Nevada &amp; Ryan Ryder</n>    <k>Jane and Tom decide to pack the kids off and book a romantic weekend away. When their car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 02:25:00" d="2020-11-06 02:54:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Vinna Reed &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>Did you ever notice the softness of your lovers skin, the sweet taste when you move your tongue over her well formed sensual body? A porn for women film by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 02:54:00" d="2020-11-06 03:04:00"><n u="From Beyond: Chanel Preston &amp; Ryan Mclane">From Beyond: Chanel Preston &amp; Ryan Mclane (2)</n>    <k>Sofia is mourning her beloved husband, but still feels him everywhere in their house. Is he haunting her for a reason? Her best friend helps Sofia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 03:04:00" d="2020-11-06 03:27:00"><n>Make Me Sweat: Kristof &amp; Kattie</n>    <k>A passionate couple in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy. Porn for women with a focus on the humand body</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 03:27:00" d="2020-11-06 03:56:00"><n>The Exes And Ohhs: Jade Nile &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>While helping friends plan a wedding, Jade and Michael?s lingering feelings ignite a passionate conversation about what went wrong in their relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 03:56:00" d="2020-11-06 04:26:00"><n>Silver Shoes: Mimosa</n>    <k>This award-winning explicit erotic trilogy from Jennifer Lyon Bell intertwines three short stories about the carnal power of what we wear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 04:26:00" d="2020-11-06 04:51:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: Aaliyah Love &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt (Aaliyah Love and Tommy Pistol) have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-06 04:51:00" d="2020-11-06 05:06:00"><n>Cinema X Pigalle</n><t>S</t>    <k>The piano goes on as an old porn movie is projected just for their own private arousal. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
</a>
