<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="63" t="2020-10-25 03:47:54"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 05:10:00" d="2020-11-01 05:28:00"><n>Fantasies Come True 2: Dillion Harper &amp; Billy Hart</n><t>O</t>    <k>The fantasies of a lifetime can be yours in five breathtaking scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica. A ballet studio, tennis court</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 05:28:00" d="2020-11-01 05:40:00"><n>Hit Me With Your Best Shot</n>    <k>Every time he grabs it he feels so strong, as if his virility depended on it. It starts to annoy me when he's been shooting at cans for an</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 05:40:00" d="2020-11-01 05:51:00"><n>Bad Sometimes: Sausage</n><t>L</t>    <k>After the acclaimed success of his first film, Lara Tinelli surprises us with a completely different and transgressive film while staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 05:51:00" d="2020-11-01 06:08:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Olivia Austin &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 06:08:00" d="2020-11-01 06:19:00"><n>Hysterical Piano Concert</n><t>S</t>    <k>A pianist's ultimate sexual fantasy is played out in an intimate concert that hits an exquisite note! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 06:19:00" d="2020-11-01 06:39:00"><n>Sun stroke: Michelle And Jade</n>    <k>These girls are trying to beat the spanish summer heat at their beautiful summerhouse in the woods. But cooling down appears to be a major challenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 06:39:00" d="2020-11-01 07:03:00"><n>Tenderness: Alexis Crystal &amp; George Lee</n>    <k>A romantic sex scene by Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Romantic porn films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 07:03:00" d="2020-11-01 07:33:00"><n>Desire For Sex: Diner D'amour</n>    <k>A beautiful film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene a couple enjoys a delicious dinner. But when it's time for desert they themselves take place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 07:33:00" d="2020-11-01 08:06:00"><n>Forbidden Affairs: My Wife's Sister 2: Veruca James &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Two sisters are in love with the same man. The older sister lets her career get in the way, and lets him go. Years later, when he returns married</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 08:06:00" d="2020-11-01 08:30:00"><n>Recipe for Romance: Allie Haze &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Love is cooking in Carolina's kitchen, and it's wonderfully delicious! Carolina is a passionate cook who is patiently waiting for Mr. Right. But what if Mr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 08:30:00" d="2020-11-01 08:56:00"><n>In the limelight 2: Denisa Heaven &amp; Denis Reed</n>    <k>These beautiful pornstars surpass your wildest dreams to fulfill their sexual desires. A romantic female friendly porn film by Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 08:56:00" d="2020-11-01 09:14:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Mia Li &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 09:14:00" d="2020-11-01 09:36:00"><n>Exposure: Add Contact</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 09:36:00" d="2020-11-01 09:48:00"><n>My moaning neighbor</n><t>S</t>    <k>Your neighbor is always moaning out of pleasure, and quite loudly. What would you do? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 09:48:00" d="2020-11-01 10:19:00"><n>Sexy Massage Fantasies: A Touch of Oil</n>    <k>A beautiful sensual film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene oil is key when exploring and touching each other's body. Sexual massages are hot!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 10:19:00" d="2020-11-01 10:36:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Bianca Resa &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 10:36:00" d="2020-11-01 11:00:00"><n>Intimate Moments 2: Sonia Sweet &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Wondering what it takes to have that fantastic sex that you will remember for the rest of your life? These beautiful desirable women are highly confident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 11:00:00" d="2020-11-01 11:13:00"><n>Bad Sometimes: Lara Tinelli &amp; Valentina Bianco</n><t>L</t>    <k>After the acclaimed success of his first film, Lara Tinelli surprises us with a completely different and transgressive film while staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 11:13:00" d="2020-11-01 11:42:00"><n>Facade: Keira Nicole &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 11:42:00" d="2020-11-01 12:04:00"><n>Milk</n>    <k>What kind of Milk are you drinking today? A romantic porn video featuring pornstar Julia Roca by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 12:04:00" d="2020-11-01 12:26:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Dessert</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 12:26:00" d="2020-11-01 13:03:00"><n>Nymphomaniac Diaries: Giggolo's</n>    <k>The blond Katerina loves sex so much that her dreams are filled with kinky stuff, but her sexual fantasies with men and women become even better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 13:03:00" d="2020-11-01 13:34:00"><n>Connections: Aeryn Walker &amp; Theodore Dalton</n>    <k>Connections, celebrates all that?s great about sex: passion, laughter, teasing, giving, receiving, &amp; experiencing real pleasure. It?s about the connection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 13:34:00" d="2020-11-01 14:22:00"><n>Feminist &amp; Submissive</n><t>S</t>    <k>Can you be a feminist and submissive? A round table discussion accompanies a sensual BDSM scene. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 14:22:00" d="2020-11-01 14:41:00"><n>Fill Me Up With Your Orgasm: Kennedy Nash &amp; Billy Hart</n>    <k>Such a waste to just get a little bit? Whether it be a refill on your drink, your gas tank, or your favorite piece of pussy, you gotta fill it to the brim! It's going to be a sticky situation when they get a fill of love butter that they crave! A Pure Passion film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 14:41:00" d="2020-11-01 14:58:00"><n>Bad Sometimes: Erica Fontes, Angelo Ferro &amp; Emilio Ardana</n><t>L</t>    <k>After the acclaimed success of his first film, Lara Tinelli surprises us with a completely different and transgressive film while staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 14:58:00" d="2020-11-01 15:41:00"><n>Light my Fire: Max Deeds &amp; Angel Wicky</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 15:41:00" d="2020-11-01 16:02:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Julia De Lucia &amp; Emilio Adrana</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 16:02:00" d="2020-11-01 16:27:00"><n>Anal Lovers: Liona &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A realistic porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 16:27:00" d="2020-11-01 16:44:00"><n>The Fantasy Project: Vivienne L, Max &amp; Harley Jay</n><t>L</t>    <k>Have you ever been in a threesome? These three lovers show what it could be like if your fantasies came true. This erotic video by Louise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 16:44:00" d="2020-11-01 16:58:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Katana &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 16:58:00" d="2020-11-01 17:26:00"><n>The Stepmother 14: Keisha Grey &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Andrew is mad at his dad when he misses out on important stuff to take care of his step-mother who broke her leg. Until he realizes how hot and sensual she is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 17:26:00" d="2020-11-01 17:43:00"><n>Birthday Surprise</n><t>S</t>    <k>It's Danny's birthday and Poppy has a big surprise prepared - he just needs to enjoy the show! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 17:43:00" d="2020-11-01 18:10:00"><n>My Wife's First Girlfriend: Jenna Sativa &amp; Leah Gotti</n>    <k>Jenna?s secret desires become unleashed when her husband catches her masturbating to lesbian porn. When Jimmy notices a growing attraction between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 18:10:00" d="2020-11-01 18:30:00"><n>The Invitation: Luke Hotrod, Ava Austen &amp; Carly Rae</n>    <k>Jane and Tom decide to pack the kids off and book a romantic weekend away. When their car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 18:30:00" d="2020-11-01 18:59:00"><n>My Love For you: Ana Rose &amp; Figi</n>    <k>A romantic film from Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 18:59:00" d="2020-11-01 19:29:00"><n>Sex Sinners and Saints: Spiritual Desire</n>    <k>Not only is the church the perfect place to confess your sins, it's also the perfect location to have sensational sex. These couples sin in church, moaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 19:29:00" d="2020-11-01 19:47:00"><n>K</n>    <k>Inspiration can reach us when we are less expecting it. The simple vision of a white sheet of paper stresses me a bit as I am a writer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 19:47:00" d="2020-11-01 19:58:00"><n>Magic Magnus</n><t>S</t>    <k>There's nothing like a man who dares to do a bit of dancing in order to spice things up, right? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 19:58:00" d="2020-11-01 20:24:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Renata Fox &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. An erotic sex scene from Favorite Fantasies 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 20:24:00" d="2020-11-01 20:41:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Carol Ferrer &amp; Pablo Ferrari</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first film as director for Thagson with a vibrant female friendly porn story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 20:41:00" d="2020-11-01 21:10:00"><n>Special Moments: Reading</n>    <k>Female friendly porn by Dusk TV's own label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. A pleasure to all the senses representing romantic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 21:10:00" d="2020-11-01 21:36:00"><n>Raw: Denisa &amp; Radek</n>    <k>Beautiful images of sexual tenderness in its pure but raw way. Close-ups of gorgeous toned bodies and horny sweat. One of Sinful?s most beautiful productions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 21:36:00" d="2020-11-01 21:44:00"><n>Carnival Hustlers</n><t>S</t>    <k>Two rival thieves take advantage of a Carnival to sneak around a Fifth Avenue inspired party, in disguise. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 21:44:00" d="2020-11-01 22:06:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Cherry Kiss &amp; Matt Bird</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 22:06:00" d="2020-11-01 22:23:00"><n>Red Light: Bree Daniels &amp; Skin Diamond</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 22:23:00" d="2020-11-01 22:59:00"><n>I Am All Yours: Daphne Klyde &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>A film by Dawn for Dusk's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting realistic excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 22:59:00" d="2020-11-01 23:20:00"><n>Sun stroke: Boiling point</n>    <k>When international DJ Cosmo needs a secluded escape, his boss? sun-kissed Spanish villa is the perfect location. Chloe soon becomes an intense distraction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 23:20:00" d="2020-11-01 23:44:00"><n>Love Me Forever: Lily Cat &amp; Vega</n><t>L</t>    <k>Romantic, passionate love. These couples show each other how much they enjoy each others company. A romantic porn video by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-01 23:44:00" d="2020-11-02 00:11:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: Angela White &amp; Donny Rock</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other. But they have yet to find true love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 00:11:00" d="2020-11-02 00:43:00"><n>Private Spa: Carlo Minaldi &amp; Rebecca Volpetti</n>    <k>This beautiful couple enjoys every bit of their private spa. We like it that hot! A delightful video by studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 00:43:00" d="2020-11-02 01:02:00"><n>Recipe for Romance: Gracie Glam &amp; Levi Cash</n>    <k>Love is cooking in Carolina's kitchen, and it's wonderfully delicious! Carolina is a passionate cook who is patiently waiting for Mr. Right. But what if Mr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 01:02:00" d="2020-11-02 01:17:00"><n>The Fantasy Project: Madison Missina &amp; Ryan James</n>    <k>Kate Eden?s research into female sexual fantasies leads her deep into the erotic imagination of women, a lush world of pleasure without consequences. But will Kate?s passion for her work lead her to lose herself ? and her relationship? A female friendly porn film by Louise Lush</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 01:17:00" d="2020-11-02 01:41:00"><n>After Forever: Britney Amber &amp; Chadalva</n>    <k>When Derrick plans a romantic weekend in his vacation house he soon finds out that his ex Penny had the same idea with her new partner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 01:41:00" d="2020-11-02 01:54:00"><n>A Talk Too Dirty</n><t>S</t>    <k>The power of dirty talk is a wonderful thing. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 01:54:00" d="2020-11-02 02:15:00"><n>Ball Control: Sienna Day &amp; Jess West</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but these two women on this pitch hold all the power. A romantic lesbian porn scene by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 02:15:00" d="2020-11-02 02:41:00"><n>Gentle Loving: Katarina &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 02:41:00" d="2020-11-02 03:06:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Take Me Now</n>    <k>A hot romantic porn for women scene by Lara Tinelli for women who love rough sex with a guy who has a a big dick. A female friendly porn video by Dusk TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 03:06:00" d="2020-11-02 03:29:00"><n>Upon Further Reflection: Brittney Amber &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Fiction writer, James Wharton (Ryan Mclane), is suffering from writers block and a drinking problem. His ex-wife is making his life a living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 03:29:00" d="2020-11-02 03:39:00"><n>Garden of Eden</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: Ever thought about a fresh fuck in the middle of nature, covered in the fruit of mother natures creation? In XConfessions, people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 03:39:00" d="2020-11-02 04:04:00"><n>Love is in the Air: Jenna J Ross &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>When her fiance gets sucked into never-ending conversation at a friend's party, a woman lures him to the bedroom for a passionate sexual encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 04:04:00" d="2020-11-02 04:40:00"><n>Exploring Couples 2: Sofi Goldfinger &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A beautiful porn for women scene from Exploring Couples 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-11-02 04:40:00" d="2020-11-02 05:03:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Daydreams</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
</a>
