<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-10-24 04:33:14"><p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 06:00:00" d="2020-10-31 06:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig IV (44)</n>    <k>66% While enjoying a tea break, Mr Bull accidentally breaks his delicate teapot. He takes the pieces to Miss Rabbit in the hope that she can mend it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 06:05:00" d="2020-10-31 06:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig IV (45)</n>    <k>66% It is fruit day at the supermarket, and Miss Rabbit is making fruit smoothies. Everyone is picking their favourite fruits to blend. George gets a special</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 06:10:00" d="2020-10-31 06:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig IV (46)</n>    <k>66% George gets a dinosaur balloon, but keeping hold of it proves difficult. Who will save George's balloon from flying off to the moon?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 06:15:00" d="2020-10-31 06:20:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig IV (47)</n>    <k>Pirate Peppa and her friends put together a treasure chest. But shortly after they bury it, Pedro realises that he's lost something!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 06:20:00" d="2020-10-31 06:35:00"><n u="Sunny Bunnies">Sunny Bunnies IV (23)</n>    <k>Comic animated antics of five colourful balls of light</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 06:35:00" d="2020-10-31 07:15:00"><n u="Shane The Chef">Shane The Chef I (27)</n>    <k>It's Halloween, and the townsfolk are decorating the restaurant with bunting and pumpkin lanterns. Shane leaves instructions with Izzy to make the pumpkin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 07:15:00" d="2020-10-31 07:25:00"><n u="Fireman Sam">Fireman Sam XI (13)</n>    <k>It's the day of the Pontypandy Giant Vegetable Competition. James has grown an enormous pumpkin, but when he tries to transport it to the park balanced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 07:25:00" d="2020-10-31 07:35:00"><n u="Ricky Zoom">Ricky Zoom I (22)</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 07:35:00" d="2020-10-31 07:45:00"><n u="Daisy &amp; Ollie">Daisy &amp; Ollie III (15)</n>    <k>With their trusty toys, Boo the Monkey and Whizzy the Robot, Daisy and Olly seek out answers to questions all kids have</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 07:45:00" d="2020-10-31 07:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig III (46)</n>    <k>Peppa and George go to play with their cousin Chloe and her friends, but the older children don't want to play any childish games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 07:55:00" d="2020-10-31 08:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig V (5)</n>    <k>66% Popular preschool animated series about a lovable piglet and her family. It's Halloween! Peppa has been helping Grandpa Pig carve his massive pumpkin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 08:05:00" d="2020-10-31 08:20:00"><n u="Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom">Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom II (9)</n>    <k>73% Holly and Ben spend a day at Lucy's school, but they must avoid being spotted by the teacher, Miss Cookie. Will they make it to the end of the lesson?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 08:20:00" d="2020-10-31 08:50:00"><n u="Butterbean's Café">Butterbean's Café I (74)</n>    <k>The Bean Team is trying to prep for their big party, but spooky things keep happening. Cricket is convinced it is a ghost, until she realises something cuter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 08:50:00" d="2020-10-31 09:15:00"><n u="Abby Hatcher">Abby Hatcher I (52)</n>    <k>Otis gets mistaken for a real dog while trick or treating, and Abby and the group need to find him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 09:15:00" d="2020-10-31 09:25:00"><n u="Pirata and Capitano">Pirata and Capitano I (4)</n>    <k>A pair of friendly dolphins help Pirata and crew to find some lost treasure which is only accessible at high tide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 09:25:00" d="2020-10-31 09:50:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (18)</n>    <k>64% It's Halloween in Adventure Bay, but a mysterious kid in a giant spider costume takes all the goodies from the trick-or-treaters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 09:50:00" d="2020-10-31 09:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig III (48)</n>    <k>Peppa and her family collect apples and blackberries in Granny and Grandpa Pig's garden so that they can make a pie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 09:55:00" d="2020-10-31 10:00:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig III (49)</n>    <k>Mrs Zebra teaches Peppa, George, Zoe, Zaza and Zuzu Zebra how to make a real tea set from clay</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 10:00:00" d="2020-10-31 10:15:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants XI (48)</n>    <k>78% Plankton lies to his grandma that he owns the Krusty Krab, and has to keep the lie going when she comes to visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 10:15:00" d="2020-10-31 10:25:00"><n u="Ryan's Mystery Playdate">Ryan's Mystery Playdate I (3)</n>    <k>Kick-flip into the day as Ryan shreds through extreme challenges to hang with his mystery playdate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 10:25:00" d="2020-10-31 10:30:00"><n u="Access MMXX">Access MMXX (220)</n>    <k>A daily round-up of showbiz news and gossip from around the world, focusing on celebrities, movies, music and entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 10:30:00" d="2020-10-31 11:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (3)</n>    <k>Almost everyone seems to know who the father of Rachel's baby is. Phoebe and Joey lie about a gas leak to get into Monica and Chandler's apartment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 11:00:00" d="2020-10-31 11:25:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (4)</n>    <k>Ross and Rachel's attempt to explain how they ended up in bed together degenerates into an argument. Monica and Chandler return from their honeymoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 11:25:00" d="2020-10-31 11:55:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (5)</n>    <k>Ross is horrified to learn that Rachel has a date with a handsome soap opera actor. Phoebe is attracted to a chef</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 11:55:00" d="2020-10-31 12:25:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (6)</n>    <k>At Monica's Halloween party, Phoebe meets her twin sister's fiance and finds that she is attracted to him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 12:25:00" d="2020-10-31 12:55:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (7)</n>    <k>When Ross learns that Rachel wants to get her own place, he suggests a vacancy in his building, only to learn that the elderly occupant is not quite dead yet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 12:55:00" d="2020-10-31 14:40:00"><n u="Christmas At Holly Lodge">Christmas At Holly Lodge (1)</n>    <k>Sophie runs the scenic Holly Lodge, the perfect Christmas getaway destination. But despite solid numbers, she is in dire financial straits. A development</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 14:40:00" d="2020-10-31 16:30:00"><n u="A Hero's Christmas">A Hero's Christmas (1)</n>    <k>Audrey and Sergeant Matt have been exchanging letters with each other for a while. Matt gets stationed in Audrey's hometown and the two get a chance to meet face-to-face</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 16:30:00" d="2020-10-31 18:15:00"><n u="A Christmas In Tennessee">A Christmas In Tennessee (1)</n>    <k>A baker in a small mountain town unites the town's inhabitants into opposing the plans of a real estate developer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 18:15:00" d="2020-10-31 18:20:00"><n u="5 News">5 News (87)</n><t>D</t>    <k>National and international news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 18:20:00" d="2020-10-31 19:45:00"><n u="Cruising With Jane McDonald MMXX">Cruising With Jane McDonald MMXX (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jane uncovers a little-known cruise route in the Great Lakes of America and Canada. She takes in the Rock n Roll Hall of Fame in post-industrial Cleveland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 19:45:00" d="2020-10-31 21:00:00"><n u="USA by Train with Tony Robinson">USA by Train with Tony Robinson (1)</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 21:00:00" d="2020-10-31 22:55:00"><n u="1,000 Years of History: USA">1,000 Years of History: USA I (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>From its first Viking visitors a millennium ago, to the Pilgrim Fathers settling at Plymouth Harbour, to independence in the 18th century, the gold rush</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-31 22:55:00" d="2020-11-01 01:55:00"><n u="The Kennedy's">The Kennedy's I (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Includes interviews with JFK's friend and confidante Priscilla McMillan, JFK's nephew and Teddy Kennedy's son Patrick as well as Bobby Kennedy's daughter Kathleen</k>  </p>
</a>
