<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="37" t="2020-10-23 04:44:48"><p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 05:50:00" d="2020-10-30 06:00:00"><n u="Access MMXX">Access MMXX (44)</n>    <k>A daily round-up of showbiz news and gossip from around the world, focusing on celebrities, movies, music and entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 06:00:00" d="2020-10-30 06:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I (3)</n>    <k>Peppa’s best friend, Suzy Sheep, comes to play at Peppa’s house. Peppa won’t let George join in. She says the games are just for big girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 06:05:00" d="2020-10-30 06:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I (4)</n>    <k>66% Peppa and George visit their Granny and Grandpa. Granny Pig is very excited about her new pet, a parrot called Polly who can repeat everything you say</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 06:10:00" d="2020-10-30 06:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I (5)</n>    <k>66% Peppa and George are playing hide and seek. Peppa is very good at hiding but she complains that George is too easy to find. Peppa doesn’t want to play with him any more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 06:15:00" d="2020-10-30 06:35:00"><n u="Mya Go">Mya Go I (16)</n>    <k>It's another sunny day in the town of Everyday, and the family are going on a picnic for Mother's Day! However, when they realise that the picnic basket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 06:35:00" d="2020-10-30 06:45:00"><n u="Fireman Sam">Fireman Sam VI (4)</n>    <k>After Sam and Tom put up signs warning everyone about some unsafe paths near the cliffs, Norman takes Mandy in search of a golden eagle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 06:45:00" d="2020-10-30 06:55:00"><n u="Thomas &amp; Friends: Big World! Big Adventures!">Thomas &amp; Friends: Big World! Big Adventures! XXIV (10)</n>    <k>Thomas travels to the land down under, where he helps his friend Ace overcome his fear of animals so that he can compete in Australia's Super Stunt Rally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 06:55:00" d="2020-10-30 07:25:00"><n u="Blue's Clues &amp; You!">Blue's Clues &amp; You! I (9)</n>    <k>It is an exciting day for Magenta because she is getting glasses! We go with her to meet Dr Eyeleen, too!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 07:25:00" d="2020-10-30 07:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig VI (12)</n>    <k>66% When George loses the key for his new toy robot in the long grass at Granny and Grandpa's house, Grandpa can't find his old metal detector to look for it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 07:30:00" d="2020-10-30 07:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig VI (43)</n>    <k>66% Madame Gazelle leave the class with Mr Bull while she goes to the dentist. The children already know the subjects Mr Bull suggests teaching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 07:40:00" d="2020-10-30 08:00:00"><n u="Ricky Zoom">Ricky Zoom I (35)</n>    <k>Ricky is upset when Loop is crowned The Crosswalk Helper for their class instead of him. But when the role becomes too much for Loop, Ricky is the first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 08:00:00" d="2020-10-30 08:15:00"><n u="Pirata and Capitano">Pirata and Capitano I (43)</n>    <k>Racket the Ogre wants to become a pirate and Pirata is in charge of training him, but he has no pirate qualities whatsoever! However, her 'bad student'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 08:15:00" d="2020-10-30 08:30:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol VI (10)</n>    <k>64% CGI kids' show about six heroic puppies. Rubble leads the pups in building an emergency landing pad for Captain Gordy in this Ultimate Construction Rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 08:30:00" d="2020-10-30 08:45:00"><n u="The Adventures of Paddington">The Adventures of Paddington (21)</n>    <k>Animated version of the Paddington bear stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 08:45:00" d="2020-10-30 08:55:00"><n u="Daisy &amp; Ollie">Daisy &amp; Ollie III (5)</n>    <k>Daisy and Ollie go on an adventure to find out why bats don't bump into things in the dark. They find out about super-hearing and echolocation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 08:55:00" d="2020-10-30 09:10:00"><n u="Shane The Chef">Shane The Chef I (16)</n>    <k>Shane gets trapped in the lighthouse lift and can't finish making his spicy autumn stew for the evening menu in the restaurant. He phones Izzy and talks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 09:10:00" d="2020-10-30 09:15:00"><n u="Sunny Bunnies">Sunny Bunnies I (4)</n>    <k>Ready, steady, go! The Sunny Bunnies appear at an athletics stadium and have their own hurdles race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 09:15:00" d="2020-10-30 11:15:00"><n u="Jeremy Vine MMXX">Jeremy Vine MMXX (217)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jeremy Vine discusses and dissects the latest news, views and opinions, with co-host Storm Huntley helping on the live phone-ins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 11:15:00" d="2020-10-30 12:10:00"><n u="Can't Pay? We'll Take It Away!">Can't Pay? We'll Take It Away! V (17)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Max and Steve have a writ to recover a disputed debt owed by the owner of a bridal shop, and also face a challenging eviction. Gary and Cona are chasing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 12:10:00" d="2020-10-30 12:15:00"><n u="5 News MMXX">5 News MMXX (217)</n><t>D</t>    <k>National and international news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 12:15:00" d="2020-10-30 13:10:00"><n u="The Nightmare Neighbour Next Door">The Nightmare Neighbour Next Door III (2)</n>    <k>Documentary series about Britain's feuding neighbours, using CCTV footage and material from victims' own cameras. In this episode, a couple trying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 13:10:00" d="2020-10-30 13:15:00"><n u="Access MMXX">Access MMXX (44)</n>    <k>A daily round-up of showbiz news and gossip from around the world, focusing on celebrities, movies, music and entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 13:15:00" d="2020-10-30 13:45:00"><n u="Home and Away MMXX">Home and Away MMXX (7425)</n>    <k>When Jai gets sick during Dean's first night caring for him, Ziggy has to step in. Is Dean cut out to be a father? Tori and Christian dine at Salt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 13:45:00" d="2020-10-30 14:15:00"><n u="Neighbours MMXX">Neighbours MMXX (8469)</n>    <k>Dipi and Pierce have gone into a full blown affair, but their respective guilt brings them to treat their partners incredibly generously</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 14:15:00" d="2020-10-30 16:00:00"><n u="Betrayed By Lies">Betrayed By Lies (1)</n>    <k>A woman discovers that her husband, who she suspected of having an affair, actually has another complete family. She also finds out that his business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 16:00:00" d="2020-10-30 16:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (1)</n>    <k>The wedding reception is almost upstaged by the news that someone might be pregnant. Ross and Joey are out to impress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 16:30:00" d="2020-10-30 17:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (2)</n>    <k>Monica and Phoebe speculate about who might be the father of Rachel's baby, while Rachel debates whether or not to tell the unsuspecting dad at all</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 17:00:00" d="2020-10-30 17:30:00"><n u="5 News MMXX">5 News MMXX (217)</n><t>D</t>    <k>National and international news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 17:30:00" d="2020-10-30 18:00:00"><n u="Neighbours MMXX">Neighbours MMXX (8469)</n>    <k>Dipi and Pierce have gone into a full blown affair, but their respective guilt brings them to treat their partners incredibly generously</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 18:00:00" d="2020-10-30 18:30:00"><n u="Home and Away MMXX">Home and Away MMXX (7425)</n>    <k>When Jai gets sick during Dean's first night caring for him, Ziggy has to step in. Is Dean cut out to be a father? Tori and Christian dine at Salt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 18:30:00" d="2020-10-30 19:00:00"><n u="5 News">5 News (217)</n><t>D</t>    <k>National and international news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 19:00:00" d="2020-10-30 19:55:00"><n u="The Gadget Show">The Gadget Show XXXII (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Using AI-equipped gear, Ortis creates a new theme song for the show, Georgie sees how Ocado uses AI for effeciency, and Paul Sinha assesses AI assistants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 19:55:00" d="2020-10-30 20:00:00"><n u="5 News MMXX">5 News MMXX (217)</n><t>D</t>    <k>National and international news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 20:00:00" d="2020-10-30 20:58:00"><n u="Secret Scotland With Susan Calman">Secret Scotland With Susan Calman III (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Susan explores the central belt between Edinburgh and Glasgow. After boarding the Royal yacht Britannia, Susan assists at feeding time at Edinburgh Zoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 20:58:00" d="2020-10-30 21:00:00"><n u="5 News MMXX">5 News MMXX (217)</n><t>D</t>    <k>National and international news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 21:00:00" d="2020-10-30 22:00:00"><n u="Friday on the Farm">Friday on the Farm I (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>A sixteen-year-old champion shepherdess visits the farm to give Rob some tips about training Pip, his new sheepdog. JB Gill finds out all about growing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-10-30 22:00:00" d="2020-10-31 01:00:00"><n u="Fifty Shades Freed">Fifty Shades Freed (1)</n>    <k>46% Now married and adjusting to their domestic bliss, Christian and Ana find their honeymoon interrupted by the sinister plans of a shadowy face from the past</k>  </p>
</a>
