<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2020-10-30 03:40:03"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 05:10:00" d="2020-11-06 05:40:00"><n>Dispatches</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Britain's Covid Jobs Crisis:. 
. ispatches: As the furlough scheme ends, Dispatches follows a minimum-wage vacancy at a Manchester restaurant, which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 05:40:00" d="2020-11-06 06:35:00"><n>Fifteen to One</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Fifteen contestants go head to head in the iconic quiz hosted by Sandi Toksvig. They face notoriously tough questions as they compete to become Grand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 06:35:00" d="2020-11-06 06:50:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp takes on a big challenge: crafting a vintage-inspired wedding for Amy and Craig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 06:50:00" d="2020-11-06 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Helen Fospero joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 07:30:00" d="2020-11-06 07:50:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Cigar Talk: When Joyce invites Vince to attend her high school reunion, Vince tells Mike that he never graduated from high school and asks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 07:50:00" d="2020-11-06 08:10:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Victoria's Birthday: Victoria panics as her 30th birthday approaches, and she drags Mike and Molly into the drama of her full-blown 'life crisis'. Ep22)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 08:10:00" d="2020-11-06 08:40:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers V (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Thanksgiving Orphans: The Cheers gang are at a loose end for Thanksgiving, so they gather at Carla's house to prepare a meal and celebrate the holidays</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 08:40:00" d="2020-11-06 09:05:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers V (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Everyone Imitates Art: Diane gets a rejection letter from a magazine for a poem she has submitted and feels humiliated when Sam subsequently sends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 09:05:00" d="2020-11-06 09:35:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Ray's Ring: Ray loses his wedding ring and is propositioned by an attractive woman at the airport. When Debra finds out what happened, she pretends to be single too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 09:35:00" d="2020-11-06 10:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Frank Goes Downstairs: After hurting themselves during a tryst, Ray and Debra say that they fell down the stairs. But when Frank gets hurt doing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 10:05:00" d="2020-11-06 10:35:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jealous Robert: Debra and Marie's good intentions backfire when they try to drive Robert back into Amy's arms - and find out that Amy and Gianni are hitting it off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 10:35:00" d="2020-11-06 11:05:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Oops: Frasier carelessly passes on a snippet of juicy gossip that leads to his colleague Bulldog losing his job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 11:05:00" d="2020-11-06 11:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Death Becomes Him: Frasier is forced to come to terms with his own mortality when a seemingly healthy colleague dies suddenly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 11:35:00" d="2020-11-06 12:30:00"><n u="Undercover Boss USA">Undercover Boss USA VII (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Ashley and Brandon Wright, the co-owners of Hamburger Mary's, go incognito in their company, to ensure that their culture of diversity is being maintained</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 12:30:00" d="2020-11-06 12:35:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 12:35:00" d="2020-11-06 13:30:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Long Beach in California to save Nino's, a failing Italian family restaurant that opened in 1958 and is now under the misguided</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 13:30:00" d="2020-11-06 15:10:00"><n>Steph's Packed Lunch</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: Steph's Packed Lunch
Steph McGovern presents her live lunchtime show featuring celebrity guests, fantastic food and the best entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 15:10:00" d="2020-11-06 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Helen Fospero joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 16:00:00" d="2020-11-06 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tracey and Iain from Wales fell in love with Ibiza on a family holiday and now want to buy a property in the pretty town of Santa Eularia. Can Ben Hillman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 17:00:00" d="2020-11-06 18:00:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Steve and Angela revamp their poolside al fresco kitchen, and Dick and Angel give their magnificent five-metre-high staircase a makeover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 18:00:00" d="2020-11-06 18:30:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>F</e>    <k>It's the final day and the B&amp;Bers meet for one last time to settle some scores. After bedtime blues and follicle findings are aired, the payments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 18:30:00" d="2020-11-06 19:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Leeds area. Darren plans to put a fancy twist on an apparently basic menu. But Billy is concerned about the amount of mustard that Darren is using. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 19:00:00" d="2020-11-06 19:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXVIII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>87% There Will Be Buds: Series 28 continues, new to Channel 4. Homer gets roped into coaching the kids' lacrosse team with Milhouse's dad, Kirk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 19:30:00" d="2020-11-06 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXVIII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>87% Havana Wild Weekend: Series 28 continues, new to Channel 4. The Simpsons take a family trip to Cuba to get affordable medical care for Grampa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 20:00:00" d="2020-11-06 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 21:00:00" d="2020-11-06 22:00:00"><n u="The Great British Bake Off: An Extra Slice">The Great British Bake Off: An Extra Slice IV (7)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>60% New: The Great British Bake Off. 
. n Extra Slice: Jo Brand's joined by Harry Hill, Sunetra Sarker and Martin Kemp, who go retro and get stuck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 22:00:00" d="2020-11-06 23:00:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XVI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Gogglebox
Britain's sharpest armchair critics share more of their insightful, passionate and sometimes emotional critiques of the week's biggest and best shows. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 23:00:00" d="2020-11-07 00:30:00"><n u="The Last Leg">The Last Leg XX</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: The Last Leg: US Elegtion. 
. pecial: As the confetti settles in town halls across America, Adam Hills, Josh Widdicombe and Alex Brooker react</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-07 00:30:00" d="2020-11-07 01:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXVIII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>87% Treehouse of Horror XXVII: Series 28 continues, new to Channel 4. Mr Burns introduces a Hunger Games-style contest in which Springfield's children fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-07 01:00:00" d="2020-11-07 01:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Treehouse of Horror XXI: Bart and Milhouse's board games come to life, Homer and Marge rescue a sinister castaway on a sailing holiday, and Lisa is smitten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-07 01:30:00" d="2020-11-07 03:30:00"><n>T2 Trainspotting</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Ewan McGregor stars in Danny Boyle's drama sequel. Twenty years after betraying his friends, Renton returns to Edinburgh. Adults only: very strong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-07 03:30:00" d="2020-11-07 04:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Plymouth. Van driver Annie Wroe serves up a racy menu with a risqué name for each course, followed by unconventional entertainment. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-07 04:00:00" d="2020-11-07 04:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Plymouth. After some fiery exchanges on Annie's night, Suzanne Hyde hopes that her 'simple' style of cooking will impress her rivals. (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-07 04:25:00" d="2020-11-07 04:55:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Plymouth. Former sailor Tony hopes to prove he's the best cook in the group with a triple-bird roast and a triple-chocolate mousse. He also makes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-07 04:55:00" d="2020-11-07 05:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Plymouth. Sarah Joy has witnessed night after night of rows, and now wants to bring a sense of joy to proceedings by rolling out the disco</k>  </p>
</a>
