<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2020-10-28 03:46:50"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 05:45:00" d="2020-11-04 06:40:00"><n>Fifteen to One</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Fifteen contestants go head to head in the iconic quiz hosted by Sandi Toksvig. They face notoriously tough questions as they compete to become Grand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 06:40:00" d="2020-11-04 07:25:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp helps Amber and Colin turn their love-starved bedroom into a vintage haven. With the flat-pack furniture gone, will it be transformed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 07:25:00" d="2020-11-04 07:50:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike's Feet: Mike and his police partner Carl begin to get on each other's nerves after working too many double shifts together during a snowstorm. Ep17)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 07:50:00" d="2020-11-04 08:10:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Peggy Shaves Her Legs: When Peggy and Molly have lunch together, Mike worries that his mother is telling Molly unflattering stories about his childhood. Ep18)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 08:10:00" d="2020-11-04 08:35:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers V (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>House of Horrors with Formal Dining and Used Brick: Carla discovers her reasonably priced new house is haunted, so Cliff comes over to keep her company</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 08:35:00" d="2020-11-04 09:00:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers V (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Tan 'n' Wash: Norm has invested in a combination tanning salon and launderette, but when he gets the Cheers gang involved in promoting the place, things begin to go wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 09:00:00" d="2020-11-04 09:30:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Let's Fix Robert: Marie gets Robert's ex and his police partner Judy together in an effort to understand why her son can't seem to commit to a relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 09:30:00" d="2020-11-04 09:55:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Say Uncle: When Ray realises that his kids would rather spend time with their Uncle Robert than with him, he decides to do something about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 09:55:00" d="2020-11-04 10:25:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Separation: Debra is upset by the unexpected news that her parents have separated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 10:25:00" d="2020-11-04 10:55:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Crucible: Frasier throws a dinner party to show off a painting he's bought, but when he finds out that the artwork is a fake, he worries that he's becoming shallow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 10:55:00" d="2020-11-04 11:25:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Call Me Irresponsible: Frasier starts dating Catherine, the jilted girlfriend of one of his callers, and begins advising the poor guy that he shouldn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 11:25:00" d="2020-11-04 12:20:00"><n u="Undercover Boss USA">Undercover Boss USA VII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Bryon Stephens, the president and chief operating officer of Marco's Pizza, goes incognito among his employees, to assess how the firm and its franchises are faring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 12:20:00" d="2020-11-04 13:15:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Beaver, Pennsylvania, where he meets a brother and sister whose inability to work together is risking their father's life savings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 13:15:00" d="2020-11-04 13:30:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 13:30:00" d="2020-11-04 15:10:00"><n>Steph's Packed Lunch</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: Steph's Packed Lunch
Steph McGovern presents her live lunchtime show featuring celebrity guests, fantastic food and the best entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 15:10:00" d="2020-11-04 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Helen Fospero joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 16:00:00" d="2020-11-04 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Maxine and Cormac got married in the Dordogne region of France and now want to buy a holiday home near Riberac on a budget of ?100,000</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 17:00:00" d="2020-11-04 18:00:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tim and Sasha plan to turn their original bathing pool into a unique feature. Fiona hosts a party to celebrate her chateau's 845th birthday, using</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 18:00:00" d="2020-11-04 18:30:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>F</e>    <k>Husband and wife Mike and Del give their guests a real taste of Wales at Deri-Down Guest House in Abergavenny. But bed blunders and a pre-order brekkie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 18:30:00" d="2020-11-04 19:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Leeds area. Drama teacher and DJ Denver aims to bring a taste of Ibiza to Yorkshire, with a Spanish menu, Prosecco van and stilt walkers. But Darren finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 19:00:00" d="2020-11-04 19:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXVIII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>87% The Town: Series 28 continues, new to Channel 4. Homer catches Bart supporting Springfield's football rival the Boston Americans, so he plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 19:30:00" d="2020-11-04 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Theresa and John Paul team up to beat the McQueens' blackmailer, and John Paul is shocked when he thinks that he's uncovered their identity. The Maaliks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 20:00:00" d="2020-11-04 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 21:00:00" d="2020-11-04 22:00:00"><n>Autumn at Jimmy's Farm</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Autumn at Jimmy's Farm
Jimmy Doherty and his team prepare the farm and wildlife park for autumn, as they welcome some new and unpredictable animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 22:00:00" d="2020-11-04 23:00:00"><n u="Educating Greater Manchester">Educating Greater Manchester II</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Educating Greater Manchester
Holly bids to be voted Head Girl. Year 10's Jack is on a final warning for making prank phone calls. And a gaggle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 23:00:00" d="2020-11-05 00:05:00"><n>First Dates Hotel</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: First Dates
This trip down memory lane looks at how sometimes opposites attract, including an eccentric theology student, a 'Norse God'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 00:05:00" d="2020-11-05 01:10:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XIX</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Sean Lock and Joe Wilkinson take on Jon Richardson and Kiri Pritchard-McLean. The Brett Domino Trio join Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 01:10:00" d="2020-11-05 02:05:00"><n>Deliveroo: Secrets of Your Takeaway</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Deliveroo: Secrets of Your. 
. akeaway: The story of how Britain's fastest-growing food delivery company has revolutionised the takeaway industry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 02:05:00" d="2020-11-05 02:55:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In Bridgeport, Connecticut, Gordon Ramsay visits Cafe Tavolini, a restaurant that is being neglected as the couple who run it teeter on the edge of divorce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 02:55:00" d="2020-11-05 05:05:00"><n>The Fifth Estate</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Drama about the WikiLeaks whistle-blowing website. Starring Benedict Cumberbatch, Daniel Brühl, David Thewlis, Peter Capaldi and Laura Linney. Strong language/violence</k>  </p>
</a>
