<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2020-10-27 04:04:09"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 05:35:00" d="2020-11-03 06:30:00"><n>Fifteen to One</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Fifteen contestants go head to head in the iconic quiz hosted by Sandi Toksvig. They face notoriously tough questions as they compete to become Grand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 06:30:00" d="2020-11-03 07:30:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp gets her bangers in a twist making sausages and pork pies for a competition at the Nidderdale Show in North Yorkshire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 07:30:00" d="2020-11-03 07:50:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>First Valentine's Day: Mike makes special plans for his first Valentine's Day with Molly, but the romantic scheme is jeopardised when he accidentally meets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 07:50:00" d="2020-11-03 08:10:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Joyce &amp; Vince and Peaches &amp; Herb: When Mike decides the couch is his new best friend and he doesn't want to leave the house, Molly goes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 08:10:00" d="2020-11-03 08:40:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers V (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Money Dearest: Cliff sets his mother up to marry a very wealthy man, but his scheme goes awry when his future stepfather announces that he's giving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 08:40:00" d="2020-11-03 09:05:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers V (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Abnormal Psychology: Frasier is excited to appear on a TV show featuring a debate between psychiatrists until he learns his opponent is a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 09:05:00" d="2020-11-03 09:35:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Humm Vac: Marie and Debra have a housekeeping war after Ray buys a cutting-edge vacuum cleaner from an attractive saleswoman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 09:35:00" d="2020-11-03 10:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Canister: Tempers flare when Marie accuses Debra of not returning a borrowed canister that holds sentimental value, but Debra insists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 10:05:00" d="2020-11-03 10:35:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Net Worth: Debra becomes angry when Ray contributes $1000 to his friends' hare-brained scheme to open a go-kart business without consulting her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 10:35:00" d="2020-11-03 11:05:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>I Hate Frasier Crane: When Frasier becomes the target of a hate campaign organised by a local newspaper columnist, Martin and Daphne encourage him to fight back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 11:05:00" d="2020-11-03 11:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Here's Looking at You: When Martin meets a woman while tinkering with his telescope, Frasier encourages the romance, but his father is suddenly hesitant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 11:35:00" d="2020-11-03 12:30:00"><n u="Undercover Boss USA">Undercover Boss USA VII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Scott Gerber, CEO of hospitality business the Gerber Group, goes undercover in his own organisation, to ensure it is maintaining the reputation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 12:30:00" d="2020-11-03 12:35:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 12:35:00" d="2020-11-03 13:30:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits the Olde Hitching Post restaurant in Hanson, Massachusetts. Tom bought the business for his daughter six years ago but refuses to let her run it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 13:30:00" d="2020-11-03 15:10:00"><n>Steph's Packed Lunch</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: Steph's Packed Lunch
Steph McGovern presents her live lunchtime show featuring celebrity guests, fantastic food and the best entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 15:10:00" d="2020-11-03 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Colin Murray joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 16:00:00" d="2020-11-03 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Neil and Linda from Lanarkshire want a rustic holiday home near Antequera in southern Spain to enjoy with all the family. Danni Menzies shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 17:00:00" d="2020-11-03 18:00:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Erin and JB set out to transform their ruined orangery into an events venue. Tensions bubble when a new spa is delivered to Tim and Sasha's chateau</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 18:00:00" d="2020-11-03 18:30:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>F</e>    <k>Best mates Glenn and Leon host at The White Horse Hotel in Storrington in West Sussex. There are hair-raising concerns and damp discoveries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 18:30:00" d="2020-11-03 19:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Leeds area. Finance director Jane plans a fine dining menu of homemade ravioli, pork and panna cotta. But Denver is still upset about Jane calling her a goth. (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 19:00:00" d="2020-11-03 19:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXVIII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>87% Friends and Family: Series 28 continues, new to Channel 4. Mr Burns hires the Simpsons as his live-in virtual reality family but excludes Homer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 19:30:00" d="2020-11-03 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Theresa fears that it's her turn to be exposed by the McQueens' blackmailer. Edward tries to buy Verity's silence. James and Sami do some digging on Kurt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 20:00:00" d="2020-11-03 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 21:00:00" d="2020-11-03 22:15:00"><n u="The Great British Bake Off">The Great British Bake Off IV (7)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: The Great British Bake Off
It's 1980s Week. The bakers put their twist on the quiche in the signature and tackle a retro treat in the technical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 22:15:00" d="2020-11-03 23:15:00"><n u="Educating Greater Manchester">Educating Greater Manchester II</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Educating Greater Manchester
The series about modern schooling and teen life returns for a new run to Harrop Fold School, where Jacob discusses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-03 23:15:00" d="2020-11-04 00:20:00"><n>New: Alton Towers: A Roller...</n><e>F</e>    <k>. oaster Year: Behind the scenes as one of Britain's top tourist attractions reopens after being shut for lockdown. Can management and staff bring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 00:20:00" d="2020-11-04 01:20:00"><n u="Taskmaster">Taskmaster X</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy game show. Mawaan Rizwan attempts a farm-related illusion in the hope of impressing domineering Taskmaster Greg Davies. Plus: pasta disasters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 01:20:00" d="2020-11-04 02:15:00"><n>The Bridge</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Epic ?100k reality challenge. With less than half of the bridge built, emotions run high and rumours are rife. One teammate wants to leave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 02:15:00" d="2020-11-04 03:10:00"><n>The Bridge</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Epic ?100k challenge. The group are shocked by former teammate Luke's actions. With the odds stacked against them, can they pull together, finish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 03:10:00" d="2020-11-04 04:50:00"><n>My Pure Land</n><e>F</e>    <k>Sarmad Masud describes his film as a feminist western. It's based on the extraordinary story of Nazo Dharejo, also known as Pakistan's toughest woman. Violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-04 04:50:00" d="2020-11-04 05:45:00"><n u="Vet on the Hill">Vet on the Hill V</n><e>F</e>    <k>Dr Scott cares for 12 dogs who were rescued from the South Korean meat trade and helps to find new homes for them. And what's frisky feline Gizmo up to? Ep13)</k>  </p>
</a>
