<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2020-10-29 03:48:20"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 05:05:00" d="2020-11-05 06:00:00"><n u="Vet on the Hill">Vet on the Hill V</n><e>F</e>    <k>Dr Scott travels to Cornwall to help rescue seal pups stranded along the coastline, and performs a risky operation on a rook with a broken wing. Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 06:00:00" d="2020-11-05 07:30:00"><n>Fifteen to One</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Fifteen contestants go head to head in the iconic quiz hosted by Sandi Toksvig. They face notoriously tough questions as they compete to become Grand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 07:30:00" d="2020-11-05 07:50:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Opening Day: Mike and Carl's annual pilgrimage to the Chicago Cubs baseball team's Opening Day is interrupted when Molly comes along. Ep19)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 07:50:00" d="2020-11-05 08:10:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Samuel Gets Fired: When Samuel loses his job at the diner, and then his apartment, Mike offers to let him stay at his place, with interesting results. Ep20)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 08:10:00" d="2020-11-05 08:40:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers V (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Young Dr Weinstein: After Diane boasts to everyone about her forthcoming evening out at Boston's most exclusive restaurant, Sam decides to bring her down a peg or two</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 08:40:00" d="2020-11-05 09:05:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers V (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Knights of the Scimitar: Cliff persuades Norm to join his lodge, but Norm isn't keen when he learns what it entails. Sam thinks Diane has invented a suitor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 09:05:00" d="2020-11-05 09:35:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Frank Paints the House: Frank offers to decorate Ray's house but refuses to paint it the colour that Ray and Debra want</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 09:35:00" d="2020-11-05 10:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Angry Family: The whole family meet the school's counsellor and a local clergyman to uncover why there's constant bickering between them and Michael's parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 10:05:00" d="2020-11-05 10:35:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Odd Man Out: Frank forces Marco to choose either Marie or him as a friend. Ray sides with Frank because he doesn't approve of his mother having a male friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 10:35:00" d="2020-11-05 11:05:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Beloved Infidel: Frasier and Martin finally discover something they have in common: they were both cheated on by their wives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 11:05:00" d="2020-11-05 11:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Selling Out: Frasier is in a moral and ethical quandary: should he do a commercial for a Chinese restaurant? Daphne offers her unique advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 11:35:00" d="2020-11-05 12:30:00"><n u="Undercover Boss USA">Undercover Boss USA VII (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Greg Adler, the president and CEO of off-road accessory empire 4 Wheel Parts, goes undercover in his own business. But his identity is scrutinised by one canny employee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 12:30:00" d="2020-11-05 12:35:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 12:35:00" d="2020-11-05 13:30:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In Monrovia, California, Gordon Ramsay visits Sam's Mediterranean Kabob Room, where he tries to mend relationships between the restaurant's owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 13:30:00" d="2020-11-05 15:10:00"><n>Steph's Packed Lunch</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: Steph's Packed Lunch
Steph McGovern presents her live lunchtime show featuring celebrity guests, fantastic food and the best entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 15:10:00" d="2020-11-05 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Helen Fospero joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 16:00:00" d="2020-11-05 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Home or Away
Wendy and Pete from Cambridgeshire want to buy their first home together, but can't agree on where it should be:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 17:00:00" d="2020-11-05 18:00:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tim and Rebecca plan their aviary transformation. Fiona starts renovating her first luxury suite. Wedding preparations hit boiling point for Tim and Sasha</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 18:00:00" d="2020-11-05 18:30:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>F</e>    <k>Mother and son Margaret and Fraser host at Royle Farm B&amp;B in Burton-on-Trent in Staffordshire, where some guests fixate on the fantastical furniture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 18:30:00" d="2020-11-05 19:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Leeds area. Local legend Billy serves up tried-and-tested dinner party favourites. And the best is yet to come at the end of the night with a Frank Sinatra impersonator! (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 19:00:00" d="2020-11-05 19:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXVIII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>87% Trust but Clarify: Series 28 continues, new to Channel 4. Lisa and Bart investigate Krusty's 'Krustaceans' candy. Homer asks Marge to help him dress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 19:30:00" d="2020-11-05 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Juliet's new-found confidence impresses Peri, but will Jordan ruin Juliet's chances? The McQueens' torment continues. Nancy's thoughts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 20:00:00" d="2020-11-05 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 21:00:00" d="2020-11-05 22:00:00"><n u="Ugly House to Lovely House with George Clarke">Ugly House to Lovely House with George Clarke IV</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Ugly House to Lovely House. 
. ith George Clarke: George revisits Wendy and Alan in Colchester, whose transformation of their sad 1960s property</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 22:00:00" d="2020-11-05 23:00:00"><n u="Taskmaster">Taskmaster X</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Taskmaster
Comedy game show. Daisy May Cooper flirts with a security guard, Richard Herring is surprised by chickens and Alex Horne wears sparkly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 23:00:00" d="2020-11-05 23:30:00"><n>Maxxx</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Maxxx
House Party: Outrageous comedy. Team Maxxx get an exclusive invite to Don's drug and sex-fuelled music industry party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-05 23:30:00" d="2020-11-06 00:30:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XVI</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Britain's sharpest armchair critics share more of their insightful, passionate and sometimes emotional critiques of the week's biggest and best shows. Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 00:30:00" d="2020-11-06 01:30:00"><n>First Dates Hotel</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>First Dates
This trip down memory lane looks at how sometimes opposites attract, including an eccentric theology student, a 'Norse God'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 01:30:00" d="2020-11-06 02:55:00"><n>Blackout</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Drama documentary exploring the effects of a devastating cyber-attack on Britain's national electricity grid, combining fictional scenes with footage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 02:55:00" d="2020-11-06 03:50:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In New Orleans, Gordon Ramsay visits Zeke's, a restaurant famed for its Cajun food and loyal locals. But under new ownership, standards have slipped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 03:50:00" d="2020-11-06 04:15:00"><n>Food Unwrapped Investigates</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Kate Quilton exposes the murky world of miracle diet supplements and reveals the giant internet corporations making big profits exposing young teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-11-06 04:15:00" d="2020-11-06 05:10:00"><n>Nazi Treasure Hunters</n><e>TF</e>    <k>The treasure hunters travel the world on the trail of Hermann Goering's massive art-looting operation and track down pieces that are still missing today. (Ep2)</k>  </p>
</a>
