<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="36" t="2020-10-23 04:35:30"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 05:15:00" d="2020-10-30 06:10:00"><n>Fifteen to One</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Fifteen contestants go head to head in the iconic quiz hosted by Sandi Toksvig. They face notoriously tough questions as they compete to become Grand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 06:10:00" d="2020-10-30 06:35:00"><n>Coach Trip: Road to Barcelona</n><e>TF</e>    <k>The coach reaches Porec in Croatia, picking up some newbies en route. It's a dramatic day, as a message from a departed tourist sends shockwaves through the group. (Ep13/30)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 06:35:00" d="2020-10-30 06:50:00"><n>Kirstie's Fill Your House for Free</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and the team help a couple from Wembley who own a flat but almost no furniture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 06:50:00" d="2020-10-30 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Colin Murray joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 07:30:00" d="2020-10-30 07:50:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>First Christmas: Mike attempts to find the perfect yuletide gift for Molly, but he has no idea what present he should buy her for their first Christmas together. Ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 07:50:00" d="2020-10-30 08:10:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike Goes to the Opera: When Mike becomes ill during a night out at the opera with Molly, his mother Peggy and Molly fall out over who can take better care of him. Ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 08:10:00" d="2020-10-30 08:40:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers IV (25)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Strange Bedfellows Part 2: Janet urges Sam to break all ties with the past and fire Diane, but Diane overhears them and beats him to the draw, quitting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 08:40:00" d="2020-10-30 09:05:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers IV (26)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Strange Bedfellows Part 3: Janet wins the election and hosts her press conference at the bar, where Diane causes a scene with Sam, leading</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 09:05:00" d="2020-10-30 09:35:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>What Good Are You?: Ray tries to prove his manliness after failing to act swiftly enough in an emergency involving Debra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 09:35:00" d="2020-10-30 10:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Super Bowl: Ray is sent by his paper to cover the Super Bowl, but his excitement is tempered by having to choose someone to accompany him. Will he make the right choice?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 10:05:00" d="2020-10-30 10:35:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Ray's Journal: Ray is horrified to learn that his mother used to read his diary, which contained his most personal - and perverted - thoughts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 10:35:00" d="2020-10-30 11:05:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Goodnight Seattle (Part 2/2): In the last ever episode of the sitcom, Frasier is feeling lonely on his own in the flat, and San Francisco beckons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 11:05:00" d="2020-10-30 11:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Good Son: The opening episode of the classic comedy series in which Dr Frasier Crane returns to Seattle, where he has a job as a radio psychiatrist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 11:35:00" d="2020-10-30 12:30:00"><n u="Undercover Boss USA">Undercover Boss USA VII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tim Betts, the CEO of Muscle Maker Grill, goes undercover in the organisation he recently bought, hoping to find that each restaurant branch is following the same standards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 12:30:00" d="2020-10-30 12:35:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 12:35:00" d="2020-10-30 13:30:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Barefoot Bob's beachside restaurant in Hull, Massachusetts, where husband and wife Marc and Lisa struggle to attract customers during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 13:30:00" d="2020-10-30 15:10:00"><n>Steph's Packed Lunch</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: Steph's Packed Lunch
Steph McGovern presents her live lunchtime show featuring celebrity guests, fantastic food and the best entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 15:10:00" d="2020-10-30 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Colin Murray joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 16:00:00" d="2020-10-30 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Home or Away
John and Carole have different ideas on where to buy their first home together. Will it be the wild coastline</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 17:00:00" d="2020-10-30 18:00:00"><n>The Great House Giveaway</n><e>F</e>    <k>Strangers Harry and Kaylum buy a majestic detached house in Ashton-under-Lyne at auction. Can they put their differences aside to renovate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 18:00:00" d="2020-10-30 18:30:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>F</e>    <k>It's the final day and the B&amp;Bers meet for one last time to settle some scores. After bathroom blues and cleanliness concerns are aired, the payments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 18:30:00" d="2020-10-30 19:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Edinburgh. Style-conscious Bruce hosts the final night. All week he's expressed a taste for the finer things in life. With expectations high</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 19:00:00" d="2020-10-30 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Large Marge: Marge accidentally gets breast implants after mistakenly thinking that Homer was flirting with two businesswomen while he was building houses for the homeless</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 19:30:00" d="2020-10-30 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Treehouse of Horror VII: Bart finds his evil twin in the attic, Lisa becomes God to a race of tiny people, and aliens Kang and Kodos assume the identities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 20:00:00" d="2020-10-30 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 21:00:00" d="2020-10-30 22:00:00"><n u="The Great British Bake Off: An Extra Slice">The Great British Bake Off: An Extra Slice IV (6)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>60% New: The Great British Bake Off. 
. n Extra Slice: Jo Brand's joined by Jonathan Ross, Darren Harriott and Siobhan McSweeney to discuss the action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 22:00:00" d="2020-10-30 23:00:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XVI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Gogglebox
Britain's sharpest armchair critics share more of their insightful, passionate and sometimes emotional critiques of the week's biggest and best shows. Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-30 23:00:00" d="2020-10-31 00:05:00"><n u="The Last Leg">The Last Leg XX</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: The Last Leg
BAFTA-nominated entertainment show. Adam Hills, Josh Widdicombe and Alex Brooker are joined by celebrity guests as they take a sideways</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-31 00:05:00" d="2020-10-31 00:10:00"><n>New: Random Acts: Black History...</n><e>F</e>    <k>. onth: The short film strand continues with work from emerging Black filmmakers. Denise Alder brings West African art alive in Mablo Micasso, a surreal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-31 00:10:00" d="2020-10-31 01:15:00"><n>First Dates Hotel</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>First Dates
This trip down memory lane serves up classic dates where sparks flew and love blossomed, from two tweed lovers, to an eager octogenarian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-31 01:15:00" d="2020-10-31 02:55:00"><n>The Witch</n><e>F</e>    <k>Supernatural horror with Anya Taylor-Joy, Ralph Ineson and Kate Dickie. In 1630s New England, a family suffer troubling events after being expelled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-31 02:55:00" d="2020-10-31 03:20:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Middlesbrough. Promotions rep Dawn Griffiths is confident that her curry and traditional Indian dancing will secure her the prize. But she has a tough crowd. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-31 03:20:00" d="2020-10-31 03:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Middlesbrough. Practical joker Ron Gordon plans an evening of expertly cooked food, elegant hosting and surprises. (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-31 03:50:00" d="2020-10-31 04:15:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Middlesbrough. Self-confessed loudmouth Kay Griffiths wants to liven up the week with some good food, colourful conversation and homemade punch. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-31 04:15:00" d="2020-10-31 04:45:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Middlesbrough. Cosmopolitan drama teacher Karena Serdecka treats her guests to a Dutch/Polish menu and takes to the stage for a rock chick performance with her band. (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-10-31 04:45:00" d="2020-10-31 05:10:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Middlesbrough. Binman Paul Tidy hosts the final night of the competition with a movie star-themed fancy dress party and garlic - lots of garlic. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
</a>
