<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2020-10-26 03:40:50"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 06:00:00" d="2020-11-02 07:40:00"><n>Gripsholm</n>    <k>60% Kurt (Ulrich Noethen) and Lydia (Heike Makatsch) are planning a relaxing vacation in Sweden. What Lydia does not know is that for Kurt, a well-known</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 07:40:00" d="2020-11-02 09:20:00"><n>Blood Brothers</n>    <k>Brice (Sylvain Dieuaide), the eldest son of the Lemeuniers, is accused of a quadruple murder. His brother Martin (Clément Chebli) will do whatever it takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 09:20:00" d="2020-11-02 10:20:00"><n u="Unforgiven – Episode">Unforgiven – Episode 1</n>    <k>Aurore (Mélody Gualteros), a 10-year-old girl, often escapes from her mother to play in the marshes. One evening, she joins two children, Paulo (Mathias</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 10:20:00" d="2020-11-02 11:20:00"><n u="Unforgiven – Episode">Unforgiven – Episode 2</n>    <k>Under a new name, Aurore (Élodie Bouchez) lives with her daughter, Rose (Ambre Hasaj). Now a cook in a restaurant, Aurore dedicates herself to the child</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 11:20:00" d="2020-11-02 12:20:00"><n u="Unforgiven – Episode">Unforgiven – Episode 3</n>    <k>Pretending to be a writer, Maya (Lolita Chammah) finds Aurore (Élodie Bouchez) and convinces her to write a book. One day the worst happens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 12:20:00" d="2020-11-02 14:00:00" c="1"><n>The Time of Secrets</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% The last vacations for Marcel Pagnol (Pierre-François Martin-Laval) in his favorite Provence hills prove as delightful as challenging. It is the beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 14:00:00" d="2020-11-02 15:35:00"><n>The Time of Love</n>    <k>Overcoming disciplinary committee, Marcel (Pierre-François Martin-Laval) gets to stay at high school. He becomes a leader among his new classmates, firming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 15:35:00" d="2020-11-02 17:20:00"><n u="The Salento Murders – Part">The Salento Murders – Part 1</n>    <k>A malevolent clan, probably from Calabria, has arrived in Salento to conquer the territory. Commissioner Pasquale Zagaria (Lino Banfi) is a policeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 17:20:00" d="2020-11-02 19:15:00"><n u="The Salento Murders – Part">The Salento Murders – Part 2</n>    <k>A malevolent clan, probably from Calabria, has arrived in Salento to conquer the territory. Commissioner Pasquale Zagaria (Lino Banfi) is a policeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 19:15:00" d="2020-11-02 21:00:00"><n>Fallen from the sky</n>    <k>January 1943. France is under occupation. Louise is 70, and in her bar, everyone likes to forget about the war. Her serenity is disturbed, however</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 21:00:00" d="2020-11-02 22:00:00"><n u="The Fury – Episode">The Fury – Episode 3</n>    <k>Hvozdíková (Dana Cerná) visits Kuneš (Hynek Cermák) in his cottage. She tells him that his return to Prague depends on his success in the Wágnerová case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 22:00:00" d="2020-11-02 23:00:00"><n u="The Fury – Episode">The Fury – Episode 4</n>    <k>The body of a woman showing signs of ritual violence is discovered in a flooded quarry. The circumstances of the murder are suspiciously identical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 23:00:00" d="2020-11-03 00:30:00"><n>Hearts of War</n>    <k>1953. A Russian soldier stationed in Poland falls in love with a local girl. Their forbidden romance turns them into traitors to their countries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 00:30:00" d="2020-11-03 01:30:00"><n u="The Fury – Episode">The Fury – Episode 3</n>    <k>Hvozdíková (Dana Cerná) visits Kuneš (Hynek Cermák) in his cottage. She tells him that his return to Prague depends on his success in the Wágnerová case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 01:30:00" d="2020-11-03 02:30:00"><n u="The Fury – Episode">The Fury – Episode 4</n>    <k>The body of a woman showing signs of ritual violence is discovered in a flooded quarry. The circumstances of the murder are suspiciously identical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 02:30:00" d="2020-11-03 04:20:00" c="1"><n>Crossroads</n><t>F</t>    <k>Three women, three eras, one fate. In 1923, Violeta falls in love with a young man trying to escape to France. In 1941, Ines lives in a desert waiting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 04:20:00" d="2020-11-03 06:00:00"><n>Mission: Arctic</n>    <k>Based on a true story. In 1735, a brave group of explorers ventured into the last frontier. Their perilous expedition led them to the uncharted territories of the Arctic</k>  </p>
</a>
