<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-10-29 03:46:15"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 06:00:00" d="2020-11-05 07:10:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder – Season 3 Episode">Anatomy of a Murder – Season 3 Episode 1</n>    <k>The team of detectives under the leadership of Marie Vyrova has a new case - the murder of a man shot by a crossbow. The case takes a dramatic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 07:10:00" d="2020-11-05 08:20:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder – Season 3 Episode">Anatomy of a Murder – Season 3 Episode 2</n>    <k>The revelation of a common history, strong ties, immoral behavior, and conflict of interests of five former schoolmates, leads the police</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 08:20:00" d="2020-11-05 09:30:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder – Season 3 Episode">Anatomy of a Murder – Season 3 Episode 3</n>    <k>The detective investigation becomes a race against time. After the revelation of a pattern of systematic revenge, the killer plunges the remaining</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 09:30:00" d="2020-11-05 10:30:00"><n u="The Fury – Episode">The Fury – Episode 3</n>    <k>Hvozdíková (Dana Cerná) visits Kuneš (Hynek Cermák) in his cottage. She tells him that his return to Prague depends on his success in the Wágnerová case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 10:30:00" d="2020-11-05 11:30:00"><n u="The Fury – Episode">The Fury – Episode 4</n>    <k>The body of a woman showing signs of ritual violence is discovered in a flooded quarry. The circumstances of the murder are suspiciously identical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 11:30:00" d="2020-11-05 12:15:00"><n u="The Poison Tree">The Poison Tree (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Karen takes her little girl to welcome her husband, Rex, who has just been released from prison after twelve years. Driving to their seaside home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 12:15:00" d="2020-11-05 13:00:00"><n u="The Poison Tree">The Poison Tree (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Flashbacks tell the story from the moment Karen is drawn into the extraordinary world of Biba and Rex to reveal the dark and harrowing secrets she hides now</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 13:00:00" d="2020-11-05 14:40:00" c="1"><n>Crossroads</n><t>F</t>    <k>Three women, three eras, one fate. In 1923, Violeta falls in love with a young man trying to escape to France. In 1941, Ines lives in a desert waiting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 14:40:00" d="2020-11-05 16:20:00"><n>Fallen from the sky</n>    <k>January 1943. France is under occupation. Louise is 70, and in her bar, everyone likes to forget about the war. Her serenity is disturbed, however</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 16:20:00" d="2020-11-05 17:30:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder – Season 2 Episode">Anatomy of a Murder – Season 2 Episode 1</n>    <k>The body of Professor Chalupa, a popular teacher at the Department of Linguistics, is found on the faculty’s grounds. The professor was on the trail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 17:30:00" d="2020-11-05 18:40:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder – Season 2 Episode">Anatomy of a Murder – Season 2 Episode 2</n>    <k>Another body is discovered, the editor of the regional branch of the TV news network. Marie Výrová and her team discover that Chalupa was working</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 18:40:00" d="2020-11-05 19:50:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder – Season 2 Episode">Anatomy of a Murder – Season 2 Episode 3</n>    <k>Výrová organizes a trap and mentions, in front of the Registrar, who the police suspect of planning or executing the murders. They have found compromising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 19:50:00" d="2020-11-05 21:00:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder – Season 2 Episode">Anatomy of a Murder – Season 2 Episode 4</n>    <k>As the investigation closes on the Registrar and the head of the security agency, confessions and arguments lead to a violent ending with kidnappings and shootings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 21:00:00" d="2020-11-05 21:50:00"><n u="Love Swing - Episode">Love Swing - Episode 3</n>    <k>Marta is kicked out of the circus but the guys decide to help her. Varya is unconscious in the hospital and everyone in the circus thinks that Martha set the accident up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 21:50:00" d="2020-11-05 22:40:00"><n u="Love Swing - Episode">Love Swing - Episode 4</n>    <k>Vlad’s mother organizes the arrival of the German circus. The relationship between Vlad and Alla becomes complicated. Trying to eliminate his rival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-05 22:40:00" d="2020-11-06 00:05:00" c="1"><n>Perversion</n><t>F</t>    <k>Investigating the death of a young woman, a police inspector finds himself exploring the torrid and mysterious side of Roma’s night life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 00:05:00" d="2020-11-06 00:55:00"><n u="Love Swing - Episode">Love Swing - Episode 3</n>    <k>Marta is kicked out of the circus but the guys decide to help her. Varya is unconscious in the hospital and everyone in the circus thinks that Martha set the accident up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 00:55:00" d="2020-11-06 01:45:00"><n u="Love Swing - Episode">Love Swing - Episode 4</n>    <k>Vlad’s mother organizes the arrival of the German circus. The relationship between Vlad and Alla becomes complicated. Trying to eliminate his rival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 01:45:00" d="2020-11-06 03:10:00" c="1"><n>Parental Guidance</n><t>F</t>    <k>Trying to conceive a second child, Giulio (Adriano Giannini) discovers he is infertile and suspects his wife, Veronica (Serena Autieri)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 03:10:00" d="2020-11-06 04:35:00"><n>Hearts of War</n>    <k>1953. A Russian soldier stationed in Poland falls in love with a local girl. Their forbidden romance turns them into traitors to their countries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 04:35:00" d="2020-11-06 06:00:00"><n>Burlesque</n>    <k>A young, full-figured high school teacher gets the chance to become attractive despite her ample figure by dancing in a burlesque bar. The world around</k>  </p>
</a>
