<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2020-10-30 03:37:59"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 06:00:00" d="2020-11-06 07:35:00"><n>The Perfect Stranger</n>    <k>Jonathan (Bruno Debrandt), an unhappy man who has just inherited a massive fortune, discovers that Anaďs (Audrey Fleurot), his wife, has been hospitalized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 07:35:00" d="2020-11-06 09:05:00" c="1"><n>Mont Blanc Murder</n><t>F</t>    <k>An inspector newly transferred to the small Mont Blanc region has been given a strange case, of a man whose body was trapped in the ice for 15 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 09:05:00" d="2020-11-06 10:30:00"><n>A Sicilian Dream</n>    <k>A poignant drama following the development of a young Sicilian boy, Ettore Corvaja (Corrado Fortuna), from the 1950s to 1960s. Yearning to become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 10:30:00" d="2020-11-06 12:00:00"><n>True Intentions</n>    <k>Jana and Marika meet on a train and quickly become friends. They go to the countryside, a remote mountain area that holds a lot of secrets about Jana's past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 12:00:00" d="2020-11-06 13:25:00"><n>Hearts of War</n>    <k>1953. A Russian soldier stationed in Poland falls in love with a local girl. Their forbidden romance turns them into traitors to their countries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 13:25:00" d="2020-11-06 15:05:00"><n>Blood Brothers</n>    <k>Brice (Sylvain Dieuaide), the eldest son of the Lemeuniers, is accused of a quadruple murder. His brother Martin (Clément Chebli) will do whatever it takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 15:05:00" d="2020-11-06 17:20:00" c="1"><n>Bon Voyage</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% A married couple takes their children on a camping holiday trip to France. They soon find out another couple is stalking them with harrowing intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 17:20:00" d="2020-11-06 18:10:00"><n u="Love Swing - Episode">Love Swing - Episode 3</n>    <k>Marta is kicked out of the circus but the guys decide to help her. Varya is unconscious in the hospital and everyone in the circus thinks that Martha set the accident up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 18:10:00" d="2020-11-06 19:00:00"><n u="Love Swing - Episode">Love Swing - Episode 4</n>    <k>Vlad’s mother organizes the arrival of the German circus. The relationship between Vlad and Alla becomes complicated. Trying to eliminate his rival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 19:00:00" d="2020-11-06 20:00:00"><n u="Internal Affairs - Episode">Internal Affairs - Episode 5</n>    <k>An influential and controversial businessman is shot. The shooter is Milan Smrček, a former soldier in Afghanistan, the son of the man found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 20:00:00" d="2020-11-06 21:00:00"><n u="Internal Affairs - Episode">Internal Affairs - Episode 6</n>    <k>Petr is under arrest, and his corruption case against the city's political and economic elite is about to fall. After threats against his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 21:00:00" d="2020-11-06 23:15:00" c="1"><n>Bon Voyage</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% A married couple takes their children on a camping holiday trip to France. They soon find out another couple is stalking them with harrowing intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-06 23:15:00" d="2020-11-07 01:00:00"><n>Mission: Arctic</n>    <k>Based on a true story. In 1735, a brave group of explorers ventured into the last frontier. Their perilous expedition led them to the uncharted territories of the Arctic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-07 01:00:00" d="2020-11-07 02:00:00"><n u="The Fury – Episode">The Fury – Episode 3</n>    <k>Hvozdíková (Dana Cerná) visits Kuneš (Hynek Cermák) in his cottage. She tells him that his return to Prague depends on his success in the Wágnerová case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-07 02:00:00" d="2020-11-07 03:00:00"><n u="The Fury – Episode">The Fury – Episode 4</n>    <k>The body of a woman showing signs of ritual violence is discovered in a flooded quarry. The circumstances of the murder are suspiciously identical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-07 03:00:00" d="2020-11-07 04:00:00"><n u="Unforgiven – Episode">Unforgiven – Episode 1</n>    <k>Aurore (Mélody Gualteros), a 10-year-old girl, often escapes from her mother to play in the marshes. One evening, she joins two children, Paulo (Mathias</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-07 04:00:00" d="2020-11-07 05:00:00"><n u="Unforgiven – Episode">Unforgiven – Episode 2</n>    <k>Under a new name, Aurore (Élodie Bouchez) lives with her daughter, Rose (Ambre Hasaj). Now a cook in a restaurant, Aurore dedicates herself to the child</k>  </p>
</a>
