<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-10-25 03:41:43"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 06:00:00" d="2020-11-01 07:45:00" c="1"><n>The Legend of Rita</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% The riveting true story of Rita Vogt (Bibiana Beglau), a 1970s West German terrorist who escapes to the East with the help of the Stasi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 07:45:00" d="2020-11-01 09:30:00"><n>Mission: Arctic</n>    <k>Based on a true story. In 1735, a brave group of explorers ventured into the last frontier. Their perilous expedition led them to the uncharted territories of the Arctic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 09:30:00" d="2020-11-01 10:20:00"><n u="The Hold-Up - Episode">The Hold-Up - Episode 1</n>    <k>An ordinary morning, a bank robbery intertwines the lives of the branch director, a star restauranteur, a pregnant young cop, an old policeman and other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 10:20:00" d="2020-11-01 11:10:00"><n u="The Hold-Up - Episode">The Hold-Up - Episode 2</n>    <k>While Agnes (Blandine Bellavoir), a young cop, brings supplies to the hostages, Mino (Yaniss Lespert), one of the four robbers, is ill. He needs insulin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 11:10:00" d="2020-11-01 12:00:00"><n u="The Hold-Up - Episode">The Hold-Up - Episode 3</n>    <k>Alex (Arnaud Ducret) enters the vault containing a loot of eight million euros. The hostages are still tied to each other and their eyes are bandaged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 12:00:00" d="2020-11-01 14:15:00" c="1"><n>Bon Voyage</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% A married couple takes their children on a camping holiday trip to France. They soon find out another couple is stalking them with harrowing intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 14:15:00" d="2020-11-01 15:50:00"><n>Silence of Death</n>    <k>Julie (Mélusine Mayance) lives with her mother (Pascale Arbillot) in an isolated house. She invents imaginary friends in the scary manga comics she draws</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 15:50:00" d="2020-11-01 17:35:00"><n>Gripsholm</n>    <k>60% Kurt (Ulrich Noethen) and Lydia (Heike Makatsch) are planning a relaxing vacation in Sweden. What Lydia does not know is that for Kurt, a well-known</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 17:35:00" d="2020-11-01 19:20:00"><n>Fallen from the sky</n>    <k>January 1943. France is under occupation. Louise is 70, and in her bar, everyone likes to forget about the war. Her serenity is disturbed, however</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 19:20:00" d="2020-11-01 20:10:00"><n u="Love Swing - Episode">Love Swing - Episode 1</n>    <k>Martha decides to realize her childhood dream and become a circus gymnast. A pair of trapeze artists lose their female partner and cannot continue performing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 20:10:00" d="2020-11-01 21:00:00"><n u="Love Swing - Episode">Love Swing - Episode 2</n>    <k>Martha and the guys rent a room, and in the meantime, Larisa, Vlad’s mother, tries to stop the partnership. Larisa tells the director that there, under</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 21:00:00" d="2020-11-01 22:00:00"><n u="Internal Affairs - Episode">Internal Affairs - Episode 3</n>    <k>A series of bank robberies in which the perPetrator does not hesitate to shoot is the current case of the Svoboda and Brazdil. The stakes are higher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 22:00:00" d="2020-11-01 23:00:00"><n u="Internal Affairs - Episode">Internal Affairs - Episode 4</n>    <k>A dead man is found in the railroads. Murder or suicide? In the meantime, Petr's boss feels that he has a dangerous mole in his team that he</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-01 23:00:00" d="2020-11-02 00:00:00"><n u="The Fury – Episode">The Fury – Episode 1</n>    <k>Major Kuneš (Hynek Cermák) beats up his ex-wife’s boyfriend. To save his career in the force, he is sent away by his superior for a “sabbatical”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 00:00:00" d="2020-11-02 01:00:00"><n u="The Fury – Episode">The Fury – Episode 2</n>    <k>A priest is shot dead and Kuneš (Hynek Cermák) takes the case. All the clues left intend to make it appear as a robbery gone wrong, but</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 01:00:00" d="2020-11-02 02:35:00"><n u="The Haunting of Block">The Haunting of Block 18</n>    <k>A recently married couple gets a special deal to purchase a spacious new property in a suburban high-rise building. Shortly after moving in, they realize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 02:35:00" d="2020-11-02 04:20:00" c="1"><n>Crossroads</n><t>F</t>    <k>Three women, three eras, one fate. In 1923, Violeta falls in love with a young man trying to escape to France. In 1941, Ines lives in a desert waiting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-02 04:20:00" d="2020-11-02 06:00:00"><n>Mission: Arctic</n>    <k>Based on a true story. In 1735, a brave group of explorers ventured into the last frontier. Their perilous expedition led them to the uncharted territories of the Arctic</k>  </p>
</a>
