<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-10-27 04:00:58"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 06:00:00" d="2020-11-03 07:45:00"><n u="The Salento Murders – Part">The Salento Murders – Part 1</n>    <k>A malevolent clan, probably from Calabria, has arrived in Salento to conquer the territory. Commissioner Pasquale Zagaria (Lino Banfi) is a policeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 07:45:00" d="2020-11-03 09:35:00"><n u="The Salento Murders – Part">The Salento Murders – Part 2</n>    <k>A malevolent clan, probably from Calabria, has arrived in Salento to conquer the territory. Commissioner Pasquale Zagaria (Lino Banfi) is a policeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 09:35:00" d="2020-11-03 11:05:00" c="1"><n>Mont Blanc Murder</n><t>F</t>    <k>An inspector newly transferred to the small Mont Blanc region has been given a strange case, of a man whose body was trapped in the ice for 15 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 11:05:00" d="2020-11-03 12:45:00"><n>Fallen from the sky</n>    <k>January 1943. France is under occupation. Louise is 70, and in her bar, everyone likes to forget about the war. Her serenity is disturbed, however</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 12:45:00" d="2020-11-03 14:25:00" c="1"><n>The Winds of Passion</n><t>F</t>    <k>In the climax of political turmoil in France between republicans and Catholics, a young teacher and a fierce activist fall in love and marry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 14:25:00" d="2020-11-03 15:50:00"><n>Hearts of War</n>    <k>1953. A Russian soldier stationed in Poland falls in love with a local girl. Their forbidden romance turns them into traitors to their countries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 15:50:00" d="2020-11-03 17:25:00"><n>Blind Fear</n>    <k>After a tragic car crash and losing the baby she was expecting, Betty seeks solace in a new job looking after a blind kid in a mountain house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 17:25:00" d="2020-11-03 18:10:00"><n u="The Poison Tree">The Poison Tree (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Karen takes her little girl to welcome her husband, Rex, who has just been released from prison after twelve years. Driving to their seaside home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 18:10:00" d="2020-11-03 19:00:00"><n u="The Poison Tree">The Poison Tree (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Flashbacks tell the story from the moment Karen is drawn into the extraordinary world of Biba and Rex to reveal the dark and harrowing secrets she hides now</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 19:00:00" d="2020-11-03 20:00:00"><n u="The Fury – Episode">The Fury – Episode 3</n>    <k>Hvozdíková (Dana Cerná) visits Kuneš (Hynek Cermák) in his cottage. She tells him that his return to Prague depends on his success in the Wágnerová case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 20:00:00" d="2020-11-03 21:00:00"><n u="The Fury – Episode">The Fury – Episode 4</n>    <k>The body of a woman showing signs of ritual violence is discovered in a flooded quarry. The circumstances of the murder are suspiciously identical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 21:00:00" d="2020-11-03 22:00:00"><n u="Internal Affairs - Episode">Internal Affairs - Episode 5</n>    <k>An influential and controversial businessman is shot. The shooter is Milan Smrček, a former soldier in Afghanistan, the son of the man found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 22:00:00" d="2020-11-03 23:00:00"><n u="Internal Affairs - Episode">Internal Affairs - Episode 6</n>    <k>Petr is under arrest, and his corruption case against the city's political and economic elite is about to fall. After threats against his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-03 23:00:00" d="2020-11-04 00:30:00" c="1"><n>Parental Guidance</n><t>F</t>    <k>Trying to conceive a second child, Giulio (Adriano Giannini) discovers he is infertile and suspects his wife, Veronica (Serena Autieri)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-04 00:30:00" d="2020-11-04 01:30:00"><n u="Internal Affairs - Episode">Internal Affairs - Episode 5</n>    <k>An influential and controversial businessman is shot. The shooter is Milan Smrček, a former soldier in Afghanistan, the son of the man found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-04 01:30:00" d="2020-11-04 02:30:00"><n u="Internal Affairs - Episode">Internal Affairs - Episode 6</n>    <k>Petr is under arrest, and his corruption case against the city's political and economic elite is about to fall. After threats against his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-04 02:30:00" d="2020-11-04 04:00:00"><n>Double Trouble</n>    <k>Marek lives alternately with two women. He tells them both that he works in another city for part of the week. In reality, he stays in the same and moves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-11-04 04:00:00" d="2020-11-04 05:00:00"><n u="Internal Affairs - Episode">Internal Affairs - Episode 5</n>    <k>An influential and controversial businessman is shot. The shooter is Milan Smrček, a former soldier in Afghanistan, the son of the man found</k>  </p>
</a>
